could cause price to reverse and now
start going up so where do you want to
buy you want to buy low where do you
want to sell you want to sell
high so that means that when price is
pushing up most people want to take the
profit that they have as it's as their
position is
increasing close their
order and they've made
money but then some people close their
order and want to get in
again so getting in
again let me
actually right
here so getting an
again to go
up would require you to know where the
market is going to stop and turn
around so along this entire pushup right
here along this entire pushup right here
let me just shade that
um along this entire push up while the
market was pushing
up
there were certain areas that were left
behind on this whole move here on this
whole pushup because the market doesn't
look like that when it's moving up what
does it look
like it looks like
this so since this is the one
hour since this is the one
hour if you go down to the 15
minute maybe the 15 minute if you go to
the one
minute if you get into the one
minute you begin to see
this let me change this color real
quick
this is how you teach free of
charge use your time
really on the 15 let me actually zoom
into this
s so this this huge move up is
that for a couple of hours price was
moving it kept going for a couple of
hours it kept going up
guys um on YouTube there is a huge delay
um with this um I do have some music
playing on um actually let me bring the
music down for the zoom people I do have
some music playing on Zoom um I just
turned it down some but there's about 69
people on it so if you join the um Zoom
chat a lot of your questions will be
seen faster as well as um you'll be
hearing this a lot faster not 30 seconds
delayed so
um sorry with
this with this right
here this move
up if you go down to the one hour this
is the one hour if you go down to the
the one minute or let's say the five
minute you're going to see that this
move up this straight move
up or or you know it could be you know a
couple of candles like two three
candles it could be a candle
here uh let me
actually followed by a candle here that
went
down Follow by a candle here that went
up another candle here that went up
another candle here that went
up followed by a
candle that went down like
that and then there just happened to be
like let's say a huge pushup
and you see it go like
that so this is how the market looks
when it's moving up and on one hour
you'll see the candles looking like this
on the 1
hour you'll see the candles sorry hold
on you see the candles look like
this on the one
hour I don't know why I just didn't do
that it look like this and
this is how the market moved up so it
was going up it had a pull back down
it's going up again it had a pull back
down and it was going up again
so that's how it
looks
that's how it
looks just like that on the hourly time
frame and on the hourly time
frame the highs and lows would be larger
like
this going to fix
that depending on what you're trading
sorry depending on what you're
trading it would look like that but
during that time that it's going up it's
pulling back this
is maybe an hour two three hours that
it's been
falling and then you could have a couple
hours that it's going
up for you where you want to get
in is you want to get in at an area
where price is going to continue
you or where price is going to begin to
go down if if you're trading something
that you can
short that you can
short short is to make money on the
downside the price is going down you
believe or you're you're placing a
position or a bet on the price going
down and it begins to go down that's
shorting it you're you're shorting it
there's some people that are
shorting while price is going up and
that's how they're losing as as price is
going up they they're saying we're
placing a bet essentially that it's
going to be going down based on what I
looked at this chart based on what I
looked at the chart and the chart
said so I'm going to enter a short
position and that in an uptrend in a
market that's going up you could enter a
short
position anywhere where where you see
the market retracing and you can enter a
long position anywhere you see the
market is
going up
from now on the one hour it looks like
this but let's say the the the five
minute the the the one minute let's say
that the five minute in one
minute begins to look like
this
so now it looks like this
and now you
see that on the five minute and the one
minute put it
here now you see on the five minute and
the one minute I'll move this five
minute and the one
minute price looks
different let me extend this out a
little bit just
you guys yeah on the five minute and the
one minute price looks different price
looks like
this for You artist I know this is iway
please just bear with
[Music]
me hold
on
sorry guys so here's here's a better
picture of it to women do things better
than men
right here's a better picture of
it this is how it
looks so let's say this
one black line going up is the 1
hour you have the one
minute which is this green Trend and
it's it's a series of highs and lows
highs lows highs lows high high low high
low high low high low but on the on
let's say the 15 minute on the 15 minute
it's one
low one
high one
high one one
low one high and the hourly it's
just one low and one high so you see all
of these different pullbacks on one
minute followed by these slower
pullbacks what Zer one 2 3 4 you see
that this is actually pointing
to the fact that on the one minute
there's more pullbacks to time and hope
to be right there's more opportunities
where you hope to be right or more
opportunities where you can be
wrong
versus there are less
opportunities on the
15minute and they're slower
opportunities they're not happening as
fast to be right but if you're trying to
make money for the day
you have about three to four
opportunities on the one
minute within that short amount of time
that you're trading one two hours to be
right or
wrong to be right or
wrong to be right about a pullback or
wrong about a pullback to be right about
a reversal or wrong about a
[Music]
reversal but it's literally like this
the Market's moving like
this
and if you look
here remember I said that the
market pulls back so let's say this is
the hourly
pullback the hourly pullback here's the
hourly beginning wait what is that no
here's the hourly
beginning here's the hourly um top of
the market and reversal
and the hourly
reversal led us here it stopped
here before
continuing up above like
that stop
there yeah stop there and continue up
above
so when the
hourly time frame is pulling
back what do you
have just like on this move up where on
the one or five minute you have these
series of highs and lows coming
up with these highs and
lows you could place a buy here I don't
know what this
was
you can place a buy here oh it's because
it zoomed out you can place a buy here
when price comes back to the area that
you're looking to buy
from and you can take profit or take
your money out of the market as it
increases when price goes above the high
above the the high that is going above
to the
left there's this low there's this High
there's this low and then we break
above the high that brought us down here
now this is only happening
on the one minute or the five minute on
the
hourly it looks like a
candle that's going often times up and
down you see it going up and down so if
the candle opens and let's say it opens
right
here let's say this this is a candle
opening and it starts to go up if the
candle op and it begins to go
up the candle opens and it begins to go
up it looks like this it looks like this
but if the handle begins to go back
down
because on the one minute time
frame remember what we said we can go
up and back down a number of times a
series of times we can go up and
down a series of
times so while that one minute
candle has been
formed while that one minute candle has
been
formed sorry the one hour candle while
the one hour candle's formed we have
price going like
this that whole hour and sometimes the
hour can close here the hour candle can
close right there and the candle looks
like that sometimes it can close there
and the candle looks like
that sometimes it can close down
here and the candle looks like
that yeah kind of looks like
that
it could look just like that they call
that a dogee it's actually institutional
candle looks like
that
so when this
happens it's because on a lower time
frame oh no let me just delete some of
this so it doesn't look
when this happens like
this it's because when the candle opened
up when the candle opened up let's say
this was the candle let me move some of
this out the way right
now when the candle opened up we were
here
and the the price went
down and
then during during the hour we started
to go back up again on the lower time
frame on the lower time frame we started
to go back again go back up and as we
were going back
up couple minutes later we started going
down
again and we did that during that
hour and the candle closed like
this the candle closed just like
this
because the first half of the hour we
were going down the second half of the
hour we began to go
up and then by the time the next hour
candle was opening up price was back
here and all of this happened within one
hour all of this this entire thing this
moved down this moved back up this moved
down happened in one hour so what what
were there an opportunity to go short an
opportunity to go long an opportunity to
go short again and an opportunity to go
long again that's only if you're trading
on the lower time frames you find
multiple opportunities during the day to
be able to take a position to buy or to
sell
so let me bring this
back so we begin to head
up
and and this is how we're looking for
the hourly we're going up like this on
the the one minute the five minute the
15 minute 10 minute whatever it is it's
go has a series of ups and downs highs
and lows that's what they call it highs
and lows that's what it's
called
so this is the low of the hourly Trend
this is the high of the hourly Trend and
this is where the hourly Trend pulled
back then the hourly Trend continued up
what's the trend I forgot to say that
I'm sorry guys the trend
is if the market is going up there's a
bunch of highs and lows that are created
as it's going up that's trending
up if the market is going
down that's a series of highs and lows
that are trending
down trending
down
so with the market going up you're in an
uptrend
Trend and with the market going down
you're in a downtrend a downtrend I'm
saying that for people who just may not
really understand that the
downtrend looks exactly like the
uptrend where we are
going down we make a high and then we
make another low we make a high and then
we make a another low we make a high and
then we make another
low like that this is what the one
minute the five minute is doing as you
see the one
hour as you see the one
hour just launching back like Godzilla
before
you and you would just be praying that
you didn't buy right
here to go
up because now you're going down and
your position is is going down in value
and a lot of people because they got in
here they hold the
position
hoping that it's going to
get
back
here
again they hold
that here hoping that it comes back here
again as it's going
down and it's decreasing and becoming
worthless with every push
down oh you know every push
down it's coming worthless and worthless
and worthless and worthless and then
they close in a
loss because they don't understand that
now that the market is going
down if you are
trading you should be
short you should be
short
until the market gets back
to what the hourly
place that it's
looking to
continue
up like
that just just make that like that
continue
up so the higher time
frame
this the green maybe I should make it
yellow because it might look a little
better yellow is the hourly
Trend and the hourly trend has been
going up for hours sometime days
sometime weeks is going up depending on
what time frame you're looking
at so if you're trading from the hourly
you have to wait until maybe Tuesday to
get in a position that might bring you
to your profit on Thursday Friday
maybe but if you're trading on the one
minute the 15
minute you may be getting in at a
position you know at maybe like I don't
know 10
10:30 and you may hold that position
until 12 o'l and be like you know what
I'm
out so as the hourly Trend was going
up you took a little bit
of you took a position and got out of
the
move in profit
along this 1 hour hourly Trend
up and you were Guided by where you you
saw the hourly move turning
around so when the market is going up
it's because there's a
demand for for that particular thing
that stop that that you know that market
as a whole there's a demand for
it so on the charts you can see where
the demand is
at you can see where the demand is
located and often times the demand is
located at a particular point
that the market
reversed and the same way we
have the demand that sends price
higher sorry
let we have the demand
that we have the demand that sends price
higher down here
right we have a Supply
above right
here that's
designed and it's it's it's not there
it's actually back
here we have a supply
area that's
above right
here some previous area as price was
going down
that price sorry actually I should I
should actually just stick
with and mitigate it for
now so right here you have a supply area
above down
here somewhere below you have a
demand
area that demand
area that demand From
Below
that demand area
below is where price
originally came
from
so two weeks
ago the market was down here at these
levels and the market began to go up and
it kept pushing
up and when price came back let me
actually just
when price came back to the area that it
was two weeks
ago there was still this area that it
was at two weeks
ago there was still people willing to
buy at this price there was a ton of
people waiting because
what they missed this whole move right
here going up I'm highlighted
red they missed that whole move right
here going up this whole move going
up and price
came back to the
area where it
sent that whole move up but on the way
back down on the way back down it's
downtrending right
it's down trending High sorry low high
low
high low
high so as it's going
down as it's going
down you can get into a
position a short
position to say based
on based on what I've
analyzed or based on where we
previously pulled back from because
remember we said that there there are
pullbacks right and then continuations
the market continues going up after it
pulls back it continues going up
after it pulls back it's in a healthy
Market or it continues going
down right here let me um highlight this
a different
color it continues going
down it continues going down
so what you see here what you see here
this this
yellow movement down this yellow line
This is the movement down so if you know
where the market is going to begin to go
down if you know where the market is
going to begin to go down you can enter
a short position to make money while
it's going
down and every area where you believe
it's retracing up and tapping into to
continue down you can add another
position going
down going down so now you're making two
times the
money that you would have been
making if you took two positions up here
you began to make two times when this
position was opened and you continue
down that's given that the market will
continue
down how do we know the market is not
going to continue
down well the area that it came from is
the
deciding
factor so this whole pushup right here
came from
here this is where the market came back
to right
here and it pushed up again from here so
here is
where you want to be buying to go
up and
here is where you want to take your
profit or you want to begin
shorting to go
down but you will only know those areas
to Short from and hold as the market
begins its down cycle you see this one
minute red um the the the red
lines that's the market going down and
that's multiple positions on the one
minute to be able to find an entry and
go
down the problem
is Within These multiple entries to go
up and
down Within These multiple entries to go
down you
have sorry you
have this low this high this low this
high this low this High you have six
opportunities to find an
area that you can get in to go
short or find an
area that you can get
in to go
long and it doesn't mean that on the one
minute you're getting or the five minute
you're getting in in a
position right
here that doesn't mean you're getting in
a
position sorry let
me to
hold let's say you got in there that
doesn't mean that you're getting in a
position to hold to continue all the way
up here you wanted to go all all the way
up
here because that's not the that's not
the way the market moves there's only
one
place there's only one actually
this most people are trying to buy here
right
here in this green
area and they're buying to go up but
this area is not the area
designed to send the
market very high like push the market
High you can't expect to hold and hold
so much
profit all the way until we get all the
way up
here
because the market is
trending down
so if you chose to take this position to
buy just know that it's
going to a position to sell or to
short so you're
buying you're
buying to go to the Aira
that you're
looking to Short from in a downtrend if
you want to get involved here then you
can but you have to know you're getting
involved here on the one
minute to go up
here and because the market is going
down you're going to get more from
finding a
position
to go
down then you
will for finding a position to go up
because the overall Market is currently
going down but that doesn't mean that
there's not quick opportunities that you
can go up with because as the market as
the as there a series of highs and lows
highs and
lows you can
time where to buy those lows
from and where to sell or
short those highs
from where to buy or
long a low in a falling Market where to
buy or long a low as a market is going
down because the markets go up and they
go down every single day you can get
involved in a trade going up or a trade
going down to make money but you need to
know where you're going to get involved
in that trade going up and for how long
and where you're going to get involved
in that trade going
down for how long
too because just because it's been going
down for most of the day doesn't mean
that somewhere during the
day it can
have a huge pushup and start to
now Trend
up and as it's trending
up all you're looking for as it's
trending up guys pay attention to this
and and nothing else when it comes to to
to structure all you're looking
for is for areas in which you can get
in for a
short or get in for a long get in for a
buy or get in for a
sell and depending on the time frame
that you're
on depending on the time frame that
you're
on you have multiple
opportunities to
buy and you have multiple opportunities
to sell so the higher the time frame you
are
on the less
opportunities there are to find a
position to buy
in or to find a position to sell in or
to find a position to short in or to
find a position to long in or find a
position to enter in or find the
position to exit in whatever it is that
your mind makes up as to why you're
getting in where you're getting out it's
either to buy or to sell too short or
too long to get in an as an entry and to
take
profit to take profit
right I hope this is making sense for
somebody so we remember where all of
these these these
Longs where all of these Longs and these
shorts are they're highs and lows and
there areas where you could get in for a
short get in to sell or get get in to
buy and go up that's all I want you to
think about I don't want you to think
about anything else no power bot power
bottom Hammer bar nothing nothing just
that movement alone this is what we're
teaching the structure of the
market so the structure of the
market moves This Way series of highs
and lows going down on a lower time
frame on a higher time frame it can just
look like it's just going
down so on a higher time frame there's
that opportunity as it's going
down there's that opportunity to go down
for a longer period of time and stop
then turn around and go up for a longer
period of time but within the smaller
time frames it's going up then it's
going down then it's going up then it's
going down then it's going up up then
it's going down then it's going up then
it's going down then it's going down
then it's going up then it's going down
and that's all of this that I just
explained right
here so if you draw it on your
chart when we're going
up in a higher time frame
Trend there will be
multiple
highs and
lows highs and
lows highs and lows if you're looking at
the lower time
frame if you're looking at the higher
time
frame all you'll
see is price going
up and then price going
down
and it will
take this move
up it could be a couple of hours that
it's doing
that and now as it's going
down it's going down for a couple of
hours
too it's just within those hours that
it's going up there's multiple people
buying and selling buying and selling
buying and selling
but there's more
buying going
on than there is selling or taking
profit and as it's going
down there's more buying and selling
buying and selling buying and selling
buying and selling there's more of that
but what there's more
sales there's more people selling or
shorting the position
then there are people
longing so the people who are longing
have limited opportunities to buy get in
and get out buy get in and get out buy
get in and get out buy get in and get
out they have multiple opportunities but
they are
limited why are they
limited they're limited because
according to the parent time frame
according to the parent
structure according to the structure
that has the authority
more than the lower time frame structure
according to the higher time frame
structure we are going
up so More Money Follows that until what
until
what until we hit what's called our
supply so when the market started to go
up I told you that it was going up from
a place of
demand I told you where the demand was
the demand is
located at the
beginning of this whole trend
that we moved up with it's at the
beginning the beginning of it the
beginning of it listen to that I'm going
to get into the other stuff with with
supply and demand because there's
multiple demands and multiple supplies
when you are on different time
frames in the current market you might
see one Supply area above and one demand
area
below
on a higher time
frame but on a lower time frame you see
a bunch of Supply areas above and a
bunch of demand areas
below what are those supply and demand
areas on the lower time
frame what are
they those supply and demand
areas are
the
lows and the
highs
but when we're going
up when we're going
up the
supply is a
previous
High
Supply is a previous high in the
market you see up here previous high in
the
market this red this let me let me
actually just change this color right
here so it's not
confusing this is a previous high in the
market that the price or or the the
candlesticks that are going
up they will tap into it'll
touch and then what it's going to begin
going
down it's going to begin going
down
after it
touches that
area
it begins to go
down so when it touches that
area in the current Trend going
up me just make this another
color in the current Trend going up to
take us
there this current Trend that's heading
up to take us
there you'll see the the let me actually
just draw it better um I could actually
just use arrows I don't know why I don't
do this
in the current Trend that's heading
up we're
going to a supply a
previous
area or a
previous High
Point in that former Trend that price
was was coming down
in we will go back to those
highs and at those highs there are
different things that take
place you'll have
price go
down after touching
there and it will go down
into some area below which is the demand
the previous
demand there's there's a series of
remember what I said there's a series of
of highs and lows in here on this hourly
Trend the yellow the yellow line on this
hourly Trend there's a series of highs
and lows in
here and with a series of highs and lows
in here there are lows on the lower time
frame
little pullbacks on the lower time frame
little retracements on the lower time
frame that price will
touch and continue up again if it's
going to continue
up so you have the supply which is a
previous
high that price goes to a old high that
it goes to and it reacts from and it
begins to go down that old
high is the area that you want to begin
to
look to
sell the market to short to
short that's what you want to look at
that old high that's up there you want
to look at that
and when the market gets there and it
touches and pulls
away when it touches there and it pulls
away you can get into a short position
make money and that short position
oftentimes is heading to a
demand so he can tap there and people
who are
buying people who are
buying
they will buy from the
demand and price will
continue now it doesn't always continue
higher than the area that it began
falling from the area that it tapped
into the
supply the supply when price tapped into
a supply it made a high on that supply
and then it lowered price so that's a
previous High that's there that's a a
previous
high now some people might
say but you said the previous high is a
supply yes I did the previous high is a
supply absolutely
correct but in a trend moving
up price can tap into the previous
Supply and give you a little movement
away from
it but then it can
continue so you got into a sell position
here you got into a sell position here
to try and sell the market down or short
the market and it went down just a
little
bit was a little
profit but then it came back
to
the area that you were willing to close
if you started losing too
much which is called your stop
loss or where your stop loss should
be so you're looking
to get in right here and sell the market
down and you're willing to get out here
if you were wrong about the
position if you were wrong about the
position so this
Supply helps you to
determine it helps you to
determine if your trade goes in the
opposite direction and you are losing
money the end of this Supply the top of
this old
high it's where you're getting out it's
where you're stop losses it's where you
say I was wrong you guys hear me I was
wrong I was
wrong about price going down and this is
where I'm willing to maintain my
stance on
price going down until I
reverse my bias until I shift it until I
change it I was wrong about that area
now just because you changed your bias
and
price put you in draw down and you lost
your
money that doesn't mean that you
automatically jump into another trade
and try to go up with
it that doesn't mean
that because if you jump into a trade
and you try to go up with
it and price was
only going a little bit up above the
previous High into the supply again
remember the supply that was back here
the scent price
down and there was a supply that was
created here but this is not the supply
you're looking to sell from this is a
supply that will give you a reaction yes
but it's not something you're looking to
sell and hold until you go all the way
down
here
unless something happens here in this
particular
area sorry in this particular
area to let you know that price is going
down now that's a type of pattern or
movement that the candlesticks will show
you likewise when you get here into the
demand there's a pattern that the
candlesticks form most
times that will let you know that we're
turning around from
here and we're going back up where
where up to where we came from
or
or sorry this is my
this won't let me be great come on move
out of here
or we're going where we to where we came
from or we're going beyond that but that
decision doesn't happen here in the
middle of the market that happens at the
low which is at a former
low or that happens
at the
high which is at a
former High a
former High a former
Supply or a
former
demand so the best places for you to get
involved in a trade when you're going to
buy or when you're going to sell it is
say it with me
only at an
area of
Supply an area of
Supply or an area
of
demand
nowhere else I don't care
if you saw this going up oh my gosh it's
going it's going it's going it's if
that's
happening on the time frame that you
choose to place a trade
on you miss that move that's not for you
to get
in you are trying to get
in and when you missed this move and it
was
leaving that's not where you're trying
to get in you are trying to get
in
sorry this dot is going to bother
me you trying to get
in at whatever
Supply that price Taps
into or whatever
demand
that price Taps
into where it came from where it came
from this
move this move
up came from
somewhere where did it come
from it came from this area down
below
and more importantly write this
down write this down because this is
where it changes this is for people who
do not understand charting at all this
is where it changes write this
down it came from here yes this is where
the market pivoted and turned and went
up right we see that we clearly see that
if you guys are think if you guys think
I'm yelling at you I'm not yelling at
you it's my passion so leave me
alone
so let me um actually bring this down so
it's not in the way
of the U meeting
controls there we
go yeah I hope this doesn't no this is
probably going to bother somebody
um oh I can just do
this right yeah I just wanted to get to
this button back
here
so in this whole move up in this whole
move that's going up this this white
this white line right
here this white line right here this
whole move that's going
up you're not looking to get in there
you're not looking to to buy
there you're looking to buy when the
market comes back to where it came
from
or you're looking to sell the
market from where it previously came
from some area
where it's going to on the higher time
frame but often times that area that
you're looking to sell from if you want
more in your sell if you want more money
when you're selling when you're shorting
if you want more value when you're
selling when you're
shorting you would be
shorting from some out hourly area
that's back
here the hourly area back here where
price came
from from the hourly this is where price
came
from if you want to hold on to a long
move just like if you want to hold on to
a long
move and price is coming from a
particular area you want to hold on to a
long Buy if it's from a demand that's on
a higher time frame and you want to hold
on to a long
sell or long
short if price is being
rejected right
here from a higher time
frame area that's where you're looking
to sell and hold this is where you're
looking the demand is where you're
looking to to buy and
hold
right sell and
hold Buy and
Hold
right so the supply is always above a
former High a previous High and the
demand is always below a previous
low a former
low and you're only looking to buy and
sell from those areas but somebody
somebody would ask the
question somebody ask the
question what if we
have I'm G to make
this what if we
have
what if we have a bunch of
lows what if we have a let me just make
this
um bring to the front what if we have a
bunch of former lows let me let me bring
this to the front too
so I wish they had a button you could
press to
just bring certain things
to
front with just a button not
even all
right so somebody would ask or somebody
would
say that on the one
minute there's a bunch of lows
do this
again on the one minute or on the five
minute or whatever it is there's a bunch
of
lows so when
prices when
sorry when price on
the when price on the one
hour is now heading down from the supply
that it tapped into
above and price is now heading down on
the one minute and on the five minute on
the 15 minute you see all of these down
moves all of these down moves make this
white you see all of these down moves
down down
down down down you see all of these
previous down
moves as
price is heading down like this as price
is heading down you see all of these
down moves all of these demands these
are little demand zones many demand
zones you see all of these demand here
demand here demand here demand here
demand here those are all of those areas
are demand zones on the lower time
frame all of them are demand
zones every single low here is a demand
Zone
on a lower time frame so as price is
going
down as price is going down this is why
you have price going down in a
series sorry let me just delete this
real
quick oh no actually I didn't have to
delete that I just got to make the line
bigger you can tell this was impr promp
2 I'm not even ready for it
so on
these on these highs and lows that the
market is making you you see these this
red line that's going down where I said
you could both you could buy from the
the the low to go up or you could sell
from the high to go down in a downtrend
right in a downtrend in a downtrend get
that in your head you're buying temporar
in a downtrend in specific areas that
you can get a little bit of something
and get out if you're scalping if you
are if you're scalping and you're
like what if this what if price is
coming down and it just goes straight
through
this can price do that yes the answer is
yes
yes it can
yes these these lows on the one
minute even though there's times where
you could buy from it are there times
where price can go St through it
yes price
can
why because the overall trend that price
is currently in from the higher time
frame is
short and it is short to get down to a
particular area on the
hourly before it begins to
go
long
again before it begins to go long again
so you're having these series of highs
and lows that are coming
down but it's only coming to a
particular area on the higher time frame
to then
reverse so on the lower time frame if
you're somebody who's who's trading and
you want a bunch of opportunities to be
able to get in and out of Trades I'm in
for a little bit out for a little bit in
for you know like like well not in for a
little bit out for a little bit but in
for a little
bit in for a little bit take my profit
and I'm out in for a little bit take my
profit I'm out in for a little bit take
my profit I'm out on the one minute on
the five minute on the 15 minute
throughout the entire trading day while
the market is open it's going to be
making highs and lows and highs and lows
and highs and lows and highs and lows
whether it's going up or whether it's
going down it's going to be making highs
and lows and highs and lows and highs
and
lows so you're not
chasing price going up and you're not
chasing price going down you're not
saying oh I see
this this is where it tapped into right
here this is where it tapped you're not
saying it tapped the the former low here
it ran below this this low it ran below
that and came all the way to this former
low right here maybe I should just bring
it
here let's say it just ran
below that looks so ugly but I can't fix
it well that's the best that I could do
so it ran through this low right here it
ran through this demand Zone remember
the demand Zone the demand zones on the
one minute and on the five
minute are not as strong as the demand
zones that are on the higher time frame
that are on the one hour that are on the
15 hour the 15 hour 15
minute that are on that it's it's it's
it's it's
weaker it it won't won't hold here price
won't tap
here and go to the heavens
above because on the hourly the area
that the hourly is looking to get
to is not
here but it's here because there's some
move down
here that is trying to come and tap into
and then
continue up
above so on the higher time frame if
you're trading minute by minute you have
to be aware of where you are in the
market are you at that hourly area where
price is looking to reverse
from are you there if you are then it's
best for you to understand that though
you are looking for Longs here
you have to
see a particular pattern happen with the
candlesticks I'm going to teach that in
a few a particular pattern that happens
with the
candlesticks you have to see that
happen before you begin looking for
buys before you begin looking for buys
there's a particular pattern with the
candlesticks that you want to
see so when price gets to that one hour
area there's a particular pattern within
here within
here that you want to see happen before
you begin to
look to get into buys that you believe
this is this is the
point that you
believe not that you believe sorry that
the area that you're trading
from the area that you're trading
from is
set to to begin to turn price around and
take it higher on the higher time
frame now when price gets here you're
looking to buy a move and this is the
move that you could look to start buying
to hold for a longer period of
time to hold for a longer period of
time down here this is the move that
you're looking for now some people might
ask if you're on the one
minute how do you know whether this is
going to hold whether this is going to
be the move that it goes from or whether
this is going to be the move that it
comes from that's where your
multi-timeframe analysis comes from so
we found what the trend was on the one
hour and the one hour Trend we saw that
it was reversing because it tapped into
a demand
zone so it was
reversing and as it was reversing from
this hourly area on the lower time
frames we began to see a series of highs
and lows that price continues to go up
to the area on the higher time frame
that it's looking to reverse
from it's looking to reverse from that
area on the higher time frame and go
back to another
area on the lower time frame I mean
sorry on the higher time another area on
the higher time frame that it's also
going to reverse from again and continue
up so your job as a Trader and as
reading these
charts is to look for those
areas that price is going to continue to
go up
from or price is going to continue to go
down from
and depending on what time frame you are
trading
on you can hold that move for a couple
of minutes or a couple of
points or you could hold that move for a
lot of
points it depends on what time frame
you're trading on so on the hourly in
that hourly area when price goes to tap
that and we look for price to turn
around from that area you can hold that
area for a lot of points coming from
there to go back
to the supply you could hold that trade
from the demand for a lot of points from
the
hourly if it Taps into an hourly demand
Zone and reverses to
continue and on the lower time frame
when it gets to that hourly place on the
lower time frame there's a Candlestick
pattern or a Candlestick movement that
you want to see that should confirm to
you it should confirm to
you that now you're going to begin to
look for buys going up so if I'm going
to be on the lower time frame there's
going to be multiple opportunities for
those buys to get back to that
hourly Supply area when I'm getting in
on this hourly demand there's going to
be multiple
opportunities as it's going up on the
lower time frame to get me
to that
supply that hourly Supply from what the
hourly
demand the hourly
Supply and let me let me actually just
um make an hourly
demand
[Music]
so this is the hourly
demand this area here there's there's an
hourly demand that's
here and some people might be
asking well how do we know where the
hourly demand
is and and other people may
ask if you
said that it's the beginning of the
move that price is coming back
to somebody else might ask if you said
it's the beginning of the move that
price is coming back
to why is it that
Within the
middle price tapped there in the
middle and then continued to go
higher you might ask
that that's the way that the market
moves that's the way that the market
moves the
cheeseburger in
the 60s 50s whenever it
was was 25
cents right here 25
cents it went all the way up to let
let's say I don't know
40 50 no no no maybe maybe something
something incremental um it went all the
way up to 60
cents because Bill Gates was buying up
all the cows and and then he just raised
the prices you know whatever it is you
want to
believe because I'm sure whatever it is
that that man buys in large drobes he
has to report on his financial
thing so if you want to know who's
buying up what just know that those
those people people with a lot of
money they have to
report their um earnings and their
financial
moves
so look into that before you believe
what anybody says um
but so we have the we have we have price
coming back down went from 65 cents
above up here to back to 25
cents and then
the supply chain issue happened oh my
gosh raised it back
up raised it back up to 50
cents 50
cents it brought it back to 50
cents and
then brought price back down not to 25
cents not to 25
cents it brought price
down
to let's say 39
cents but it
was 25 cents and everybody was we loved
it oh my gosh it R the the health that
it brought us the strength of Vore said
no one ever the ch cheeseburger
definitely was in demand wow like hot
cakes is going so the price went
up but when the price pulled back
down the people who
missed this opportunity
here have an
opportunity to get in again
before it begins to head
up before it begins to head up if
if if it's something that's going to be
a part of our future if it's something
that's going to have value within the
future and that value is not
determined by if they say that they're
going to create a robot that's going to
cook every everything you ever want and
you never have to go food shopping
again because the robot is just going to
be able to generate all of it out of
thin air and and when it comes time in
case of
emergencies it can deliver your baby too
it can deliver your baby
too but it it doesn't stop there it
doesn't stop
there and all of these things are being
said
said and the price is going higher
geez goodness on I remember when it was
25 cents and and when it was 25 sense
then and and and China got involved
China to got involved
and and then we
we they did something thank God the the
government did something for
it but then those communist bastes they
just got involved
again and and none of those prices are
related to anything that that government
is doing so I don't know why we even
talking about that it goes up
again it goes up again if any if
anybody's new to this Channel and this
is the first video first video you're
watching
welcome it goes up
again it goes back to the former area
that it was
in it was it was highly valued
and goes to that area and what prices
begin to fall
again because at this
area there's more
Supply there more more Supply
here then there is the
current
demand that's going up the demand for
it it's started to
weaken the demand for
it
every time we were going up on the
hourly the demand for it would
get
stronger and stronger and stronger and
every time price pull back just a little
bit just a small just let me let me
actually just save this as a template
and then make the rest of
them
yeah the demand for
it every time it pulled
back didn't I just say
that no I didn't I did I say
this trying to Price look at trading be
oh now now it want to go there okay so
look here we
go
well so we just still G give me issues H
okay I apologize guys with my technical
difficulties all
right yes here we go so as as we
continue I apologize for that
um
as we
continue the demand for it people are
still buying you see how we're we're
going up and coming down going up coming
down going up coming you know you coming
back down going back up people are still
buying as these prices head
down and and right here
the prices are are still going
up still going
up like
this sorry
actually
what is
oh so the the prices are still going up
here like this you see it's still going
up the green boxes this is the
demand the demand is still sending price
higher people are still involved people
are still buying that's why it keeps
going up it keeps going up sometimes it
comes back and touches the previous area
right here and sometimes it doesn't
right here sometimes it doesn't even
come back and touch the demand down here
because it's so strong so much buying is
going on pushing price
higher I started with this saying that
what happens if we continue to
push and the market doesn't pull back
it's an unstable
Market the reason why we pull back is
because we are creating a structure in
the market and that structure is
creating stability
for the market now the market is not
perfect So within the market a lot of
the times you have price push push push
push push and and don't pull back guess
what that just means that it's primed
for a huge pullback
into a previous demand but what has to
happen first what has to happen
first what if the supply was here
because there are certain days where
news takes
place and it pushes the market
up what if we come above this Supply
right here
we come up above this Supply right
here like whatever it is here we come up
above it we break through it we break
through that
supply and then you see a start to pull
back you see a start to pull back into
the
demand and the next Supply is all the
way up
here can the market go
here Will the Market go
here there's a possibility that it
can yes there's a possibility that price
can just stop here and start to go all
the way down
here if the market is going all the way
down here and now it's going below the
the previous area it came
from that's telling you on a higher time
frame that now the market is in a higher
time
frame bearish
Trend but
currently this higher time
frame is a bullish
one healthy pullback continuation above
how do we know when the market is in the
higher time frame is in a
downtrend when the higher time frame is
in a
downtrend that higher time frame the
structure the candlesticks that are
going down will end up going below you
see this area right
here this area let me
um Circle it what um see what color
something
bright yeah I guess so
here this is where the market went down
on the hourly and it pivoted up
right so if the market comes back to
this area often times it'll come back to
this area give a healthy
pullback and
then then you'll see it continue
above then you'll see it continue above
like that give it healthy
pullback and
continue that's if it's going to
continue its
uptrend but if the market is breaking
down not a lot of people are buying
whatever whatever it is what whatever it
is that's happening when the market runs
its former low the former low that it
put in when it put in the high the
former low the former demand when the
market ruins or takes out or runs or
goes below the former area that it came
from that's the
first
sign that the market is reversing
and it's going to start to go
down it's going to start to go in a
downtrend and
now you might be able to
find
areas where you could expect
price to come and tap back
into and then find a long longer move
down from the hourly time frame but when
does that
happen that happens after the low that
it came
from that happens after it is
violated after we run below
it it pulls back up into the area and
then provides us with a short going
down so this yellow line is the hourly
the white line could be your one minute
five minute 15 minute whatever it is
it's lower than the higher Trend that
you're
following and on that lower time frame
you have multiple opportunities to buy
buy buy buy as well as you have multiple
[Music]
opportunities to sell sell sell sell
multiple opportunities to do it but what
they have to be in
areas that you could expect price to
reverse from and
continue you could expect price to
reverse
from and
continue these areas are areas of
supply and areas of
demand areas of
demand
so just
because a demand is created down here on
the
hourly doesn't mean that price is going
to it has to come down here
no it does not have to come down here
price can go here price can stop right
here and continue higher like
that because of well well that's usually
after a high is put in and the this is
rant we took the high we ran above the
former High
so we're not looking for for any sells
or any rejections we came above the
former
high and if you're trending up and you
tapped into a demand Zone
below we're expecting the demand Zone
below the last area
below the price came from we're
expecting
that from here to put in a new
high
above where the previous
High came
from or or where sorry where where the
low where the low came
from so this low here came from this
high
here so as we begin to make our way back
up we're looking for price to come up to
this high that we just came from
why because
that's supply and demand if there's more
demand we take it to the supply and take
price as high as we can and when there's
no demand
there and there's more Supply present
the
value of the current thing that you're
trading at that supply and there's no
demand left there's no strong Demand
anymore at that
[Music]
Supply you will see price start to break
down start to shift lower to go back to
an area of
demand a low a former low or a former
area that price came out
of to tap into and if there's enough
demand
there guess what that demand
does if there's enough demand
there that
demand sorry let me move this that
demand
puts in a new
high if there's enough demand here and
you still have people waiting to get
back to
here but there was enough demand
here and somebody might be like how do
you know that there's enough demand
there because when you get
there on the lower time frame
you
have a
series of highs and
lows coming down sorry this is so ugly
let me draw something
things you have a series
of
highs and
lows I don't know I don't know what's
going on with my drawing skills I don't
know is this is is the angle of this
like look at me like what is happening
it's not me it's you trading me I mean
it's me because I drew it but
look we have a series of lows highs lows
highs lows don't worry I'm G fix it
highs lows highs
lows we have a series of that uh we we
have a series of
that
coming
down series of lows and Highs coming
down
right
down but then so let me make this
red have a series of lows and Highs
coming down and what
happens me just change the color of
this what
happens when we get to that oneh hour
demand Zone remember we said this is
this is the
demand let's say this is the demand the
green box
when we get to that one hour demand
Zone that's down
here I apologize guys my OCD is the
reason why I'm so accurate so you have
to accept
it so
we get here to the demand
Zone and we're expecting price to go
higher
right what are we looking to
happen in this demand
Zone if we're expecting price to go
higher we're looking
for price to go above an old high
because as we're going down we're making
low high low high low high
low and then we put in a high right here
price moves really fast put in a
high that
violates the former
High remember what we said if we know we
we were going up in this
market and if we wanted to know whether
we were going to go down we would have
to violate an old low right so on the
lower time frames when you're
reversing from a higher time frame
demand you have the Run of a former High
that's
there when that former high is
ran price retraces and what you guessed
it
correct
continues in its uptrend maybe I need to
do this on an angle or something I'm
like what this is so
ugly I don't know I'm better at fixing
it than I am at creating
it so now you
see now you
see a a demand just like this now you
see a
demand just like that
right and sorry not not demand now now
you see now you see a reversal now you
see a reversal and the trend is moving
up and you see demands are being
created you seeing that demands are
being created again
supplies are being created
again but these supplies that are being
created are tap are tapping into
former supplies to the
left taab into former supplies to the
left former highs former areas of
Supply cuz the truth is you guys keep
hearing me say supplies at the highs and
lows but the supplies at the highs and
lows are the ones that I'm telling you
guys to choose because that's where the
the larger movement comes from within
the smaller
Trends but there are times there are
times where price will
not go back
to that demand
below it will just just go
right
here and start to continue higher just
like
this it'll go right there and start to
continue higher so it'll go to the top
of the old high right here the old high
it'll go to the top of the old
high and continue up like
that just just like
that so you guys hear me saying that at
the bottom of the one minute
Trend there are demands
there but there are multiple
demands
within the one minute
trend
because even on the one minute Trend
even on the five minute Trend even on
the 15minute
trend even on the 15minute
trend there's also a series of highs and
lows in here
too there's also a series of highs and
lows in there too and that series of
highs and
lows that is provided by the
candlesticks that you
see the candlesticks that you see are
forming those
small highs and
lows inside of
it so just like on the 15
minute
where you could exp expect little areas
of supply for the market to tap
into and give you a rejection back
down before continuing
higher the same way that that you have
that on the 15 minute is the same way
that you have smaller ones in there on
the one
minute so now the smaller
ones these small smaller ones on the one
minute the smaller down moves the Down
Candles the down areas before price
continues
higher
these can give you
buys and cells
too these can give you buys and cells
too based
on the smaller areas of demand but just
know that those smaller areas of
demand and the smaller areas of Supply
above on the one minute they don't hold
as much as the higher time frame ones
do but you can find entries here you
just have to understand that those
entries are only for a couple of points
or a quick move so it's a larger
position but a quicker move you're in
and out in and out that's scalping
that's what I teach that's what I do on
the the the on YouTube Every Day
live I show you areas that you're able
to get in and get out of the market
using this entire way that I just
explained to you guys that the market is
structured using multiple Supply areas
multiple demand areas and I'm pointing
that
out with
what with just these
squares with just these squares
that's what I'm pointing that out with
these
squares and then you see the movement
happen you see the flip and now you know
you're looking to get involved in buys
but the buys you're only looking to get
involved in buys when the market
flips at previous
demands
not in the middle not after price tapped
it and it's running up to to take out
the high not at that time you're looking
to get in here when the market pulls
back and you want your entry to take you
higher because often
times
if the market is not looking to go up
from here
here you will have your entry
here sorry let
me you will have your entry
here you will have your stop loss
here your stop loss is is how much
you're willing to lose B based on the
size of your account how much you're
willing to lose for anybody who doesn't
know how much you're willing to
lose
before you get out of the trade and stop
your loss from going further eating into
the rest of your account that you
currently
have so it's how much you're willing to
risk right here your entry is here in
the middle of this
area your stop is behind the area that
you're trading from behind the Zone
behind the zone that you're trading from
it's behind the
zone and you're looking to
Target potentially the new high but as
price is going
up as price is going up remember what I
said there's a
series of highs and lows in here that
takes you up so guess what guess what
with the series of highs and lows that
take you
up if price is not going to run this
High what it's going to look
like is you have these highs and lows
going up
right price stops right here at some
former Supply area that's there and what
does it do it violates one of the older
lows if it violates one of the older
lows on the one
minute you know the one minute cycle now
is getting ready to go into a
downtrend but for how
long most times it can just be going
back
to a previous area where it
started and it's going to continue
higher how do you know it's going to
continue higher because it's going to
run one of its older highs TAPS in and
continues like
that and this is how the market pivots
this is how the market
moves and this that I just mentioned the
way this Market chooses to
Pivot this that I just
mentioned is the Market's cycle of how
it goes
up when it
reverses when it
reverses now how it's going
down and when it reverses
to how it's going up and all I'm doing
on the one minute when I'm trading
during the during the the live sessions
is just tracing all of those areas that
price is bouncing off of to continue so
your entry is the bounce to
continue or the bounce to short the
bounce to go down or the bounce to go up
the bounce for the retracement or the
bounce for price to to continue going up
that's all it is and guess what guess
what how do we
know how do we
know where the areas are that price is
going to retrace from or start to go
down from before it continues
up often times it's right near the
former
highs so when it gets to its former
High you see it retrace
down and then when it gets to the former
area below or the the the demand one of
the demands that's within the smaller
Trend what does it
do it continues up so if you want to get
involved in the market you can get
involved in the market on a quick scalp
going down which is risky because it's
against the trend you saw the trend just
changed right here once we ran that
former
high so you can get involved with a
scalp going down that's quick but it has
to be at an area of
Supply when it's going up you can get
involved in any side of the market any
side of the
market that's a sell or a buy but you
not you must know where you are you must
know where you are what is the current
Trend Market structure that's what it is
what is market structure the highs and
lows that we're currently
seeing how do we know that the market is
still going
up was any lows violated here's a low
here's a low here's a low no lows are
violated yet so what are we
expecting we're expecting price to turn
back and retrace
and continue right and then what does
that create the next
low the next low that's there that's
what it creates the next low and when
price is ready to go down again what's
what are you looking for what's going to
happen what are you looking to
see you see a low violated right where
does that low tap into though
to go back up and then
short the low Taps into a previous
demand after
violating the old demand there's a
demand just below it at times that it
Taps into to go back up and now you're
looking for
shorts to go
down as the market is going back down
all you're looking
for all you're looking for is
opportunities Too Short
now
until
until you see one of your
highs
violated and now you're going long again
until what until what it's deja vu y'all
it's deja
vu until we see a low
violated and then now we're going down
again to where we could stop here there
could be some imbalance now on the
playlist I have a master's class
playlist I want you guys to watch it
after watching this video this will be
the first video on the master's class
playlist because everybody will have
access to this information thanks to
Armani by the way but this will be the
first
video the the the other videos in the
playlist teaches you more in depth about
these pois and which one or point of
Interest that's what it's called about
these zones about these demands about
these
supplies it teaches you which ones you
could use to make more profit from
versus which ones you should just not
use and wait and and let it get to the
other one it teaches you that in the
master class playlist but you first must
understand how the market
moves and this is the
structure in which the market moves and
these different lines denote the time
frames that you're seeing all of these
highs and lows in and all of these highs
and lows Within These time frames are
areas where you can get involved in the
right
direction in the
direction one of the biggest issues that
we
have is being on the wrong side of the
market
why because we don't
know where our former Highs
are and we don't
know where our former lows are
and a violation of it is what gives us
the
next
Trend in that direction what gives us
the higher time frame retracement y'all
know the higher time frame y y'all
talking about you know like you want to
take moves on a higher time frame the
lower time frame will tell you when when
the higher time frame is pulling back
how because we are
violating one of these
lows we tap back in and then we
short and now we're
beginning the downtrend and you have
multiple opportunities to find shorts
why here's a banger that a lot of people
don't know y'all ready y'all ready
here's a banger that a lot of people
don't know now some people do some
people do on in my group because I teach
it but here's a banger that a lot of
people don't
know the
market if you're counting the
pullbacks these little these little
pullbacks that the market keeps going
back and tapping into something if you
count the pullbacks often times when the
market is pulling
back you get four to six pullbacks and
oftentimes the seventh one
fails the seventh one oftentimes the
seventh one fails sometimes I see the
market sometimes I see the
market it it it's three of them and four
of them happen and and then it's done it
it reverses how do you know when the
reversal is happening we just taught
that when the violation happens so even
if you're counting the
these you're counting these along with
looking for these and when you're
counting these is letting you know guess
what's coming bad
boy guess what's about to show up y'all
been waiting y'all
ready and
usually the fourth to sixth one is
forming around what oh
goodness
goodness the 4 to6 is forming around
around the area that it's getting ready
to reject
from and begin
what
baby and begin the four to six combo
slice
again and they be running retail crazy
in the
market because retail is what what are
we doing
we trying to sell down
here sell down here and the market goes
up sell down here and the market goes up
sell down here and the market goes up
and then we try to buy up here and the
market goes down buy up here and the
market goes
down what are we
doing when according to Market structure
there's a there's a way in which the
market
moves and we're trading what we think
and what we
see sorry what we're trading what we
think and and and what we believe we
see
but
but it's not what's actually happening
in the market it's
not what's
actually happening in the market that's
what I want people to understand it's
not what is actually happening in the
market
so there's there's types of Candlestick
patterns that people are at times
waiting for to
happen the types of Candlestick patterns
that people are waiting to
happen they're waiting for it to
happen and while they're waiting for it
to
happen they don't know where they
are where are you are you in a Zone
if you're in a Zone then yes if you're
not in a Zone then no so if you see
price pushing like
this if you see price pushing like this
how dare you put in a long how how
Reckless are you to put in a
Longo when we understand that the
market pulls back and continues pulls
back and continues pulls back and
continues pulls back and continues pulls
back and continues we understand
that so our
profitability is in the
pullback our
life getting better is in the
pullback our hope is in the
pullback our dreams our Visions all the
things that we want is when life pulls
us
back when it pulls us down and we don't
understand
why we had a place of too much Supply we
had a place of too much going
on we had a place that was overvalued in
our
lives and the blessing was in the
undervalued
spot the undervalued
spot that's where it was that's where
the profitability
was so we waited for
that we waited for
that so I know that this is a lot to
digest um there's a lot to digest a lot
was taught here a lot but this is the
structure of the market so if you ever
want to know what Market structure
is and you want to get out of this
retail support and
resistance which retail support and
resistance is waiting for price to go
below the demand
waiting for price to go below the demand
violate the demand but they're trying to
chase or put in
sales once we get the run of the demand
once we go below the demand they're
trying to put in CES right here because
they say that we're in a range and the
range consist
of all of the orders that's happening
within here
and they tell you that you should look
for a
sell to go below here or a buy to go
above
here when
that's when the market
reverses when the market goes below here
reverses and comes back into the range
when the market goes above here reverses
and comes back into the
range so you're not looking for an entry
above or below below the last Supply
above or the last demand below you're
not looking to chase the run or the
break out of it or or you're not looking
to just jump in because it's heavy
selling pressure after the run of a low
no because after the run of a low what
do we get what do we just
explain what do we just explain here
after the run of a low we explained that
after the run of a low there is what a
pullback so why on Earth will we be
chasing a cell below a demand if after
it went below the demand it
[Music]
pulled so I know that that's a lot to
take in and that's what I'm going to
pause for today and tomorrow I'm going
to take take you guys to
church and help you guys to understand
Market structure and where to get in and
where to get out precisely exactly but
you first need to understand this you
first need to grasp this you first need
to know this you first need to know get
it out your head the market does not run
on support and
resistance I get that that's the thing
we've been taught for the longest of
whatever and no wrong it does not run on
support and resistance
and if you wanted to classify what
support and resistance was there are
zones that you can call support and
resistance zones that you can call
support and
resistance and you can take that as an
entry from the support or that as an
entry from the resistance not from these
areas that are above or below a
particular
range because that's how you get wrapped
up
quick and I'm going to teach
that tomorrow so I'm going to teach that
maybe in the in the evening should be
like more like 4 five no no no not four
five maybe like s o'clock Eastern
Standard Time because at least I can
give you guys some examples in a real
market right because that's what mentors
do that's what real teachers do in the
real Market they will teach you as it's
happening because they know what they
know what they know as the teacher as
the mentor so this is an
entirely spontaneous course that I just
went through that was amazing though I'm
glad I I um I got that explanation I'm
glad I got that in because wow that
that's going to help a lot of people
with structure and not chasing these
dumb areas where it's like oh my gosh we
just went above certain area let's get
in now and that's the way the market is
designed go above a certain area come
back into it go above a certain area
come back into it go up a certain area
come back into it so why you chasing the
area to go up if it's always coming back
in wouldn't you find it coming back in
or find it coming out of
it hey
yo so yeah yeah I'm in there in there
there's a lot of heat um in one day um
you know I know other people who who um
dang I didn't even record this I'm so
upset it's just on YouTube so now it's
gonna have to stay on YouTube um for a
lot of people who don't understand
structure who don't understand Market
structure you know like this this should
help but what I want you guys to
understand and this is why I'm coming
back to teach this tomorrow one because
I love talking and I love teaching but
two
because there are
times when the market comes below this
right
here and when it goes back
up it puts in another
high so I know we talked about the
demands being violated but there there
are times where when the demand is
violated it will put in another
high and it's how to avoid that so don't
think that just because you saw that and
you got that and it's like oh yeah
that's that's great is gonna no this is
the
bridge I've used other people as the
bridge in times and that was my fault
for bridging their garbage
work with this hot sauce that the Lord
Jesus Christ gave
me
that was a mistake and this
here is what real Market structure is
this is Market structure with supply and
demand on multi-time frames multiple
time frames I gave you no candlesticks I
showed you nothing at all other than
lines and with these lines this is
exactly how the market moves and when I
come back tomorrow I'm going to show you
guys
exactly how it works
together with the
candlesticks with
them and we're going to work through it
together because then this this series
of structure and supply and demand will
go into structure the right way
and then swing points and then all of
the other stuff the Candlestick
structure the the little tiny
candlesticks are how you can time the
very beginning of the move and take it
from the bottom to the top of where the
rest of the market will go I'm going to
to um explain that for you guys so um
you know I know I did plan to answer a
bunch of questions I didn't really get
around to it I do apologize you guys
know I love and I talk so much but I
hope this was heat for you guys I hope
this was a great explanation for you
guys um and tomorrow we're going to come
back for more tomorrow there's it is
going to be fire y'all want to be there
I don't know if I'm GNA have it on
YouTube now because tomorrow is
essentially still going over all the
stuff that I went over in the rest of
the playlist this is just a bridge to
what supply and demand is and what
support and resistance is and then I'm
going to give the rest of the video on
how to identify supply and demand this
is not what support and resistance is
sorry this this is what support and
resistance is not that's what I was
showing you guys but what what supply
and demand is and what Market structure
is this is what I just went over with no
candlesticks tomorrow I will do it with
candlesticks so you see how this all
aligns together and then where it's best
for you to get into a trade what time
frames it's best to look at how to
correlate one time frame a higher time
frame with a lower time frame so you're
able to get that move on the lower time
frame and risk a little less than you
have to to be able to get the larger
time frame move because if you're
risking from the large time frame then
you're also risking a lot more and what
I mean by that is that if you look here
let me show you guys
this and I'm doing this because I know
other people are going to come back and
watch this if you get into a buy right
here an an hourly buy look at where your
stop loss is look at where your risk
is you're
risking all of
this just to be just to hope that you
make this up above up here just to hope
that it it it comes all the way up here
to run the high you're risking all of
this but what if I told you you'd be
able to risk this
much youall see that little slivery red
this much
much in order to get the same
amount that's where multi-timeframe
analysis comes in and that's where
identifying those areas within
multi-time frame
analysis that's going to to to get you
that that that small stop loss that
small
risk I tell people all the time I want
to pay peanuts to eat cavar I don't want
to pay cavar money to eat cavar please I
could split that money 20 ways from
Sunday going to more more things that
matter I Cav on you got Cav off for you
off $25 off
you you learn to preserve Capital that
way that's what I want I don't want to
work hard who wants to work hard
what hardest worker in the room I was
that for years where did that get
me
[Music]
nowhere n so I'm gonna be back tomorrow
o'clock 7 P.M Eastern Standard Time
That's 7 PM Eastern Standard time so
that's um
1900 Eastern Standard Time
1900 Eastern Standard
time I'm going to do the second part of
this video and it's going to run right
into no not work hard until you get
smarter absolutely not get smarter so
you don't have to work hard sorry
somebody put that in the zoom thing get
smarter so you don't have to work hard
my dad always used to tell me when I was
younger son I want you to go to school
and get an education so you don't have
to work as hard as I do and little did
he
know he meant get an education but it
wasn't in school for
me and and I have a college degree it
me get education
yes but it's subjective to where that is
and the education for you to prosper in
the markets is
here on this channel and every live
stream you show up to in this
Discord 7 PM Eastern Standard time EST
EST your profitability is on these live
streams in the Discord that we currently
have join a Discord if you guys have not
done so already it's here the the link
is is is on one of these videos or maybe
on this video I'm not sure but join the
Discord be a part of what we do there's
people who come in and get offended
because I'm so like militant when it
comes to learning but this is direct you
don't have you don't have the
opportunity to mess up this is the one
minute time frame that I trade from and
we when we be find an hour moves right
4our
moves on the one
minute and so militant because that
discipline helped me to be as precise as
I am today and I'm precise every day
that I come in the market I dare you or
anybody that's new and that's listening
to the sound of my voice come on live
stream I dare
you and try to edit and alter whatever
analysis is I'm given I'm promised you
you will get chopped up why because my
analysis is always
correct when I'm
live all you guys hear me you heard that
that sounds pompous and arrogant right
that sounds like not smart Raja Concepts
right to say something like that
right that's what that sounds like but
nope I said that and I mean it if I
telling you there's a cow in your
backyard and you go back there and the
cow is not
there you better call the police because
somebody stole your
cow someone stole your cow and if you
live in an
apartment someone stole the cow out of
your backyard I promise you you better
call the
police
all right guys so I hope that that was
helpful um get out of here thanks
everybody for coming out um I hope you
guys learned as much as you know you
were able to I know this is Long window
was a very long teaching longer than I
expected but this is the beginning of it
and this paired with what we're coming
back for tomorrow will help you get that
that right footing in in the market
you're going to have days where you
still have down days you still have up
days because the market moves opposite
of our um impulse so if our impulse is
to buy often times the market is selling
at that time when our impulse is to buy
when our impulse is to sell often times
Market is the market is buying at that
time Market moves opposite of our
impulse opposite of our impulse opposite
of our impulse that's what I said right
opposite of our
impulse opposite of our impulse and and
and with this let let me actually just
um note this out these
pullbacks happen at
previous previous highs that were former
pullbacks so the pullbacks happen within
the
pullbacks pullbacks happen within the
former pullbacks the previous P the the
current pullbacks will happen in a
former pullback the current pullback
will happen in a former pullback but the
current pullback happens at the former
pullbacks previous
Trend so the bullish pull the the
pullback that's that's on a bullish
Trend will happen at the
area that it pulled back on a bearish
trend but y'all are GNA get that
tomorrow so I'll see you guys soon I
appreciate you guys and um I'll see you
guys soon as we always do in our live
streams you know turn this music up and
we're gonna dance ourselves right on
home and I'll see you guys soon all
right you guys enjoy you can spam up the
chat with hearts and everything whatever
it is you need to however it is you need
to get out whatever whatever you need to
say I'll I'll read whatever it is that
I'm reading within like the last couple
of minutes of listening to this and I'm
out of here but I'll see you guys soon
later guys
[Music]
enjoy
the
[Music]
got
no
l
[Music]
B
do