but how bad do you want this it's not
gonna come from me telling you get in
here get out here
how bad do you want this how bad do you
want to be able to wake up every day
y'all hear that every day
and take a quick 10 point trade and you
done for the day you could even be done
for the week
I told you all about my student low-key
right
y'all see the house that he bought right
you know what let me let me let me
actually
let me actually show y'all
let me show y'all Loki's house
so this could be some motivation for
y'all
and why I do not play
when it comes to let me let me bring the
volume down a little bit why do not play
when it comes to laziness and and not
taking yourself seriously
yo
here's Loki's house
let me click on it
to give you all an idea of of
you guys see this
this is Loki's house
that
he just bought not too long ago
here's the aerial view
of his house
y'all see this
anybody that comes to this man's house
connection going on all right I turned
the music off so that should be
that should help it y'all see this
this is the aerial shot
of his home
that means that anybody coming to his
home
they have to have some sort of business
there
in order to even walk by it
[Laughter]
don't even walk by it
y'all know where where
y'all know where Loki lived prior to
this
the hood
poor neighborhood with gang violence
drug infested
having to look over his shoulder
wherever it is that that he's going
and Loki wrote to me guys I want you
guys to know that that this is not
something that took
years to happen
this is not something that took years to
happen yes he lived in the ghetto this
is not something that took years to
happen
Loki wrote to me in March he was in my
group
he only had his his uh uh funded account
and guess how much money he had in his
bank account
zero dollars
V zero dollars
and he said this has to work for me
it's my last shot all I have is one
funded account when I was telling him to
get a trade copy and a trade copy of
course 150 he was like I don't have the
funds right now it's just this only
account
that I have
and I have nothing else in my bank
account that's what he said nothing else
in my bank account
so he said I'm depending on being able
to get a payout from this account it's
my last shot
that's what you said so this is my last
shot
so that man was banking this is what
some of the Twitter Traders they they
love to speak against this oh if you
trade him for money then you need to go
and fix your situation
then you then you need to go and and
deal with that do you need to go and get
a job Loki said he couldn't get a job
his record he had he he couldn't get a
job
no skills to really do anything to bring
in income and guess what still had a
family that he had to provide for
ain't that crazy still had a family that
he had to provide for
so what was needed
discipline
and the right information
and the right information so I told them
I said listen Loki
I said every time I look at your chart
you got stuff on there that I do not
teach you
good stuff on your chart
that I do not have in the course that
that I've taught
so get rid of those Bollinger Bands on
your chart
he came and asked me about some
indicators some Lux I'll go indicator
tell me what you think about this this
was still during that time where he was
struggling and didn't want to lose their
single account because he was counting
on the payout to come out of that
account
I said do not talk to me about no Lux
I'll go indicator you all you need is
what's in the playlist
I want to hear any of that don't no
indicator nothing you need to be able to
see this for yourself
so he came to me one last time this is
his last shot let me actually read let
me let me read the text message
we really checked the the message that
he sent to me
look at this this is this is March 12th
remember we're in June right now we're
at the end of June
we're the end of June let me let me let
me put his put his uh uh
put his house back up on the screen
so y'all here with somebody living in
that house right now
was saying just a few months back
because he wasn't living in this this
this location
put it back up on the screen for y'all
show y'all why I don't
play
when it comes to to taking yourself
seriously
when it comes to putting in the time
putting in the effort
this is house remember there's this
house right there
this is in March March 12th so this is
not even just a few months ago
he said actually look his his February
here's February
he wrote To Me February 17th and he said
hey thank you for everything
I keep making the same mistake of
getting in at the wrong time and ending
up in drawdown
now this doesn't happen every day but it
happens more on days like today I'm
spending all of Sunday studying the
videos
and really wanted your recommendation on
which videos or live streams you think
will help
so
I told him when it comes to risk
management
first of all here's what I actually
wrote let me know even show code here's
what I actually wrote I said hey brother
what's up so I've been digging through
some videos for the last hour or so
video five is the one that deals with
entries Trail your highs and lows hit it
in every single video is half of the
work already knocked out
I'm not giving him any new information
you don't need to know you know any
anything else trailing your highs and
lows is half of the work already knocked
out
I said an execution plan is what's
needed and I wrote in caps per trade
I said use the entry methods on video
five while back testing and forward
testing Don't Force the entries that you
want take the entries that you see
that's what I told them not the entries
that you want
take the entries that you see
I said that should be good to start with
sometimes it's just a reset
that we need this is what I said then
he said thank you brother there's just
so much material to go over
and I've watched them several times
but I guess my memory sucks
this is in in February
so I got on a live stream with them in
the group
and I talked to them
about this specific thing and he knows
that I was talking to him in particular
because he knows the last message he
sent to me I didn't respond back to that
message
I I got in actually I have I have a
recording of it
according to me I recorded it I said
your memory is not the problem
it's what it's competing for
so the more that you know
the stat line of your favorite team
what Joey B is doing and what he's
saying
what Trump is is doing
what are all these other people that you
Keeping Up with the Kardashians
Keeping Up with the Kardashians and and
not with what you need to pay attention
don't hear that
he said
his memory sucks no your memory doesn't
suck
your ability to follow instructions suck
that's what it is
I said
take 30 days and and this is this is
what this is the same thing that I told
them inside of the group after this
message I said take 30 days
to only consume this to only consume the
playlist take 30 days nothing else
forget about any award shows that's
going on forget about you know any games
that's being played he told me he was an
avid follower of sports games
and then he started to tell me that he
no longer knows what's really happening
in them he doesn't really follow them
sometimes when friends come over they
talk to him about it I started to see
the evolution of it
so I told him I said your memory is
competing
for all these different things that
you're taking in more
than this
more than than the actual learning
it's competing for that
yo you will have time to keep up with
celebrities later on if that's your
interest you have time to keep up with
real housewives of whatever it is for
the ladies that's him for the men who's
forced to watch it you will have time
to keep up with those things you have
time to go back to Netflix and and watch
Bridgeton and all that you will have
time later on you know how many shows
that's on the backlog for me that I that
I still haven't finished
you won't have time for those things
trust and believe you will have time for
it
right now is not the time
you will have time
for those things
you want to listen to what Joe Rogan has
to say about whatever it is you want to
watch the Eagles versus Mark Zuckerberg
fight you want to keep up with the
events leading up to the next
go ahead keep up with it
and be poor
or get rid of it and change your life
change your mind listen they say it
takes 21 days
21 days
to make something a habit
and if you could make it a habit you can
make it a lifestyle right
21 days so guess what that means there's
20 trading days
and then
one day goes into the next month
so when the market is open you're tape
reading when the market is closed you're
studying
when it opens back up your tape reading
when it closes you're studying
and you're doing that over and over and
over and over and over and over and over
and all I'm saying is one month for God
[Music]
you can't stop watching your favorite TV
show for one month in order to change
your life forever
one month
one
they asking for arm and a leg I'd like
to ask you to join my group
nobody asks you to pay anything but
attention
one month that's what I told them in the
group I said
one month just devote one month to this
you will begin to see some changes in a
week though
y'all heard Denise when she came on and
said you'll see changes in a week
but one month is what I'm asking you for
guess what I learned all of this that
I'm teaching I learned it in four months
it took me one month to start pulling
money out of the market but I learned
all of this in four
and I was able to take what I learned in
those four months
and chew it up
and give you it in a concise manner
that's that's what 20 20 hours 23 hours
of course work that's 23 hours in the
playlist
I don't even really know how much hours
it is I don't know 23 24 hours something
like that that just added a new video to
it so let's say 24 hours I was able to
take what I learned over four months and
deliver it in 24 hours of speaking
24 hours
and I said take that 24 hours of
coursework and let it be the only thing
you watch every single day
let it be the only thing that you watch
every day you'll get tired of my voice
you're going to be startled by me
yelling at my kids
I'm telling you I'm laughing but but
it's required
this is the sacrifice that's required
this is required
I said one month every day I get it it's
dry it's long oh my gosh it's so much to
write down then after I write it down I
have to go and look at the charts and
then try to interpret it
try to interpret it
after writing it all down and sometimes
when I try to interpret it guess what
I'm trying to interpret it
I may stumble I may think it's bad and
it's something else
I may be defeated on some days
but you gotta keep going
you gotta keep going
because soon enough it's gonna break you
gotta keep going so I wrote that I wrote
that to him
on the 18th then he wrote back to me the
following month on the 12th so this is
almost almost 30 days after I sent that
rebuke to the group almost 30 days
and he said good afternoon Dave I don't
understand what's happening with me I've
put in many hours of studying every day
first he told me he was setting aside
Sunday to watch to watch his videos okay
yeah I know where you at brother you
setting aside Sunday to watch it okay
yeah cause you just you just watching
for a couple of hours a week and then
and then you go and think that you're
Superman because you won one entry and
then the rest of it you start to fall
apart
because you think a couple of hours a
couple of hours in in one day out of out
of the two weeks
that you said you was going to set aside
you watch the video for a couple hours
you wouldn't want to trade you like oh
yeah the videos work
and then you started to fall apart after
that the consistency started to mess up
you might even feel good about having a
winning day and then the rest of the day
start to feel brutal
brutal oh my gosh I know how that feels
you did great on one day you conquered
it you said yo I could I could do this
for the rest of my life
I could do this for the rest of my life
goodness
I'ma be rich
that's what you said after that one
winning day
and the next day you came in and you
barely made it out alive
started thinking twice about it then the
following day you came in and you got
that bomb entry oh that was good and
guess what after that you started to
fall apart all the way through start to
give you gains right back
even if it was demo start to give you
games right back
and guess what the first day you watched
the video and you did that
and then the second day
you went back to a little more of it and
then you were like all right you know I
think I'm good now
third fourth fifth day guess what you
stopped doing watching them videos
guess what you stopped doing studying
guess what you stopped doing being
diligent and consistent with what you
were told to do which was watch it every
day which was set aside time all of it
all of your leisure time you think you
want to go and and watch a movie watch
the playlist
you think you want to go out and drink
with some friends watch the playlist
you feel like going out for to the park
to have fun watch the playlist
you feel like going out to the movies
watch the playlist you feel like going
to a restaurant watch the playlist
whatever it is you feel like you want to
do replace it we're watching the
playlist and Loki started to tell me
I'm not even going anywhere anymore I'm
not even doing anything some of my
friends they always calling me checking
in on me trying to figure out why I
don't hang out with them
and I I don't even you know I'll catch
up with them another time
I told them I said you in that bike
again
and y'all all around having fun but
nobody knows your situation behind
closed doors
nobody knows what's really happening
but but they'll buy you a beer yeah
but they but they get drunk with you
yeah yeah yeah they chop it up with you
yeah yeah
but when it comes to
the issues behind closed doors this
that's ripping apart your family
is ripping apart your marriage
it's causing Rifts between you and
whoever it is you take care of or those
that take care of you
they're not out there trying to get you
out of that so get rid of it no one's
saying get rid of them as friends but
they're not conducive to the journey
that you're on right now get rid of it
he used to tell me yeah I'm gonna be in
Brooklyn I'm going out with the biker
gang to to do this or not you know we
we gonna head out there and and we got
this rally we going to and I love to
meet up with you oh oh meet up with me
you think you think I'm hanging out with
with somebody who don't follow
instructions
you just gotta hang it out with losers
yeah
not ah pizza pie
I'll see you another day
cause clearly you are not taking your
time seriously you clearly not taking
your time seriously
you got enough energy in you to go out
and rev your engines illegally because
because bike biking is is that's illegal
in
ATVs and and dirt bikes and all that
riding up and down all around town in in
New York that's illegal out there but
you're going out to do that all right
because that's the desire of your heart
to to be around people and seek
validation and all that other stuff
that's a desire your heart
and I wasn't talking to him in
particular I was talking to the whole
group when he told me about this
I'ma throw shots but not directly at you
but I promise you you're gonna feel it
because I don't miss
I don't I don't miss
yeah no I don't I don't
y'all see that bad boy
now who who said who who who told y'all
[Music]
so
he said
I've put in many hours of studying every
day
I'm watching and taking notes
and I'm still struggling to be what
consistent
still struggling to be consistent
now some days I would see him
in the group
you know showing up to the live streams
but I did not see him posting any charts
laughing and talking with everybody but
not posting any charts
what did I tell them I said post charts
because it's the only way I'm gonna know
where you are and your level of learning
and what to direct you to go back to
what video to tell you to go and watch
so you need to post it's very important
don't come in and ask me what my account
size is don't come in asking me you know
where I'm planning to what I think the
market is doing today
where I'm planning to get in oh is this
buys right here don't even think about
it
because you're not taking yourself
seriously if you come along with that
so
he said for me this is this is March
12th
for me this has to work as I don't have
any more options to bring in income we
are on the verge of losing everything
and I don't know what to do
y'all hear that
let me read that again
let me read that again for for those in
the back I think they got time
for me this has to work
as I don't have any more options to
bring in income
we are on the verge of losing
everything
and you know you know what he you know
what he said to me
you know what he said to me
he said I don't know what to do
that statement there
had to be the most
asinine an erroneous statement
I could ever hear from somebody that I
was giving
every day of my life to
telling them what they needed to do
doesn't know what to do
he said I'm studying video one today and
this is probably the 15th time I've
watched it
I said what are you struggling with
he said it's still my entries I said
show me a chart
of a failed entry for you
so he went to show me the he sent me the
chart
he sent me to his the the chart of his
failed entries
he sent me a chart of his fail entries
and guess what was on there
guess what was on that chart
Bollinger Bands
support and resistance lines
and when he sent it to me
guess what I responded with y'all
guess what I said to him
guess what I said then
I said nothing
at all
nothing
to nothing not one word to him
oh you're about to lose everything
and even while you're on the verge of
losing everything
you still can't follow the things that
you tell how bad do you want this
how bad
do you want this
cause you telling me
you want this bad
but you showing me that you don't
because when your friends told you let's
go meet in Brooklyn and we go bring our
bikes out and we gonna go and have us a
good time guess what
they gave you the time they gave you the
location and you did what
you follow the instructions you showed
up at the time
you you showed up at the location that
they they tell you to go to
oh you know what to do that
hmm
but you you didn't know what to do
now
okay
got you
heard you brother
so
the following day
I did a stream inside of the Discord
and uh ripped bases up
in there and told them I'm taking the
rest of the week off
I said yeah I'll see y'all next week
we're taking the rest of the week off
and
I sure did take this free cold
so I told them I said I'm gonna do a
class this weekend coming up
and I said I want everybody to be a part
of it
what was what was this class yo what was
the class that I did I did the class
and the class was everything that I
already did before nothing changed
nothing at all nothing
that gives them no entries to get into I
didn't get you know what this is what
you want to trade with because you you
better be sure that that if you put this
on you I didn't give them
nothing
other than the same information
that they were refusing to what was the
strategy y'all
to remember
so I can tell you what what uh what I
need to tell you
but it's your job
to make sure that that you remember it
you create rules around it I've in the
playlist I've given so many different
ways to enter
I've given so many different rules that
your entry should abide by if you're an
impulsive type of person
or if you're a calculative type of
person
if you have anxiety ways to manage
so many different ways to end it and
what did I do I went back did a little
video with them and guess what it's the
same thing
guys go here you see you see breaker the
low you tap back in and it'll be short
but one thing you want to make sure
you're looking at is
the higher time frame as well you're
working in conjunction with the higher
time frame
and you're trailing your lows right
as you do you trailing your lows
and this is the way you manage and you
can do this each and every day whether
it's from the top side whether it's from
the bottom side no matter what pay it's
on
stops crypto Forex Futures bonds two
fish five loaves of bread whatever it is
if you if you could chart it you can
trade it
that's it until
in their group and I went and enjoyed
the rest of my my weekend
in post no Market Outlook for them
nothing
because I don't have anything to say
because I already said all of it and I
was disappointed as as a teacher
to know that that
I'm putting so much time and energy into
making sure you get it and I care more
about you getting it than you do
this this type of mentorship
know who's coming
coming here
this ain't
we're coming to the whole hands and
laugh with each other
no because you you laugh and still broke
nothing nothing you but but you know in
general
we we find ways to comfort ourselves
being broke we find ways to comfort
ourselves while under stress and we're
doing the opposite
of the things that we should be doing
always find time to to be comfortable to
to do whatever it is that we want to do
we always find time to do it always find
time to feed these habits
that are no good for us
always find time always find the funds
to do so
and we over here talking about my well
well my reason why is because you know I
I just I just want to give my family a
better life and I I want to buy my
parents a house
yeah and and you know I I just you know
I want to go in and and go back to my
country and to be able to you know and
and here's here's my presentation
you know this this is my reason why
and and I I
I I I really want to be able to do this
in life
and
and you're supposed to just just
show up here
with that little knick-knack paddy whack
work ethic
and you think Something's Gonna Change
for you in a market that people have
been trying
to figure out for years
I'm talking about decades people been in
this market
most have been losers
and you coming along
with that
kind of work
Jesus delivered Christ
so
I wrote to him and I said what's up
brother
class started this is what I did to
class
he said I haven't slept in two days
finally slept and just getting up
and I said it's cool brother
I recorded it
because I know what that meant
it wasn't telling me yeah I'm busy doing
so and so you know I'm gonna try to
catch it did you record it yet
were you were you ever drop the
recording no hasn't slept in two days
what's what's On this man's mind that he
hasn't slept in two days this is a week
after he wrote to me that he was on the
verge of losing everything
you telling me that he ain't sleeping
two days
and I'm like okay I know where that's at
because I know what kept me up at night
I know I know the the eviction son or my
dog kept me up
I know missing meals so my kids could
eat and and we have a little more
to eat
until we finally run out I I know that
kept me up for days
I get a tiny little bit of sleep and
then wake back up again
only could sleep two three hours
I know that kept me up
and
that's what was going on with him so I
began to see the evolution
proud of that he he
sent me a
a
thing he said he said have you checked
out the indicator for smart money
concepts by luck Lux algo
so all I did was send him a tweet
and my tweet said
this is why I send everyone to learn SMC
from ICT himself
because there was somebody saying oh all
you got to do is get in anytime you see
the indicator do this all you got to do
is get it anytime you see the indicator
do that
somebody you know said they were just
they posted a video about it so I sent
him that tweet
that it's an absolute Griff coming from
that company to say someone should do
this they're going to end up being a
liquidity
they're gonna end up losing their money
with this no matter what indicator you
have out there
it is not enough
that you should depend on
something popping up
and you going into to take a trip that's
called signals we don't do that here
Fair total
and that was the last conversation that
I had with him that entire conversation
last conversation I have
and he would show up every single day to
the uh
we show up every single day to the the
live streams that I was doing he started
to post some of his charts inside of the
thing he started to send me some of his
charts individually some people a little
insecure about posting it around the
people so they end up sending it to me
that's fine too
that's fine too if they privately send
it to me as well I'm fine with that as
well because it's still getting the help
that they need but they're putting
themselves out there
but if you if you look
that was March that he was telling me
that for those who count on your fingers
still
April
May
June he moved here
it's on the verge of losing everything
two months prior
to being able to
buy a house Bigger Than The Fresh Prince
of Bel-Air
more land than the White House
two months
because what doing exactly
what he was told to do
following the instructions putting in a
time making it work for himself
now
changed his whole situation
because of what obedience
y'all don't have to like me here I don't
care if y'all don't like me I like me I
don't care
but you'll have to take seriously
what it is that's being taught here
because it's necessary
it's necessary to have these things in
your mind going over and over and over
and over and over and over and over does
random thoughts
over and over again is plenty of mine
what I used to think about when seeing
empty car spaces imbalances
seeing seeing all these different
you know things outside that had nothing
to do with trading I would see it in
other things
because that's the only thing that was
in my mind running
the only thing I'm up at night
thinking about the entry that I missed
and how I could have
how I could have could have changed it
how I could have been involved in it or
the entry that I lost and and what I
could have did to
I'm up that's going through my mind the
whole time
the whole time how I over leverage when
I should not have
how I escaped
from an entry that I should have lost my
account on
because of what I didn't follow my rules
I don't care where Beyonce is
what I care about is is
why I'm not getting this I care about
that more than than what she's doing and
what what new show is out there
then who's playing what sports it was an
avid NBA follower I used to follow all
the games I used to watch all the games
when things got tight for me I knew what
I needed to do I knew I needed to let go
of everything
that fulfilled my momentary emotions but
did nothing
for my circumstances
nothing
if the part of risk management too
many on our way in Risk in life
y'all are not paying attention to
the things that's that's necessary to
progress your friends are going to be
there trust me the same friends that I
lost
learning this
I look back at where they are now and
they still in the same place
still having the same conversations
still think about the same thing still
blaming people for the issues that
happened
the friends that I lost
once I chose to pick up
and and do what I needed to do for my
future
I started to progress
I had to leave a lot of people
had to leave a lot of people behind
I realized that people weren't really my
friends
that's the thing about profitability
that a lot of people don't talk about
once you finally get this and you put in
the hours that's necessary to get this
and you cut off the whole world to do
what you need to do
you're going to have more people that's
against you than for you and you got to
be willing to lose
not just in your entries
You're Gonna Lose family over this you
can lose friendships over you're gonna
lose sleep definitely
but you're also going to lose a poor
mentality
you're going to lose a lot of the things
that held you back
you're going to lose weight I'm telling
you boy you're gonna lose some weight
you're gonna lose weight
and that's that's both
the weight
from your body
and the things that held you down
things that held you down
you'll lose that equally
and you're going to have a different
sense of of
you know
what reality actually is you're gonna
live in a different manner
you're going to lose that attitude
to lose the anger problems that you have
You're Gonna Lose the negative
self-talk
that you give you're gonna pick up some
esteem
You're Gonna Lose That depression that
anxiety get rid of all of it yo those
things are gonna
but it starts from somewhere doing the
same thing every single day
same thing every single day that's what
I tell people I can't give you
psychology I don't know what the issues
you know the the plague you are I don't
know what's happening
I don't know what you're thinking in
your mind how you feel about yourself
how you feel about others how you feel
about life things you're going through I
don't know those things so I can't give
you psychology on that
but what I can tell you is doing the
same thing every single day
and doing nothing but that
will put you
so far ahead
of the learning curve that when you look
back
you're not going to be looking at
you know I'm not where I want to be
you'll be looking at I'm nowhere used to
be
now I'm where I want to be but I'm also
not where I used to be
so he told me he was on the verge of
losing
everything and he only had one twenty
five thousand dollar account with zero
dollars in his bank account
and now he has three twenty five
thousand dollar accounts that are all up
a hundred and thirty five thousand
dollars in profit
so that's each account has a hundred and
thirty five thousand dollars in profit
and he says some days he doesn't even
have to trade
and gifts
this this is the kicking Disney kicker
here
guess
how much points
he gets in his trades
guess how many points
five
points
that he gets in the trades he takes
five
not these hundred Point stretches and
and and
you know
holding on all the way to the highs
taken out
Five Points
and look at what
for March
to now
this is almost almost three months
because it was April when he when he
really started to get it and he really
started to stack his account it was in
April
so three months later
he has three accounts three 25k accounts
that are in
135 135 000 in profit
all of them each
and he only takes five points
that's enough
for him
and look at how I put that put in my
head
so
you know I want you guys to understand
that there's there's so much power and
and obedience
so much power in
you know understanding this I'm gonna go
through the um
the group in July and and I'm gonna show
them
what matters most it's not being able to
catch every trade
it's not being able to take every single
entry you're just being able to get 10
points 10 points a day
just ten points
on a on a pair like this is so easy to
get 10 points you get 10 points in one
candle
points
that you can get you see I imagined
earlier when we came in here
I talk about how
you know we uh uh we're gonna come below
this right here and then you see a
balance that'll come back around and
take us back into
the range up above here
now say that while we before we even got
to to this
or we might have just tapped it
but I'm giving you guys a confidence
that
we're gonna trade below here
and then shift backed up into back up
into
this range now particularly Drew this
across yeah
did you see us make our way right back
to you
look at the rejection that came out of
here
what happened
I told y'all down here I said oh that's
a nice flip in there
you have a low here
you have a low here we respect that low
here
you have a low here
and at no point have we violated any
lows and we continue back into the
previous range
multiple opportunities
to get in on that move
happens every single day I was going
over it with my group
every single day
I don't know whether we bullish or
bearish on the day I have no idea I
don't care
because we're intraday Traders we you
know scalping
and the power of 10 points
is in each
and every swing
that you see here
and whether it's the rejections from the
left
or the continuations to the right
whichever side you want to take up an
entry on
some people only see the market in a
short way some people only see the
market a long way
good thing for me I'm probably autistic
so I see it both ways so you know you
you can be on either side of the market
but all you need is 10.
you guys can do the math
10 points is 40 ticks
so
with
with One Mini contract
you're getting four ticks
it's uh
five dollars per tick
with two which you guys see me mostly
use
it's ten dollars per tick
so ten dollars per tick on
10 points
that's a four hundred dollar trade
that you can get one of those each and
every day
or every 20 minutes
but you can get one of those each and
every day
in very precise areas and taking ten and
moving on with your day taking ten
moving on what you did now
add 10 contracts to that
add 20 contracts to that
guess what trailing drawdown or no
trailing drawdown
a lot of the times just one candle
has 10 in it
just one candle most of the time you you
know you might see two
that has 10 in it
whether it's short whether it's a long
10.
when I first started streaming I shared
it on Twitter when I first started
streaming the rules that I created when
I first let me actually show you you'll
think I'm lying
you'll think still think I'm lying let
me show you
because I'm a
great storytelling y'all always think
I'm lying so
let me show you how to see it
right here
look at what the rules say here
I said I'll take multiple entries from
the one minute I know I didn't put time
frame but whatever
I said which usually comes out to 20
trades per stream
also let me know if you want me to check
a specific ticker for you
10 Pips and dip is my recommendation for
each trade but you can hold to wherever
you want
my trades are not Financial advice
please consult for financial advisor
that was my very first video
that I ever posted
um that I ever did on this channel very
first video
when I became profitable I started
traveling doing all these different
things and I'm like yo none of this is
fulfilling if I
see how easy this
you know what I did for 210 a day 250 a
day for 300 a day you know what I you
know the type of stuff I had to do the
amount of things that I do and you
didn't tell me I could do that in two
candles
what
it's like nah I gotta teach this and I
spent a whole year doing just that
running up my accounts
while just teaching people for free
for free
nothing else
you say 10 Pips in dip you bring the
chips I got the Pips that's what you say
all the time in the beginning
baby
you bring the chips I got the Pips baby
and and that
is how all of this was
created because I was even learning
other things along the way as I started
to teach other people
I started to learn more what you guys
should consider is try to teach your
loved ones try to put into words what it
is that you're learning to your loved
ones and it's going to show you that if
you can't explain it to a five-year-old
then
you need some work
to do you can't explain it to a
five-year-old
so yeah I've been teaching my kids read
up but no red red down Green up
there's a teaching them imbalance
and and just like slowly walking them to
what does price do when it Taps into an
imbalance and it's going up
what do you expect first to do if it's
happened to an imbalance and it's going
down
just just really simple
what is that institutional candle
what is that hidden snd
and then you put them
into contacts
then you put them into context on the
trend that it's in
and and it there's almost just you know
build on that
don't go too much into that but
you guys should do that I said 10 Pips
into 10 points and you out 10 points and
you out 10 points of you out you take 10
contracts to put behind 10 points
you take 10 contracts to put behind ten
points
on NQ what are you at
two thousand dollars per trade
I'm sorry two thousand dollars the
minute you the moment you enter in
the candle TAPS in spout comes right out
2 000 just like that
there's no trailing drawdown nothing is
not going to come back you wait for
anything
unless you holding it but you don't have
to
because a lot of times just tap right in
and shift out we teach the manipulation
we teach how to get in on the
manipulation
and if you learn to be able to get that
10 each and every time which most times
almost always
you will
with just
10 the power of 10
and there are times that the
you know it may very well go further
than 10. it might go into 15 might be 20
sting man just ride out
sometimes what happened too
but
just 10 points alone
can benefit you so if you're demo
trading and it ends up being ten dollars
well twenty dollars
or is it being 20 cents
there's been 200 that would be two
thousand dollars whatever it is
if you're demo trading as long as you
can get the move each and every time
as long as you can get the move
each and every time it doesn't matter
what climate you change you're trading
in
it could be a recession you also I
showed y'all what what the early you
know with 2017 2016 kind of look like
you know even before that same type of
ranges where you get 50 to 100 Point
ranges in a day
but all you need is 10.
so I'm you know getting away from the
public space and
you may show the
YouTube I mean the the uh the group
we show them the power of 10.
and how each and every day you can make
something happen for you with just
the power
of 10.
just the power of 10. look at this
little Canada that went in here
this little one right here
this little one that tapped into the 30
of this year y'all see that and when it
pushed up
what'd you get on that candle
13.
on that and as if you were long
13 on that
we drag this on over here we have this
here
13 on that over here
from the bottom of there to to this one
pushing up that's 15 on that
just a few points actually a little a
little higher than 15 because the other
candle opened it
up so 15 on that
in the group we teach the zone
so looking price coming out of the zone
look at Bryce tapping back into
hidden s d below
price come back into what the 70 percent
of the Zone these are hitting levels and
coming out of that level
guess what
ain't it easy to get 10.
just 10 alone
say 10 contracts
two grand a trade
whether you're drawdown is trailing you
or not
you don't have to worry about that
because you're understanding the power
of how easy it is
to get 10 and get out
that one short that I showed you in the
Discord earlier took 15 points of one
candle you see
exactly
and one candle
out
y'all got me sweating up my shirt and
stuff like that might have to change
this
I mean I am preaching
but I want y'all to to
you know really really understand the
idea of what I'm saying this this common
occurrence here I was teaching them that
it happens every every single day
every single day everybody's chasing
these yeah yeah we're I'm telling you
the market is going down today we don't
even come in and want to know whether we
we bullish up there we don't want to
know that we don't care
we do not care if we're bullish or bears
we don't care at all
where am I able to get in and take time
that's it
where can I get in
and take ten
and remember the zones that we trade
from
is giving you 10 right out of it bam
closed
you got to tell you how
like I said whether it's two contracts
you put on that where there's 10
contracts you put on that no matter what
it is that you put on it
so long as you can get the move
then you have the possibility and you do
that all day you don't have to you're
not just stuck with doing that you know
like you got to find out one moment so
you're sitting on your hands and you
just waiting no
no who's waiting what
get away from Killzone wait for wait for
uh uh you know
wait for the for you know somebody to
stop talking because it's just
manipulation is that I hear this he can
destroy thing all the time stay out the
market where they do is he can do he can
destroy that's called a range and that's
the best environment to trade in
arrange the stupid
oh
that's the best environment you can
trade in
this range
I'm telling you you're gonna see July is
gonna be something and then August again
August I'm gonna do the boot camp
in August
uh and that should um
yeah definitely help with uh
any of the questions that
you know people might have because it's
gonna be straight through interview from
Zero to Hero and to enjoy the market
structure
to video one
video two
three four five and now six
and then showing you in different
sessions
Asia London
uh and New York
Sydney even
you know right out of spread hour you
can come in throw a Haymakers
you know so
these things couldn't be applied to any
Market you trade and I'm hearing Futures
a lot I'm here on NASDAQ you know I
taught on US 30 because people said that
was the hardest thing to trade so
obviously I said why not teach on it
so I told on US 30
and now you guys see mostly you know put
NASDAQ on the screen but I it could be
on anything
guys guess what you can you can trade
gold on Futures as well
you drink gold on Futures as well
same thing apply to go yeah
and goal to give you
way more points coming out of these
zones than
yo
gold will give you way more
then then you know something like NASDAQ
Willa or
you know whatever other pair you you
traded
very easy
to be able to get them 10 on goal what
no spread on Futures too
and you guys understand the power of
these little tiny movements and why you
should not be you know expecting these
these large
uh large entries
some people hold gold from from here and
they're holding it all the way to like
you know
some of above yeah I've been holding
gold for 1900 and I just I'm just
waiting for it to get on up to you know
back to 2000 you know like no
you get in a quick move on go
and quickly get out the same way you
traded as but gold will give you more
per per uh
per time especially in Asia
especially in Asia you know easy to get
10 points in Asia on gold
London Gold scallops all the other pairs
they scalloped smaller ranges so that
means your stops are smaller you know
it's
boy I'll tell you yo y'all gonna learn
something
we're gonna learn today
I'll go learn something
so uh
you know that that was just my little
two cents about why y'all should be
taking these um
Concepts
uh seriously
because you don't need to catch the top
and the entire move you know like going
somewhere you don't need to
all you need is 10 points nothing else
uh
yeah exactly yes this this tapped almost
everything that that everything within
the zone
this tapped almost everything with this
now I can take you to specific areas
that I would be expecting it to well I'm
going to be doing that in the Discord
specific areas that I'm expecting it to
tap into and what The Narrative of those
areas are telling me
The Narrative of those areas will tell
me where the price is going to continue
up above it
so you know the the narrative building
process is important too but yeah this
this is I told y'all that using these
zones these zones are just this is just
uh Child's Play this ain't no you know
no real stuff this is training wheels
when you're utilizing these zones this
is trading Wheels tradables trading
Wheels this is training wheels
using this
this is just to get you to conceptualize
what it is that the
the you know
I'm seeing
as a reason for why I'm expecting a
rejection in these different areas
but it goes a lot deeper than that so
this people that come in and and
you know they quickly jump over this but
this is the start of it there's there's
nothing else you can do nothing's gonna
speed you up you don't need a one-on-one
me I tell everybody that you don't need
no one-on-one you need to book a
one-on-one
you don't need to wait for no boot camp
you don't even need to join my group
all this stuff is there but it starts
somewhere
and that's the playlist
you know
there's Blues
he said it's up to tap to 70 and drop
this is 70 right here
of the largest zones I told you would be
yeah
trading into
and most people are looking for this
high up above here
is it a got a little green line up there
there we go
but look this this is either side as we
mentioned
whether somebody took a short hair is
that 10 points away from the short
10 points on this
better believe it
so
you don't want to dispel this
misconception of of you needing to catch
the bottom or catch the top
all you need to do is just catch 10.
yep
all you need to do
is catch 10. that's it
so uh I hope I hope that you know what
what I'm gonna do is um I'm gonna take
that that uh
portion
um from this video
and I'm actually going to put it into
the playlist as the psychology part of
it
because
again I can't give you psychology
specific to your situation
but all I can tell you is what you need
to do to change it
you know financially
because there's still other problems
that that finances don't solve you know
you know as much as I'm able to do I
still deal with like over stimulation at
times
still deal with you
certain issues as regards to my health
you know some days still you know have
just mental pressure of Life all that
other stuff that still comes with it you
know
but I'd rather cry on a full stomach
than an empty stomach
I'd rather cry in a home than
you know somebody could easily toss me
out
rather cry on the way to Target
and
having to go Target somebody for some
change you know
so uh it
it's an added bonus if you need
something you know
that's it
but
I'll add this part to the uh playlist as