okay
so here we go um you guys can hear me
right right good good
um so yeah I I asked you guys about this
Zone it was clear as day you know like
it was I expect most of you guys to get
it that right
there that right there remember what I
said about your zones too I said make
sure something is taken before price
manipulates into your Zone
so that's the thing that's taken
there
um but um on to what I called this uh so
so sandep what's up how you doing um you
know one thing I do appreciate about
um you know a lot of the uh uh students
here especially the younger students um
and that's nothing you know do with the
gas I'm Giza myself you know but um with
the younger students they they tend to
be
um um very transparent about their
process the emotions that they feel and
and how hard they're they take
on um losses and a lot of the times um
the lessons that that come through those
emotional
losses are the ones that are uh
lasting so um you know let me say this
directly to uh uh send deep and anybody
else that that happens to be in that
position um you know there there's you a
couple of students who have uh found
their found themselves um you know sort
of in that position where uh they're
doing everything they
can to
to understand this they're putting in
the hours they're they're uh uh you know
writing every single word that's spoken
they're going back over everything to
look at everything that's that's uh
um uh uh how do I say it every
everything that's
that's a part of a trade plan that's
concrete they're adding that into their
approach in the market yet there seems
to be
no uh breakthrough
or if there is it seems just like
this it seems like you get that that
high oh man DT FX it it his
Concepts crazy like have you have you
guys you know uh seen it soon soon as we
drop up you right in the zone you get in
the zone and and Bam it goes right out
perfect perfect right that's how some of
us are we we tapped into ch's anonymous
we tapped into
dtfs we tapped into the the uh uh stuff
that was there obviously we joined the
mentorship you know um took steps to
progress ourselves
but
this right here this extension
here this
extension moving its way up like
that
in in a a
market that is
healthy the market that's
healthy you're going to
have pullbacks
right sometimes it's deeper mitigations
than we anticipate
it but that deeper mitigation just
brings us back
to the foundation
right when when we
get when we get a a a boost off
of the original knowledge we took in to
help us to to break
through that little range that
our
um uh trading has had us in
for some
time we get that rush but then we often
head right back to where that Rush began
so you have a lot of people now who are
on the second
layer who are like okay I understand
swings I understand
fractals I understand to wait until
price takes something I understand like
there there's all of these these
different things that that
um you know they they kind of have
grasped to the point where they're here
right here this is this is back into the
P of their growth back into the P of
their development back into the P of of
where they
originally found some progress right
right but one thing I often tell the
students is that
even
though you begin to get to a place where
you find more progress what you need to
understand is that
you are not Incorporated in all of this
you and and what is
you you is a
refined
system that throughout all the feelings
and emotions within this this cycle if
you want to
take you're trading to another
level if you want to take it
higher then there are some lows that
that that's going to be
ran it's going to look like
this because guess what Within
this within the foundation of everything
that's
here we realize
that we only know a very small amount
we've only spent a very short amount of
time doing
this and what we don't
know or or what we don't
remember is that the
blueprint is
higher highs higher lows right higher
highs higher lows right but what we're
not often paying attention to within
this move
down into US trading
higher is that this little move inside
of
here was not a part of
structure it was just the
introduction to let you know
know that we'd be
reaching to that side of the market
whatever is back here whatever is back
there so you need to understand
that even as you make this
push and an advancement in your trading
you're going to have some lows that go
below where you even started how you
even even began to to you know um
process this all the different ways that
you felt about yourself that means you
are running this is where you started
remember Charter Anonymous is is this
this
large let me just you know change the
color for Optics Char Anonymous is this
large box here you scratched the surface
and that catapulted you so what does
that mean about this Zone this community
the the teachings that are that are
placed within the depths within the
depths of the material that's there the
the the stuff that's there that that you
know if if you can remember every word
and friends in the office you put that
energy there put that energy into the
the deepest parts of it the things
people don't go back and watch go to the
videos that have the the lowest amount
of views on it
and be like oh my gosh this
is this the treasure is really Beneath
the Sea it's it's
beneath our plans our plans was
what our plans was to come into Char is
anonymous right because I know I know
some some of y'all you know uh uh had
had those plans as well our plans were
to come into chars anonymous
spend a month and then become a
millionaire the next
month but some of us had to find out
that our plans was not a part of
structure so we were able to go back
into not not the origin of your move the
origin of
mine the origin of the playlist the
origin of the basics the principles the
you know it's it's all
here and
that's where that ENT that the Ascension
occurs
that's where you begin to actually
create
structure that that ran your prior
thinking that prior low that was in your
mind that that prior you know uh uh
idea that you know sure enough
within one month's time you are going to
take this you you know blow the roof off
yes you can you can but guess what every
Trader no matter how much you remember
the things that Dave
teaches has taught in in in any of the
forums that I've taught
on every
Trader will have to run their own
low we have to run the low of their
expectations
we have to and and unreasonable
expectations at that we'll have to run
the lad of of holding on to what it is
that they had in
mind and stick
to the foundation of
it stick to what's what's been given
remember everything that you need is
here but for some people the surface is
what they're looking to you know uh uh
take and and and go to the next level
and and do whatever it is they're doing
it's the surface that they're paying
attention to but they don't know first
to break structure to the top side
right that's thing they not considering
this what what video was that y'all come
on y'all know first
to first tap breaks structure to the top
side and when the second tap comes
in often times with the second
top you get a run of the low that
provided the first
to and we begin to now
accumulate to
leave and take out the high that brought
this low to us right so our development
at tra as Traders it's the same exact
way but we need to understand that
that we've we've uh uh We've tapped the
surface of what we know but there's a
lot deeper we can go that can catapult
us to a higher
place and and some of you guys are are
in this you know some of you guys there
somewhere within this Dynamic whether
it's the person first joining whether
it's the person you know just watching
the playlist whether it's the person
that's down in the dumps over here and
feel like you know they just want to
break structure and and and go to the
downside and just short the rest of
their career as a Trader that's not you
you are not that
person you are hungry you are willing to
do what it takes you are willing to sit
down and not get up until things change
but you have to also be willing to be
broken that's what the market does to
people it breaks you the more detail you
notice the harder it is to to make
certain decisions but guess what those
decisions become a lot easier because
now that you have that detail you're
going to know within that detail what's
highly probable and what's
not and now you can choose you don't
even have to be a part of everything oh
give me something give me something give
me something give me something that that
sounds like a
gambler but for the person that knows
when to step
in that
detail that you're
learning there comes a time where you
become confused because you see all of
it and you do not know where to start
start you have no idea where to begin
because that looks like that but it also
looks like that but it also looks like
that but it also looks like that but it
also looks like that but it also looks
like that but it also looks like that
but it also looks like that and if you
go back into back
testing you'll see that all of it looks
like that where are you in this in this
equation where are
you where do you know the move comes out
of whatever move it is if you want that
Mambo Jambo you know nice
looking if you want that large move just
just leave not that means you got to
leave alone all of the other stuff sit
it to the
side and just stick with that move that
you know is rooted in in the personality
that you have and and the
contentment for whatever it is could
could be given to you behind that zone
and that might mean going back to
incorporate higher time frame into lower
time frame just so you're on the right
side of the
market yes you don't have to go up but
it's important for you to go up if you
struggle with what's below let me show
you guys um uh there was this this Wick
that I set um an entry on last night I
think it was a 12 minute was it no it
wasn't 12
minute uh let me see
uh was it or was it the one hour no it
wasn't the 1 hour so it had to be the
15 so there there was a limit that I I
had
set on this right here
right
and I set the limit
there because it was a higher time frame
Zone my understanding was that this low
within here successfully took out this
High to the left body closure so this is
a sucessful low that's
here so my limit was set here and guess
what I never got tapped
in never got tapped into this limit
because of the spread on cfds now my
invalidation was behind here and I was
just looking to take profit right up
above the previous high that led me into
the zone right
here and the spread did not take me
in but was that something that I was
like okay yeah now the the spread didn't
take me in so let me go and try to short
something real quick let me look for a
short in here maybe let me try to short
this right here then let me because we
we got to get back into even even over
here look at this Zone
here you have this Zone within here was
the 50% tapped in
here let me just double check before I
give youall snake oil be like yeah you
see it wasn't tap and it was it
wasn't so when it's not making its way
back to
what you
anticipated how do you engage with
price how do you follow what it is
that's occurring now if we were just to
remove this obviously we see no lows
taken right this is this stairway up
this is trend line whatever you want to
call it so you know that this side of
the market you are on but this is after
a flip that occurred on the 15
minute so some people what they're doing
is and and let me let me show you guys
cuz this was me I listen that that's why
I say it's important mentorship is
important mentorship is important
because you guys have to know that
within that same system that you're
using here are here are things that's
going to trip you up so so it's it's as
simple as
remembering where you are within your
range right so we know this is the
bottom of the range we know that this is
more or less the top of the range up
here most of the rejections came out of
here these three or four up here within
this low down below and this high up
above to the left multiple rejections
are happening in here but
this is particularly this Zone here
right so when a lot of us see this break
up
above we
immediately want to begin getting
involved in something that's going to go
higher and especially on the 5sec that
could suck you in and trip you up if you
do not leave the one minute as your
master time frame and follow the one
minute as your master time frame so
here's what ends up happening now we
want to engage in a a market that we see
is trending higher and we want higher
prices but what we don't understand or
what we're not really using at the
Forefront of our our uh understanding is
that we do not have enough money to push
price higher in the event that we take
out a high to the left right they did
that not us not our money their money
was taking us that down right that we
just we was just a part of it but that
money was taking us down and this is
where their money flipped right here
this area here so when they brought us
up above their High here to the left it
would be nothing but
audacity for me to believe that I can
get price to go higher and now I'm in
that Blockbuster move going back to sell
side and there's a lot of us that plan
for things like that rather than being
content with what's currently happening
here so what do we end up
seeing we end up seeing a couple
rejections coming off that that area
below we get the confirmation and this
is where people are getting in at this
confirmation to trade higher or people
are looking for a short to trade
lower and the greed steps in right
here the greed steps in this delivered
the high to the left but
then we saw an equal High which what
takes out both
lows so here we are in our it's the snd
responsible for the break so yeah the
first tap to break a structure to the
top side the second top not even knowing
where we are
not even knowing what occurred what
would where where we are in structure
these things happen to us and we get
lost and confused without just
remembering
right that when in doubt yes you must
stay out that entirely true but you also
should not be trading things that you do
not have experience for and I'm not
talking to to deep in general I'm
talking to
everybody taking trades on for for
things you do not have experience with
you do not have experience with if
anybody had experience holding 100 200
300 Point moves guess what they wouldn't
be here right
now so for us to think or have the
audacity that we can get more when we
barely walk away from the market with
anything at all it's a heat check for us
is 10 enough or is it
not and is that 10 aligned within your
your understanding of your ability to
get 10 and back testing each time some
of you guys need to stop back testing on
the 5sec and back test on a one minute
how are you going to be successful with
the 5c if you don't even know what the
one minute is doing you just you
pressing the button and hoping that it
just follows whatever you your think
analysis
is cuz you didn't use technicals you I'm
I'm sure you didn't you thought about it
and said oh price can go higher and the
minute you thought price could go higher
guess what right the other
way and then the minute you turn around
and try to engage the other way right
the other
way and then it's easy to see him back
testing and in back testing we go oh oh
yeah you know that that's thing that Tri
me up a lot you know cuz back testing is
looking like this for some people just
like this missing all the first of all
do do you see how much detail is in this
bad boy much detail in this look look at
this equal did we say a run what oh you
you see
the so so um if it's and deep and and
everybody else that's that's sort of out
there um you know who who feel stuck or
or who you know continue
to um you know trade wait let me
actually just turn this
off wait don't tell me I lost everything
did I oh come
on come on I'm just
oh okay whatever um yeah so so we we
need to know that when we are back
testing are we back testing to make
money are we back testing to learn what
price is doing so we could see it ahead
of time and know how to engage with
price I'm not back testing to find Longs
I'm not back testing to find shorts I'm
not clicking through the bars to find
where I can get in on an entry the
reason why I started back testing to
begin with the reason why I started back
testing to be
with is because I wanted to know how
this
moved not to to actually like push the
button and and oh yeah right there I was
I was right on that that zone yeah cuz
we we write on the Zone today and then
we take the same Zone tomorrow and we
get clapped on
it and then we take three more zones the
same day that look like today's Zone and
we have confidence in today's Zone but
now is a new day
and we get clapped 20 ways from Sunday
on that
day because we're we're carrying over
what what it is we're doing in back
testing to try and materialize it to
money quick but we should want to
materialize the things we learn in back
testing
to understanding quick to applying it on
the charts quick not
to make the money quick because guess
what you can put 20
contracts on on a short you could even
get access to a 100 contracts and throw
it on a
short and flip a coin and be
right so it's it's
not about back testing to be right back
testing to put a a a monetary amount
behind it it's back testing your
understanding of what price does versus
what it does not do and guess what all
you're doing is exploiting where to get
in that's it you're exploiting that
little subtle change there and you're
and now you're learning where to get in
now you're learning how to operate now
you're like there's a ton of stuff
that's within that I tell people no zone
no trade but you know a lot of the the
the students in premium see that some of
the zones that I take it's not
traditional zones it's sometimes the
entry is not a a traditional entry but
it's because you fully understand what
Market structure is doing or or where
order flow is going or what we're
reaching into or what part of order flow
you're in I always say that right so
that means that if you're in a certain
part of order flow that takes price
higher and we come back and run a
low and we tap into is something that we
understand this is how the market works
and this is how to clean people out and
then they begin to trade higher from
here we don't necessarily need to be
present for that top if we understand
that this is the way it works now it's
done with this side and it's heading to
that side and this is the lowest part
that I'm
in on on the side that's getting ready
to to be attacked I'm in the lowest
portion of that entry back testing will
teach you
that but to back test and say hey so I
back tested and I I I calculated that
within 10 points and if I at least give
myself a considerable stop of maybe 11
points I can be risking X Y and Z and
then if I Target a one to one then with
the one: one I'm able to and you're
building up all of this stuff in your
brain about what your entry is supposed
to do for you you're fixing yourself in
that in that position of what price is
doing and
then we get
clapped
because our rules or at least the things
that we
expect it's not defined in the
candlesticks why do you guys think I
said no zone no trade to begin with and
then I said take 10 and get out take
five take 10 and get
out what do you guys think I said that I
didn't say that because you guys can't
catch more than 10 but the greed in you
will always try to get
more rather
than understanding where your level of
experience is and trading relative to
that if you don't come in throwing 50
100 Point bangers every day on on some
of these pirs you should not be looking
for it
if you've lost more
money in the market than you've taken
out you should not be looking for
it because you need to understand that
that when you fully grasp this
compounding will be so much more
powerful than your high and low being
taken out you oh yeah I want to go for S
sign oh yeah yeah it's going to go to
buy side you know like we have have all
of these
ideas that we want to see
materialized and our experience doesn't
even support
it our experience doesn't even support
it when I built my computer there was a
ton of drives I had to download that did
not come
pre-installed there were things I had to
download just to make certain components
of it
work so the product was put together and
and ready to turn
on but that doesn't mean that everything
was in its its uh Data Bank its memory
bank to be able to operate at Full
Throttle
right needed to be some things cleaned
out blo
wear blo wear
is I tell you how to beat the market I
tell you
if you in if you invest if you
invest in an in an SB Index Fund you're
going to beat the market every time
that's
that's blow
wear trading in the zone with Mark
Douglas blow wear all of these things
are blo wear because they do not
actually
help you to perform the task at
hand do not actually help you with
that so some of us need a hard reset
like I'm talking about you know reset
everything from from from
from the
basics from the
basics
back to the
basics some of us
joined some of us joined after running a
low in our
lives some of us joined after running Al
low in our career running Al low in we
we might have been at highs
before but some of us joined after
that and we somehow thought here was
going to be the thing that brings us
back to the former
high and when you hit resistance
that should have sent
you below the expectations that you came
in with deeper
into all the information that's resting
inside of here all the information that
comes from the profitable people you
even see in this
group they months months back they were
exactly where you
were but what did they do follow those
instructions
and on the other side of
that bullishness but guess what with
some of them they'll
still have these highs and
lows that often times they come to run
little inside
low and they don't give up there
they know that it's just to bring us
back
to wherever it is we were originally
going they're aware of that they
understand that and and they take these
losses and they run to back test they
run to watch the video they go back to
to whatever it is that help them to
build that understanding the first time
they Double Down On
It and that's when you see them trade
higher and they ask questions like oh do
you guys have down days do you guys have
bad days do you guys ever struggle do
you guys you know like you have to be
transparent with that journey of a
traiter which is entirely true but we do
have those down days but because a lot
of the stuff that we
did was a part of
structure those down days do not afford
us to go any lower than a certain point
we just continue to mitigate these areas
mitigate these these
INE
[Music]
inefficiencies that's so funny mitigate
these
inefficiencies that are left behind and
are winning winning winning winning and
we just come back to double down on
those so when we get back to the same
place we were last week or the same
place we were last month we understand
that even if we run the low of that
place doesn't
matter we we created a new hind look at
look at where we came from look at all
the stuff we got through look at all the
the issues that
arose and you found your way you were
you were down here you about to give up
you about to break structure and go
spiraling support her resistance you but
but what happened what
changed you did something
different so for anybody here you know
doesn't have to be one person in
particular but for everybody here if
you've lost a funded account
if you know you you lost a a personal
account whatever kind of a whatever kind
of account it was that that you you know
lost you need to understand that you can
just buy another one right say Amen
somebody you can just buy another I'm
kidding you need to understand that you
are not your funded
account that separate you from what's
done on that account you are not your
fund that account lost not you they that
account that they were limited that
account was limited and and that account
lost
but for me I took the lesson they took
the L and now I'm going to build on top
of that I'm coming back for you
baby I know where I left
you and and that's the energy that that
you know you guys sort of have to uh
show up with you know you are not the
mistakes you made on your funded
account you are you you that's not you
that's you learning
you can learn to lose $100,000 too
though of your own money but you don't
have to this is some of these funded
accounts are far cheaper than it is to
pay College
tuition I always say it was a waste of
time for me to go to college I wish I
would have found this sooner I would
have definitely been great at this even
if I found it sooner this is my speed
this is something that I I'm I'm an
obsessive person I'm going to put in
time to what I'm doing I'm going to
become the best at it the best that
means I'm going to study everybody else
their emotions their feelings their way
of managing I'm going to study all of
that and then go in the lab and cook up
whatever it is that I can I I can afford
to put in my own pot and cook it up in
back testing
right and then show up the next day and
and and make it happen and if I wanted
to if I wanted to be really spicy I
would back test and forward test at the
same
time back test and you come on y'all got
so many pairs Mark something out on
another pair while you back tesed some
of the issues back tesed working out
where wherever it is you were having
trouble
with Mark that stuff out and go back to
it it's rewarding in itself back testing
may not feel like much go forward test
with back testing
then and you know I feel like those
things will pick you back up again you
have to rely on some Kumbaya session or
or or you know you don't have to go hire
a coach or or whatever it is that's out
there you can deal with it yourself just
by back testing yourself you know where
you go wrong every time you know where I
was going wrong
overleveraging that's where I was going
wrong overleveraging knowing the dollar
amount that was enough for me and
chasing
that
but I still could
not just catch a little tiny move I know
I wanted $1,000 out of a trade I still
didn't even know how to get $5 from
it so so
measurable targets
measurable and practical trading if
price leaves you it left
you no reason to force a trade from the
other side of it wait for it to come
back to you and there's lessons that you
learn in Waiting there's people that
would discourage you from sitting at the
chart and watching your setup or or
watching it come back to your area for
you to you know take an entry some
people discourage that but you guys have
to sit down and watch the learn stage of
it watch everything that's happening why
do you think I have all of these charts
over here all all of these things you
don't think I go through through these
things every now and again and just Mark
out different things you know when
whenever whenever I'm
ready
got let me just look at this real quick
I
think
was it
usdc oh yeah it was it
was
oh no no it was NZ USD nzd
USD so somebody had asked me on on
Twitter about it first of all they said
it look interesting I'm next now when
people write
that hold
up sorry now when people write it looks
interesed I'm just going to ask what's
interesting about it you know yes it did
it did I'm not going to say it look
interested but I told the guy I said
we're going
below 59600 I said it's looking the
market is looking look look at me with
with the genius
the got my my my uh educator had I'm
like well we're we're going below 59600
you guys have see my my TW my response
on Twitter why did
I have an idea that we were going below
this and why wouldn't I wait for any
kind of Longs if I know that this is
where price is reaching
into that's what I would do I would wait
on that so when I when I mentioned that
you saw this move go up like that and
then what this breakdown occur right
within
here or was it over here I think it was
like early morning so it might have been
over there something like that but where
do we end up going what direction were
we looking for because of the narrative
that was already given to us I I don't
know if you guys um uh let me see what
his name is in here he he uh posted some
charts that um
I know for a fact he's been in the
playlist um I think it was Precision
trades I don't know if he's heing now
but I think it might have been Precision
trades um yeah yeah Precision trades he
posted in the member spam section if you
look at what he posts about video 4
only you look at what he post he's not
running around trying to take every
single entry 3050
70 all like trying to take everything
every every WI way price goes and you
know if you look at it he has very very
detailed um I guess not very detailed
but there's some there's some
annotations that are there that's
helping them to understand what it is
that they're seeing in the context of
the playlist alone and you don't see
them drawn out no large zones there you
know yeah I'm going take this one up
there and then draw this larger one from
down here and I'm going to take that one
up there that's something that will d
destroy your trading career before it
even
starts destroy your C your trading
career before it even
starts all I used when I first started
was the 50% and why do you think I was
able to see all the other stuff going on
around
it and pay attention to it oh yeah I
know that's the the you or or you might
even know that's the 30 but do you know
how to trade it no you just saw a tap on
it and you thought we were ready to
trade higher
and then got clapped right after and
then try to take another trade after and
got clapped again on that one because
when you realize you were invalidated
you try to trade the opposite way to get
the rest of the move and got invalidated
on that one
too those things are fixed in back
testing and when you're back testing
with
rules that's it when you're back testing
with rules nothing else you should not
be aimlessly back back testing oh let me
go back test a
flip let me let me go let me go back
test you know the the market
flipping yeah so you see if I just use
the 50% of the flip then that'll be
fine and you got zones from from
everywhere you don't
just yeah if if I just use the 50% of
the
flip then it'll be it'll be
great the 50% of what
flip when you back to this this if your
chart looks like this I will ignore it
you don't know what you're doing when
your chart looks like
that price is only doing one thing it's
either it's going up or it's going down
and for you to have this idea that maybe
it might be going up but maybe it also
might be going down you shouldn't even
be touching a button to trade
with with that kind
of I'm thinking that
if I'm I'm getting ready to um uh use
the the admins a lot more to speed up um
uh well to clean up the group a bit
because what grinds my gears the most is
people saying that they have back tested
and and you know learned certain things
and then they're posting entries saying
maybe I
think no get that off of The Forum
there's no you think you're not that
that's not it's either it is or it isn't
you sure about it or you
not but there's no think cuz when it
come time to take your money they don't
think gone ye your stop is they don't
think about running your
stop you you ever noticed that they get
to you take profit and they they trade
away for every just a little bit see a
little consolidating r take profit look
like it's go in there again and go away
from a little bit you ever seen him go
to your stop loss
ye straight through it supposed to take
you out there but took you out
[Laughter]
there so
um we really have to realign what it is
we're back testing
you're you're back testing one thing
until you get so good at that that now
you can back test the next thing and
then when you get so good at that now
you can back to and when you look back
on all of
it man oh man growth that the that's on
the other side of that that that type of
energy only comes from putting your head
down down and getting to
work you are not ready to push the
button if you cannot say where price is
going and your entry is not
actionable
enough to to take it there and and what
I mean by that is a lot of you guys be
trading and and maybe not you guys but
just people in general a lot of people
trade within this environment
and marry moves in
this they marry shorts that are going
down and goes back to take them out they
marry Longs that are going up it goes
back to take them out they marry shorts
that are going down it goes back to run
their stop they marry Longs oh yeah we
flipped in here yeah now we going up
then it takes them out like
that marry marry shorts here price
trades up moves down into here equal low
here and now they're doubling down on
their short within
there we have to stop that kind of
trading if we actually want some
progress and that means that
understanding what it is that we're
doing before we even push the button is
important
before you need measurable
targets you need specific entries that
you do not deviate from this is the only
kind of Entry I'm willing to take some
of y'all need oneto ones go back to the
basics get that tap into the 50 and let
it come out of the zone and that's it
that's where you close it up because you
can't trust yourself on anything
else right
now so I mean I'm I'm having this
session not not just for uh uh one of
the students but but for everybody in
general that you need to know what you
are doing you cannot afford to come in
here and guess and then think that that
your emotions won't you know take some
sort of damage from
it so um I know that message is for for
quite a few people not just for one um
and and if the shoe fit you know lace
that stitch up
because you you want to do things to
rule out or or to get rid of the
unnecessary quirks or behaviors that you
have within your trading now you want to
do something to to you know quell or get
rid of those issues because as you as
you grow as your account size gets
bigger as your your um uh position
sizing you know get gets larger these
same things are going to show
up you might think it's nothing with a
little one lot two lot but when you
start trading on on larger size
then now all of a sudden a psychology
session needs to be booked when it's the
same
move it's the same move the same thing
no matter what's behind it it's the same
move so if price is doing the same thing
every
day and you have a losing day what
changed it wasn't
price it wasn't the
algorithm it wasn't manual intervention
or or whatever these things are that
people you know just seek and destroy
and and and like whatever it is they say
for not understanding what price is
actually
doing
so that means that every time we take a
higher time frame higher low seek could
destroy starts and there's no way you
could get involved in that at all
because
because let not even go go that route
you know save that for the mentorship um
but I'm going to put this video on
YouTube because this is not just for for
you guys this is also
for you know like everyone that will
come into this space everyone whether
it's the trading space whether it's the
mentorship no matter what it is this you
guys have to be realistic about it I had
600 bucks when I
started and that's all I had to my name
if I lost that I was
done done and dusted it was over for
me but knowing what was on the other
side of that and knowing the amount of
pressure I applied to to you know like
uh
uh what I was doing in school and even
when I was studying for school I wasn't
out there going to parties I wasn't you
know watching all this TV and and all
that stuff
no I was taking 21 credits this semester
and working two jobs and volunteering on
the
side volunteering two jobs that were
paying me in different cities and taking
21 credits and putting them on two days
out of the week so guess what when
finals came around do you know how
unbearable that F that had to be like
the worst part of the semester was
finals and
midterms because guess what if you
taking 21 credits look at how many and
they're all on one one or two days so
I'm in school Tuesday and Thursday
taking 21 credits I'm there from 8:00
a.m. to 8:00 p.m. imagine what exams
look like imagine
what but I was able to to create a
system around that that got rid of what
partying that got rid of what
friends that got rid of what all of this
extracurricular activity that had no
bearing on whether I would be successful
in what I was studying or
not so I got rid of
that
sometimes it's just in that I was
playing video games when I first
started even when I was pulling money
out of the market I was still playing a
little bit of video games and the minute
I silenced all of that the minute I got
rid of all that yes there's balance but
you cannot afford balance right now
that's for anybody out there that's
struggling or whatever you cannot afford
balance cuz if you over here talking
about balance guess what yeah increase
increase your balance in in lifestyle
and watch your your balance in finances
decrease it's all about balance yeah
okay you want to balance that book and
not the
checkbook something has to
change and and that's your way to the
next
level by
changing
something so uh this for everybody here
you not not just you know not just cep
or or anybody else but it's for
everybody somebody can get something out
of
this and change gears and and undo a lot
of what they've done over the past month
over the past year or whatever it
is and for those who are progressing
don't be so hard on
yourself you're not where you used to
be you may not be where you want to be
but you are not where you used to
be that deserves a round of applause
even if you feel like you you're still
you know struggling or you you still you
know trying to figure things out or it
might be overwhelming at this at this
place in your life you're not where you
used to
be that's what we
celebrate but we keep pressing forward
until we get there we don't stop until
we get there we don't pick up our head
until we get
there and then when we get
there we don't even going to want to
talk to anybody anyway because when you
start to really understand money you
realize everybody's crazy this the where
y'all spend your money oh my goodness
you you traded
$400 for for shoes to to step on the
floor all right that let me like get
beside myself so um that that's for you
guys you know you guys get early access
to it then I'll prepare I'll premere it
um uh for the public this will probably
be video 12 of the playlist um so s deep
you just uh created a a a good um uh
segment in in your in you know your
growth and in in your struggles you
still
provide something that could help others
and and this was it your honesty your
transparency you know your willingness
to be open and and and you know forward
or direct with what you're dealing with
knowing most traders in this industry do
not that's why I sto to do this
segment that's why I stopped to have
this conversation with you and anybody
else that any of this applies to so I'm
stop the recording right
here