okay here we go does it let you guys
know we're
recording yes you you are awesome Lis
definitely all right great
great great now we are
recording
ready for a double headed yeah that's
how it's going to
feel I wake up in the morning I'm gonna
be like ah why did I do this last
night but it's cool you know I work for
myself
so I'm gonna dock my own
pay T what's up how's everything man
good seeing you always happy to see you
around man I know you're hungry for for
Learning and and you want to learn more
um I know you're definitely going to get
it you going to be able to leverage this
and you won't have to have you don't you
won't have to take the same path you
know new friends you know take or or
will take you know so always happy to
see you around
man let's get into
it all right
great
actually where is
um gotta pop out the
chat all right there we go my friend
Stacy is on tonight hey Stacy what's up
how you doing
girl I hope I um you know teach pretty
well um well enough to to make you miss
out on sleep because it's kind of late
right
now so I hope I meet those standards put
me in a pretty tight spot
leis no I'm
kidding all right
um let me yeah yeah that's that's uh old
man sleep time 10
o'clock
um
I know I'll let you know all right
fingers
crossed Ryan what's up how's everything
man I got your message by the way Ryan
uh I know those days
man oh you know like when they say the
baby and the bath
water I know those days man but you know
hats off to you you know being involved
you know you know it's a newborn and and
you
know difficult
man
yeah yeah get some coffee right yeah
yeah exactly get some coffee that's what
we
need at this point I just need to
eat the the coffee beans as chips you
know I think that's what I need to
do just munch on
caffeine I used to eat the nestly powder
out of the the uh the Box you just eat
the instant
coffee yeah so um I want to make sure
that that uh C me to F the strategy yeah
yeah exactly exactly that's the bridge
underwater they don't know that there
coffee that's all it
is uh so you guys um I want to make sure
everybody's familiar with um swing
points you guys
understand swing points right and it's a
bit ugly but
I make sure you guys
are familiar with this so these are
essentially a series of highs and lows
in an
uptrend and then whatever would would be
here this this would be the next high
here um so with these highs and lows um
whenever you have this low put in and
you have a high a new high introduced
that breaks Above This High
here that validates this low as the
protected low in terms of the
trend so now you're looking for price to
come back within the range of this
high
and this
low and a lot of the
times when price comes back within the
area there are different areas that
price often goes to
um some people talk about the discount
area some people talk about the premium
area you know there's there's quite a
few areas that price Taps into
um you know whenever it is that that
we're trending up or trending down the
same thing goes for for downtrend as
well
so what happens here is that price Taps
into an area that's below here that's
below this low below this high price
Taps into an area around here that's
responsible for the break of this and by
responsible I
mean
let me see if I could find an area now
uh maybe an area we tapped into I think
I just actually caught
one right
here so if you guys
[Music]
look this is the
high right here this is the last low
that's right here obviously we're
shifting structure to the top side you
know here like you know usually when we
want to see our bullish flip so this
would be the long here that we're
generally
taking but oftentimes you have it to
where if price crosses above a high you
know a high is taken
out there's usually an area below this
last high that was taken out that was
responsible
for the structural shift
above so usually it's an snd zone or
there's some sort of imbalance that
price may end up tapping into and a lot
of the times there there is an snd Zone
below
here
but if there's multiple snd zones
often times you can rule out the
lowest because there are times where
this has mitigation already within
itself as price is pushing up above now
there if you look here there's not um a
lot of mitigation here already you know
so price just happened to trade higher
but there was an
imbalance let me
actually make this visible for you guys
there was in imbalan directly above the
area this area
here this was the last down move that
sent price up to break structure to the
top side the last down move that sent
price up so often times the last down
move is where price is coming back to
mitigate before it trades
higher so what I did was I saw this
imbalance directly above the zone and I
usually say utilize the imbalances that
are nearest to the snd D Zone so I had
this imbalance here this is when uh the
the market opened over here price tapped
the imbalance right
here right above the snd Zone
responsible for the structural break to
the top side
price Taps this instead of tapping into
the
zone and it takes us
up so the first tap usually is a scalp
the second tap is you're looking for a
double bottom on the right side and then
price goes up so you see we're still
actually pushing from from this this
area of Market open right here at this
imbal this this imbalance that's here
but if you
look there are swing points that you
know price is making as it continues
higher there are some swing points that
price doesn't return back
to right
here price doesn't go back to it just
because it hasn't gotten here or hasn't
come to mitigate here does not mean that
you can't get involved on anything High
higher than this most people are waiting
for it to come back here and if it never
does they're just watching price and not
getting in so now what they're trying to
do
is they're trying to catch the sell up
here to come down here or try to catch
the sell up here to come down here or
try to catch the sell up here to come
down here and and they're exhaustingly
looking for nothing but sales trying to
come back down to this
area because they believe that price is
going to come back
to this area to mitigate
it and they continue to do that over and
over and over again and it looks exactly
like this short here short there short
there short there short there short
there short there just trying to create
a short to fit The Narrative of price
coming back to the area
and it doesn't make it that but the
thing about swing
points up here let me actually uh move
this and then erase
this H
yikes
so the thing about swing
points are
that you could have price come down
here and you could have price stop here
you could have price make its way back
up
there and you could have price come here
and it could look like this
and for you you
see an order block
here an order block
here and as price is
trending you're trying to figure out
price could be making making its way
down now let's say let's say we get you
know move here we
get just come up
above come
here tap into the air we go short now we
short below this
low we tap here most people see this tap
here most people see this tab
here
and they automatically think that we're
putting in another
high
here but often times we end up getting a
tap
here to retrace up into some area left
behind here and then we continue
down then we tap here and they think
we're bullish and we're we're going to
heaven
and we end up tapping into some area
just above and then we come back down to
here then they're playing this as
bullish trying to
find this bullish move that's going to
take us up here and let's say it comes
all the way
here and
then it continues
down like that and they
have trades that
are
here trades that are
here some losses maybe up
here you know like
here another trade down
here all trying to catch price going
up trying to catch the bottom of
price because of these areas to the
left that they're confusing themselves
about so I mentioned that the areas to
the
right are the areas that you want to pay
attention to in terms of getting
involved in
continuations the areas on the left are
areas that you're looking for price to
possibly reverse and then continue up
out of the
area so the the area to the left is
looking for
reversals but often times we're
confusing oursel with these demand zones
that are here and we're trying to trade
each and every one of them there could
be like a smaller one in here here there
could be like a very tiny one here and
we're playing all of this trying to just
get a move going
up
and we're losing on some of
them so
now we get into a buy here it takes us
out we jump into a cell
here and it goes up takes us out
we jump into a buy right here it goes
down take us
out we jump into a sell here it goes up
takes us out we jump into a buy here it
goes down takes us out and that's how
the cycle of Madness continues to
look it continues to look that way and
it's because we're confusing ourselves
let me actually take some this we're
confusing
ourselves with these
zones as prices coming down instead
of instead
of looking for an area that's
here
or or an area that's
here you know or an area that's
here for price to make its way back up
to like
this we're looking over here and trying
to chase the history within the past
because we're trying to find
reversals rather than look looking at
areas that are being tapped into on the
right side for continuations
down so if you see something is trending
down find an area to get in as it's
going down you'll see the reversal at
whatever important area that price may
come in
touch whether it's below or whether it's
above you'll see the
reversal within a specific area that
it's being rejected from like a Supply
area from the higher time frame or
demand area from the higher time
frame so we're trying to catch all of
this down below
and these moves are giving us
more these moves here they're giving us
way
more but in in turn we're trying to to
catch this and trying to catch this and
trying to catch this and trying to catch
this and trying to catch hoping one of
them
is the point of reversal and we can take
it all the way back up
there and that's how we end up losing
more trades than
winning so what I always
mention while we are trading is that
whatever direction we're looking to head
to based on the higher time frame
bias
take one
trade going in that
direction this would already be shifted
to break even after one structural low
is taken
out and you would just be taking this
one trade here going
down and what you can I you can play
either side of the market at this point
because
now when you get in here you know it's
just a quick Scout when you get in here
you know it's just a quick Scout when
you get in here you know it's just a
quick Scout and before you know
it you can get all the way down
here and these little scalps gave you
way more Pips way more money because
these these little scalps here can be
high lot siiz scalps you're already in
profit coming down so at any point that
you
are an extra profit you could leverage
that extra profit also with just a
higher lot size to scalp up real quick
so this might be coming down on like a
one lot where it's it's $10 sorry or or
$1 per pip let's say it's coming down $1
per pip and you're already here let's
say I don't know uh
uh you're $200 in the positive
here now when you're catching these
little scalps up you might be able to do
$10 per pip
here take a quick 10 20 Pips 200 bucks
there and you're still
$200 coming down but you just made 200
bucks on a quick Scout another 200 bucks
on a quick Scout another 200 bucks on a
quick Scout another 200 bucks on a quick
Skype wow this right here is just making
its way
downtown and still reaffirming that we
have been coming down from this
area and we are still in profit and this
profit that we are in we are head
hedging against it to get little scalps
within these areas we're hedging against
the profit that we're incoming down and
it can make it all the more profitable
while you're trading or what you can do
is just find areas that price comes back
up to to continue to compound going down
that's another way that you could manage
your
risk but it would just be a appropriate
to the numbers that are in your account
and obviously you would not get greedy
you know you're not going to be $200 in
profit and now you know you're doing
$100 per pip you know you out in two
Pips you know or your profit is blown in
two Pips it starts to go the other way
so this is one way to have this just
coming from this area from and this is
usually a higher time frame area let me
say that you find this trade this one
trade that's usually trending in a
particular area it's usually from a
higher time frame
rejection and it's heading down or back
down to some sort of imbalance or snd
that's below so that one trade is when
you usually see the larger structural
bearish or bullish trip bullish flip
sorry bearish or bullish flip you see
the larger struct Cal one and then you
take price down and you're anticipating
with each pullback either you could play
a quick scalp going up or you can play
adding another entry in going down after
it Taps into whatever imbalance that may
be here whatever snd that may be here
Taps into there then you just add in
another order to continue and the profit
from this order here is now allowing you
to put in a second order directly below
it even if this does come into a little
draw down you're still in profit from
this order here so it's only cutting
back into some of the profit from the
previous area but you're in no draw down
you're still in profit with both trades
but this can only come from
understanding Market structure though
these snd zones are not not snd zones
that are responsible for structural
breaks these snd zones often times let
me move this down a little bit these snd
D zones often times
uh these snd D zones often times serve
I'm talking about the you see the the
down move before price shifts
up the Zone that's left behind the high
and the low that's left behind when
price moves out of the
area the high and the low that's left
behind when price shifts above this
area price can come back into it
sometimes and then leave but there are
times where price like this doesn't go
back to it and continues to Trend
up this is an unmitigated area now if
this area here is not
responsible
for let's
see
right here so we have we have this high
right
here we have this
High let me move this down a little
bit
[Music]
we have this High
created we still have some area that
price fell from down
there so we're looking
for the area
responsible for flipping us above the
structural high right here we're looking
for that area responsible somewhere down
here for shifting us above this because
that particular area is where we are
going to tap
into and then take another leg up
that's the bullish area that price is
looking to make its way back
to so bear with me it's all going to
come together in a
few it's going to come together when we
when we get to the charts I'm going to
show you guys
this know it feels like a college
lecture but you know just bear with me
so this area here here is not
responsible for anything this area down
here is
responsible but when price comes to this
area here price still gives you a
reaction to go
up but that reaction that you're getting
from here to go up is just a retracement
to go to a particular area and tap into
that area above to come back down
below the
area that price tapped
into so you have
people trying to
buy
buy buy buy they continue to do that
over and over and over again rather than
understanding that it's
by to
sell to
buy to
sell to buy that's how the market
moves the market moves like that and you
can
time each and every one of those Taps
you can time them they may not be
entirely perfect but you can time them
and create a system around it so as we
have this trend going
down we have now mind you this is the
higher time frame area that we tapped
into so if we rejected from a higher
time frame we know that it's a heavy
rejection from somewhere up here and
we're coming back to something down
here because it's rejecting from Supply
on the higher time frame to demand
somewhere down
here so on the higher time frame we
understand that that's where price is
targeting but on the lower time frame we
see price trending this
way and we're looking for areas to get
involved in
price and there are areas that you can
get
involved where you don't have to utilize
the current
Trend or you can utilize the current
Trend it just depends on how you see the
market you utilize the current Trend
you're going to get
more more value for your
trade you're catching an area or tapping
into an area to break structure to the
downside so you get a discounted move
and and then
some you at least get two times what you
were
expecting either the the the break of
the structural low is one and then it
could cross other structures below if
there are no bullish areas that pric is
tapping
into but remember since this is a bias
from the higher time
frame all of these moves up we know that
are just temporary retracements until we
might see on the higher time frame that
oh maybe there was an imbalance within
here on the higher time frame and then
it sent price up to here maybe we
miscalculated on
that you know or it would just continue
to the overall targets sometimes it's
just based on what people have charted
out there there are people who have
certain um demand zones charted out
certain Supply zones charted out and
they miss the tiniest imbalance that's
there and price actually Taps that and
goes
away because they didn't have it charted
out when you have these things charted
out it's giving you an explanation for
everything that price reacted off of and
why price retraced where price retraced
to and where price continued down to
when you see that over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over and over and over again
like
you begin to become confident in playing
different sides of the market only
relative to that
rule that you have on whatever side of
the market it is that you're looking to
get involved in so I'm going to take you
guys to the charts now and show you guys
exactly how this plays out on the charts
let's see let's find a
[Music]
trend I want to find a clean Trend so
it's
um just easier to give an
explanation
to and
um yeah let
me because there's different ways to
play this it's just that I'm introducing
this to you
guys and you have to be able
to play the foundation of it first
and
then you can kind of add your own thing
into
it
um so let's
see try to see let me see if I could
find a pair that be
swanging
yeah let me see if I can find a pair
that's
uh it's giving us some nice
swings I think oil had some nice swings
today uh nope it did
not you can you got you guys probably
see me scrolling around looking for a
particular area and thinking oh well
maybe this doesn't happen everywhere it
does happen everywhere I'm just trying
to find a cleaner area to to show you
guys how it plays out so you're not um
struggling with the basic understanding
of it let me maybe go to the 15 minute
um because those moves tend to be
clean um okay right here oh look look we
have do we
okay so we talked about swing
Point
within certain
Trends
um there are swing points within swing
points within swing
points
so you know you
have
this here you go up
break structure to the
downside
this this last move here the swing up to
where price broke structure to the
downside this is the last swing
point that price had then
price goes break structure to the
upside price comes down to this area
here and then price pushes up
to here price comes down to this area
here and then price pushes up to here
price comes to this area here up to here
so you guys get the understanding you
see how none of the Swing points really
do not look the
same you know they really don't look the
same in terms of there was some sideways
movement within this whole swing Point
here probably shifted
up then there's you know movement down
into this area tapped in and then price
shifted up so what we
also don't
see or or maybe don't even uh consider
as we're looking at those swing
points is that within this area
here there are
also swing points happening
also swing
points just
smaller
so we
have we have this here
we have this here on the inside these
swing points on the inside along with
these swing
points on the
outside these are
institutional swing
points when these swing points are
violated that's when the uptrend is
getting ready to
shift and assume a downtrend so you
would have a violation of this
structural institutional
LW you'll have price retrace into the
area and then you'll have a short out of
it and that would be the beginning of a
new trend the beginning of a
downtrend and you can spot that on your
own
by just keeping track of these pivot
Points but there's the inside
structure pivot Points and then there's
also the outside structure pivot Points
and a lot of this is
explained here in this video you know so
I'm just giving you guys a piece of that
but what I'm going to show you guys
is with utilizing what I'm showing you
you need to know structure you need to
know how to utilize swing points that's
imperative that you know that so with
institutional swing
points along with smaller time frame or
or smaller structure swing
points often times
price will go above a particular
swing come back to it and trade
higher and because you have small swings
large swings you want to know within
those
swings within this swing
here you have price break above
here there are multiple areas
that you see price can price can reverse
and come in touch here you might have
this area marked out you might have this
area marked out and there's so
many wha
ifs about price tapping into these
areas
so what we mentioned was
that this is yes a smaller swing point
but also a demand Zone that's
responsible for breaking structure to
the top side breaking this structure
here so you're looking to trade from
here not here not here you're looking to
trade from the area responsible for a
breaking structure now what I will say
about utilizing that area responsible
for breaking structure is that often
times when prices has shift
bearish already from somewhere up
here that doesn't
hold and price continues going down we
might have already tapped into an snd
above but we're looking to come back to
this here to go bullish without paying
attention to what just happened at the
higher time frame up
here so we get
confused as to why it didn't work out
and why price came further down here
maybe and then maybe came up here and
then down here and maybe came up here
and then down here and we're trying to
figure out why this didn't hold or sorry
why this didn't
hold and it's
because you may have missed something
from the supply area from the top area
we might be getting rejected from an
imbalance from a Zone you know that's
above there there's there's plenty of
explanations as to why price would shift
through there but you would also know
that since that was the last area that
price could hit and put in a new high if
it goes below that area then consider
the rest of the area lunch me and that
gives you a bias that price is often
going to shift through these areas so
with these areas here you see how price
never came down and touch these areas
with these areas here
if price ends up coming down to maybe
mitigate this area below sorry this area
below here if price comes down to
mitigate this area below right here I
don't know let me let me
just okay yeah right here let's say
price comes down to mitigate this area
below you're going
to see that you'll get a reaction from
each one of
these even if they're even even if
they're
unmitigated even if they're unmitigated
you'll get a reaction out of each and
every one of these or not each and every
one most of them you'll get a reaction
up out of most of them like
that like
that
even though this was responsible for the
structural
shift we already tapped into it and went
so if you have price coming back below
this
area then we're shorting through the
area but we also have long opportunities
that are present from here quick scalp
up here quick scalp up here quick scalp
up here quick scalp up while you're in
one trade coming down here
so now you have one trade dropping and
then you have quick scalp up to trade
down quick scalp up to trade down quick
scalp up to trade down so now you're
understanding how the trend is
forming
so with this let me
actually go back to the us3 now for the
the overall
explanation this right here is a swing
point this
high and this low swing Point price
trades above price doesn't come back
into it this leaves an unmitigated area
when price comes back to the area
usually trading down we're looking to
tap into the
50% of that area and potentially get a
move to take us
up so let me actually
see I didn't even pay
attention so you see right
here we tapped into the area you see the
middle right here where this crossair is
we tapped into this
area and we pushed
higher
so now that that you guys get an idea of
Swing points swing points can be
utilized as some form of directional
bias and
reversal and I say that because look it
take for since this swing Point
here price trades out of
it comes back into this area back into
the swing Point price Taps the 50% of
the Swing
Point
here and keeps
going but not just that if you happen to
miss the larger swing point there are
smaller swing points that are in here
that build the
trend so now you have this area here
this tiny swing Point remember we just
missed this larger move but now we
looking for continuations so what do we
have this tiny swing Point
here price
comes Taps into it and it
leaves we we
see this swing Point here do we get
anything from
this
no there's another swing Point directly
above here but price ends up trading
through it but still continuing above so
what do we have now this swing Point
here this high and this
low
now we place a square over the swing
point when price trades above the swing
point above this swing point
this this
move this move went up to here traded
down below to here when price trades
above this area above
this above this high
you're looking for price to come back
into the
50% of this previous swing point that we
just traded above we just traded out of
you're taking the area of the previous
swing point you place a square around it
price comes back into the area of the
Swing point we tap right into the middle
of it and we you trade
higher you have another swing point that
price creates
here we didn't get price coming back
into it we had this where price came
down and went back up but what do we do
now we
FIB I mean sorry we we take this swing
Point here because this is also a swing
point this one down candle into this up
move this is a swing Point too just on a
lower time frame so what do we have
price Taps
into the center of this swing Point
takes you
up but then price also Taps into the
center of this swing point and takes you
up actually it goes a little further
into the swing Point down below to here
and ends up taking you all the way up
here but the same way that you can trade
swing points as the trend is going up
you can trade swing points as the trend
is going
down
so here you have it this is the last
swing point I don't even know if it it
actually tapped but this is the last
swing point this up move and price
shifted down out of
it when price shifted down below it it
came back into the
area 50% of the Swing point you see
clean tap 50% of it the larger swing
point this here the larger swing point
this previous swing point it comes back
into 50% of it and then it shifts down
it leaves so often times you have it to
where there's large swing points there's
smaller swing points and price even
responds to the smaller swing point
because now look at this this is a
larger swing Point here exactly at this
area if you were to take the
50% of this larger swing point
and find the swing Point within it or
maybe the imbalance that could be up
here or
something you would end up
pinpointing the exact area that price is
coming to tap into and you may be able
to short using that
area with the overall bias that we were
coming back up to the 50% of this swing
point so now your bias is that we're
coming at back to the 50% of the Swing
point but we find we found a smaller
area in there within the 50% or
above that we can refine price to refine
our entry to so we took the swing point
that was within the larger swing point
and we got a tap into it and price
traded below so what you guys need to
understand with these swing points is
that the larger swing points are more
likely the smaller swing points are
easier to break through and what most
people don't get is that these swing
points up here these swing points that
you guys see me marking they're just
Supply zones they're order blocks from
the higher time
frame
right here let me see maybe the
[Music]
2hour this is one 2hour
candle or even a
fractal so you see this is a fractal
from the
2hour time
frame but when you go lower it opens up
to other things so this is why I'm
saying utilize fractals as zones as well
because fractals are Supply areas swing
points are Supply areas left behind so
you have this swing Point
here price trades up into it yeah
there's a little bit of draw down
sometimes depending on where you brought
it where you drew it so this from this
low I'm telling you to learn how to draw
from the low to the high and then when
price trades below it you're looking for
price to come back into the 50% of That
Swing that's what I'm telling you guys
because you need to First be able to
understand how this works but my actual
swing point when you start understanding
swing points my actual swing point would
have just been the low of this candle
here to the high of this candle
here and I would have got a cleaner top
less drop down but price Taps into the
area and it trades
below so with these swing points you
could utilize these swing points as
directional bias from the higher time
frames you could utilize them as
directional bias so now that we have
this swing Point here
created now when price begins to Short
if we're going to continue higher we
need to find the reversal in the middle
of this previous swing Point
here
sorry
here so
now when we're
shorting we have a
direction on where price is going to but
we also have an area from this 50% % of
where price where we can potentially
narrow down price doing something in
here so now that we have the 50% we know
that we're looking for price to come and
tap into anything below this the 50% so
now when we open up the 50% and we look
what do we see we see the snd here
responsible for breaking structure here
so now likely area 50% of our swing this
within here is the snd responsible for
breaking the structure up here we also
have an imbalance here as well multiple
imbalances below which makes this area
likely for price to come down and
mitigate as well imbalance just below it
mitigated also so we're not necessarily
looking for price to come below this
area but we found this
area from
our swing point the
50% and refined within the 50% of That
Swing
point the area that's responsible for
breaking
structure so now this becomes the area
we're looking for but one would ask we
have a bunch of imbalances how do we
know price won't tap into any of these
areas it's a great question
price can tap into these areas but guess
what these areas would overall end up
being it would end up being a reaction
at this imbalance a reaction at this
imbalance a reaction at this imbalance a
reaction at this imbalance until we get
to the targeted area and then we reverse
from
here so now as pric is Shifting back
down to our swing point
because the larger swing points are the
likely swing points that price will come
tap into in Reverse now as price is
Shifting back down to
this you'll
see that you will have multiple
opportunities to scal this and balance
up scal this and balance up scal this
and balance up scalp this imbalance up
maybe scalp this fractal up scalp this
snd up because we know overall we're in
our one trade coming back down to here
but we know all of the likely
reactionary areas that are here for
price to give us a nice quick pump
up we're scalping off of
that as we're coming to our likely area
for the reversal so this would get rid
of that mindset that you guys are
expecting us to
reverse from here and maybe reverse from
here and maybe reverse from here and
maybe reverse from here and maybe
reverse from here and maybe reverse from
here we're not expecting reversals no
longer through here we're expecting
scalps up but not only do we get our
scalps up as we're coming
down we
get the rejection from here
to here from here to here from here to
here from here to here from here to here
so any side of the market that you want
to play
on whether it's a scalp up or a
continuation down you see it all
happening and the areas that it happens
in is the zones that you're looking to
to trade from but the those are only
reactionary
zones the actual Zone that you're
looking to reverse from is just one area
and any other area that's along here
you're only looking for a quick Scout
but what I will say is that with the
imbalances price can often come directly
to this imbalance right here above never
tap into this snd Zone down here never
tap
sorry price can never tap into this here
but it can tap right into this
imbalance just above it and then
continue to put in another high and
smart money and all these people are
waiting for this old juicy order block
to come yeah oh hit that area imbalance
gets tapped and it
goes that's where the IM balances become
game game changers for you and this is
why I mentioned that areas that are
likely because price broke structure
from that area choose the imbalance
that's there because it could reverse at
the imbalance and not the snd and
sometimes it will reverse at the snd but
there are times where it will not go
back to that snd it would just hit the
imbalance directly look like look it did
it right here
sorry look at this right here this area
here was responsible for breaking
structure here price came and tapped
this imbalance and continued up and all
these other people who who love to play
order blocks and all that other stuff
never got a
tap never got a tap into it oh we
waiting for price to tap into the demand
area never ta there what did it hit the
imbalance directly
above so we want to look to get involved
on most of these moves as they can turn
into just a quick Scout for you and
often times never come back down here
and end up being a longer move that
you're taking up so you want to get used
to understand the reactions that are in
these areas and how to capitalize on
them and because they are
reactions that that are um uh uh because
these these reactions are are uh uh you
know like you're you're kind of playing
them in terms of of when they tap in and
they
go you can capitalize on each and every
one of those being precise with your
risk management so if you tap into the
50% of this area because it's a likely
area you may be able to risk a little
more on it risk 10% 15% on it because
you see that these reactions off of
these areas tend to be very very sure
and very very powerful but with the
imbalances what I will say is that with
the imbalances on the higher time frames
price tends to go a little more than the
50% with a lot of these imbalances so
sometimes price goes 61 68 you know like
within that area 70% even and then
continue up so you have to be able to
brace yourself for some of the draw down
that you could be in if there's any
you have to brace yourself for some of
that draw down and that's where risk
management is important because charting
is not the only thing that that's
important in profitability risk
management is actually the thing that
creates profitability because you you
create some sort of system within your
scalping that you're able to take
certain calculated risk and you're able
to make you know small portions of money
let me see I end up holding uh end up
holding a lot of my scalps too long and
it retraces on me yeah that that's true
how how do you decide to hold for larger
moves versus it's just a scalp um like
what changed your bias from a scalp to a
longer move what changes my bias from a
scalp to a longer move is a structural
break because let's say let's say this
turned into a scalp here like this was
my scalp here my quick scalp up you know
price trades up
here price comes back into this area you
know I'm I'm in from down here so I
don't really care what's going on here
but as price continues to go and you
start to see structure breaking sorry
you start to see structure breaking to
the top side you're not getting out of
this because you know at the end of the
day price is only coming back to this
swing
point
and price will tap into the swing point
and then take you higher which this is
exactly what it did you guys see
this this candle this green candle with
this Wick sent us above the swing
point this green
candle when we closed we came back into
the 50% of the Swing
Point tapped in
and we
left so if this is a bullish Trend
that's trending it's only coming back to
particular areas tap into it and go
because we already broke structure up
here once we broke structure up here and
you got in here your stops are at break
even here but you are expecting some
retracement back into the area after the
structural break so a lot of the times
you might be getting
in you might be scalping from here and
price goes
up and then when it goes up above this
structural High it comes back into the
area and takes you out at break
even and then it ends up going above to
wherever it is that that you thought it
was going
to and a lot of the times that's because
not understanding where you are
structurally and this is why I continue
to talk about the like under
understanding structure is very very
important Candlestick structure
intermediary structure institutional
structure and utilizing all of it uh
what would be the confirmation to get
into a tap of the imbalance and not wait
for liquidity to get to the ob
um the requirement to get in on the the
top of this imbalance is
that if
price TAPS in let me let me show you if
price Taps into this imbalance and
shifts above the
area you want to see price come back
into this area that's above the
imbalance tap here you want to see it
come back into the the 50% of the area
this is a swing here this one
candle this one candle is a swing swing
on Candlestick structure so this candle
actually created the well the imbalance
actually created the swing because price
shifted down tapped the imbalance and
then swung it up so this imbalance
created a swing and all we did was take
that
swing and when price trades above it
we're expecting price to come back into
it which that's exactly what it did here
if you guys look tapped right back into
the center of this one candle because
this one candle is the swing came out of
the Swing tapped back into it
here and then traded
higher
so so this is why understanding the
different types of
structure can help you to get into
trades before you know smart money is
waiting down here for their little order
block Taps ICT Bros are waiting here to
get into an entry and they can't and
they go oh ICT doesn't work you know or
this doesn't work and that doesn't work
and a lot of the times they just don't
really understand you know like like how
price moves how how the algorithm moves
and they end up getting caught out there
like this you know so um you can utilize
swing points but not just that
not just that
guys swing points work on higher time
frames so this is the one-h hour time
frame if I take this swing low to this
swing
High when price traded below it we had
price try to come back up and trade it
down but we had this area still
mitigated from the one hour so if we
wanted to catch a high higher time frame
reversal we would have chosen a higher
time frame swing point and not just that
remember with the higher time frame
swing points what we're looking to do is
get in at the 50% and our stops are
behind here but this is a lot of risk so
what I do is I take the 50% of the Swing
point and I look for a possible area
within this 50%
that price could potentially tap into
and give me some reaction so guess what
that
becomes imbalance imbalance imbalance
imbalance imbalance there's always
imbalances Within These swing
points and since imbalances give you the
stronger Taps out of the area you find
the imbalance that's likely to react
react from the swing
point I hope I'm not losing anybody here
so now you take this imbalance and now
the imbalance becomes your entry and the
50%
becomes the where you're where you're
entering and your risk is directly
behind the
zone why not choose the imbalance above
that one the imbalance above this one
this is a swing point I'm looking for
price to tap into the 50% of the Swing
point or
above but if you look within
here there's no
sorry there's no volume up
here remember how we say price is
attracted to
volume there's no volume up here this is
price going straight up to immediately
pushing straight down and it left an
imbalance there's no volume in this top
area where were we consolidating up
here there's no consolidation here so
cons consolidation is important because
when that area comes back to be
tested then you usually get a reaction
out of the area so we consolidate up
here within this swing point right here
we consolidate within here and then we
get a tap into the area and we short
from the Consolidated area from the area
that has volume so we're choosing this
imbalance here knowing that up here
there's no volume there and most people
are using these volume indicators and
they're like oh if price goes I don't
know let let me see if I could find that
volume indicator that people are using
right now it's like a a huge Trend um
uh that that people are using
um it's like uh
uh I don't even know how they how they
would they would capture this maybe it's
the last swing or something like
that let me
see maybe it's here who knows yeah I
don't know I don't I don't see well the
volume indicator is showing that the
volume is here
so people are utilizing this volume
indicator with these
swings to find out where the volume is
and where price potentially May react
from when you can already see the volume
with your own
eye you can see the volume with your own
eyes because the imbalance chosen is in
the 50% area yeah exactly that's why the
the imbalance that I chose is at the
50% where usually looking for price to
react at the 50% sometimes price can go
a little further up within it but we're
looking more so for price to react at
the 50% so we take the area at that 50%
and utilize that as the most likely area
for price to reverse from and that's
just on the swing
point so usually you want to make sure
that within that area there's also some
volume there because we know that price
is attracted to volume and now you no
longer have to use this little volume
indicator to tell you where volume is or
you know there are people who are like
creating strategies off of it where you
know they're like if price goes above it
and once it comes back below it you get
into a short I have no idea what what
any of that stuff is and and how
beneficial any of those things are like
there there's I would never endorse that
at all because what what's the structure
behind that you know like what like they
would have it go up above here and they
would place a sell stop right below here
and they would wait for price to tap
them in and take them down below
here and you know they they would take
that momentum entry below this volume
part whatever this is called cuz I don't
use this indicator so I don't know like
where the most volume is they'll
take the entry here when it comes below
that area so I've I've been seeing
people utilize this to trade with but I
still think that you can find the volume
just using your eyes you don't
necessarily need to um use an indicator
to help you spot that because you can
already see the volume just in the
clustered areas the areas that are
Consolidated that's the volume areas uh
Crystal Clear that's great uh this is
what many Traders would
call buy to sell candle or sell to buy
candle um or institutional candle 50% of
that last candle that caused the break I
back tested this on trading view at the
second top of the 50% you barely get
caught in draw down exactly yeah you
barely get caught in draw down
barely you know because of taing into
that that area but then you also have to
know that sometimes those areas are not
touched like the the the smaller swing
points we try to choose the small the
smallest swing points for for price to
react off of let let's say we chose this
swing Point down here right
here right here we had price go above it
so if you put your stop directly above
the swing swing point you would have
just been taken out and then we had a
reaction
down you know but this swing Point
wasn't a swing point that gave you a
clean rejection and took you down so if
you utilize the wrong swing points as
well often times you could end up
becoming you know mixed meat and you
want to utilize the swing points that
are in areas that have volume to it
areas that have volume to it you want to
use those swing points so with this
swing point we wouldn't necessarily be
using this
here but we would also look to maybe
spot something above like an imbalance
or fractal or or something above here so
I think this is a fractal tap here which
also is this um snd here this hidden snd
back here right
here
yeah it's hitting snd here so price
usually Taps into it rejects out of it
let's let me just move this price
and then liquidates it so it looks like
let me
[Music]
see
oh it didn't even liquidate
it it came really close and then shifted
down yeah it didn't even liquidate
it actually I'm wondering oh no no no no
no this wait is this no I'm tripping
it's not thinking this was the news the
other
day on uh on June
28th because we had that huge pushup
followed by that push down
um oh no this is news
right yeah this was news or something
like
that we were talking about this this
area and then probably shift it down for
the rest of the
day yeah yeah that was news that was
news oh no it was this I'm sorry I'm
lying look at me over here telling the
truth about the go to
hell I'm kidding so yeah the the swing
points um let me see after I stop us
indicator I feel more secure off my
trades yeah and if you utilize these
swing points as areas to scalp you could
certainly just you know impact your
trading um in terms of like scalping
those 10 20 Pips make 10 Pips your hard
partial or 20 Pips you're hard partial
so it creates this discipline that
you're out intend 10 out and 10 out and
10 out and 10 out and 10 so for every
trade that you take now with us30 it's
going to be more than 10 Pips with those
reactions because we see how heavy those
are but it'll just be out in 10 out and
10 out and 10 or partial at 20 partial
at 20 partial at 20 partial at 20 and
when you get used to it then you'll see
that okay now I could up my risk a
little more now I could hold a little
more and as I'm holding a little more
I'm able ble to be confident in my trade
and maybe add in a second position or
maybe take a scalp from this area back
down but I know we're not going all the
way down we're just retracing to here
and I could stay in this trade right
here and head back up you can only spot
those things and understand those things
when you are using structure so I'm
teaching you guys about these swing
points but I also want you guys to
understand that that with these swing
points you need to know structure so
this area we tapped into this area I
think this area was like called out on
stream or something like that or right
before stream we tapped into this area
and I had mentioned that we were coming
down here what did I see down here when
we came down this tiny swing point from
across the
way and if you look within this larger
Point
here price traded above it came back and
mitigated it and then traded
higher but we have an area below a
demand area that was created below that
went untested went
unmitigated so we had news happen that
took us all the way down here to tap
into our area our
swing the last swing before price
shifted to the top side why is this
swing important also yes we got a tap at
the middle of this swing and we got
pushed up but this swing is way more
important why because this is the snd
that broke structure to the top
side so regardless of the Swing we still
have to come back to mitigate the snd
responsible for breaking structure to
the top side
and often times those little tiny
mitigated areas that are left behind are
usually areas that the news trades to
and bounces off of heavy and most people
just are not aware of the little areas
that are here that are left behind and
not knowing how they potentially are
used so most people might have been
jumping into a sell to come below here
but this is a swing that was responsible
for breaking structure the swing was
responsible for breaking structure the
swing was responsible for breaking
structure so we came back to the swing
that was responsible for breaking
structure last mitigated last area that
needed to be
mitigated before we assume trading
higher and that's why we tapped into
this area here and went bullish so guess
what
what areas are we potentially looking
into to go long from and in the event
that there's chaotic news or anything
like that that happens but the market is
not shifting barish guess where our next
high impact news event will take
us snd left behind that was responsible
for the struggle stru will break
above and after Biden crashes the stock
market you know like everybody says
these
days then you start to see some normaly
heading back up it's like yeah we're
rallying again oh my God we're doing
great and they just don't understand how
structure
works so that's me teaching with swing
points it goes even more in depth with
these swing points by the way guys
um because there are ways to know which
swing points will get liquidated
entirely so often times price has one
swing Point here and it leaves another
swing point above
here and if it fails to make a third
swing point up here
a lot of the times you'll have price
come tap back into this
area give you your pump up but we failed
to make the other high and when we
failed to make the other high we're just
liquidating the second swing point that
formed to take us back to the first
swing
point and then the first swing
point is
where we end up actually going long to
put in more
Highs but since a lot of people don't
understand how all of this kind of works
together um they're usually tripped up
in these swings you know trying to find
the bullish area trying to find the
bearish area trying to find a trend and
this and that and and if you just
understand how these areas are
utilized most people think that you take
the high here I mean the low here to you
know the high here maybe
and you're looking to maybe come back
into sorry not the main this is actually
let me just move all of
this so they go
here and they'll take this
here sorry default and they're looking
for price to come back to this
area
here and
there's this swing
here and within this
swing
there's this swing
here but being that we understood that
this this fractal right
here mitigated
this what you may end up getting is
price coming to tap this fractal because
now this fractal becomes the demand Zone
the the area that's responsible for
mitigating the demand Zone becomes the
new demand zone so this becomes the new
unmitigated demand Zone and within this
swing here we have two areas we have
this area here
that's responsible for the structural
break
here and then we also have this area
here that's responsible
for even this you know this structural
break this multiple structural
breaks so if price ends up coming back
down it can tap into this area not even
go back to this or even tap into the
middle of this
and then assume to put in a new high
because this is the last unmitigated
area specifically this fractal being the
last unmitigated area for price to
continue to trade
higher because we broke this structure
we came down and mitigated it we broke
this structure we did not mitigate it so
this is still outstanding right here but
we can potentially have a tap back into
this area but then we could also take
the low of that area tap deeper into the
area and then actually take the high out
of there but this is just essentially
showing you guys areas on how to spot
reversals how to spot reversals in real
time utilizing swing points so now these
be you you leave out Wicks when defining
swing zones only Wicks that go below um
below a particular low so if you look at
this uh this Wick right no is
it wait let me turn
this no it's
not so it's it's only Wicks like this
right
here you see this swing Point
here this swing point from from
this this Wick here to this Wick here so
what I've found um and you guys might
find different results for you or
different things that you might see
quicker and and may understand a little
better um but what I've found is
remember how I said there's the
liquidity grab candle where price you
know goes below a certain low and then
shifts above
it and it continues
up so this candle
I say we discount the Wix because it
traded below the previous low here both
here and
here it traded below it but then it
closed back inside of the range of that
candle so because we traded below it and
closed back within the range of that
candle this Wick is considered
manipulation so I'm not using the wick
because that's that's a manipulated move
it was a manipulated move down before
price went up they're not looking to
come back to this move this move shook
people out of the
market and it push back up they're not
looking to come back to the Move That
Shook people out of the market because
that would bring them back to break even
and what profitability is that so the
reason why I discount that is because of
often times when we come back into the
area after trading above we actually tap
into the only the 50% without the wick
and price trades
above so we're not counting this because
this is a liquidity grab if we counted
this with structure then we missed the
move and we would continue to miss moves
and then when price comes back to this
area we try to catch the move here and
it just rails through the
area because we missed the actual move
when the actual move was
here and it was this fractal that
mitigated this area this swing a fractal
is a
swing this
fractal right
here was the swing that mitigated the
area and left so now that makes this
fractal a likely fractal to have a
reaction
on you guys understand you know what
what I'm saying you know I hope I'm not
losing anybody I know it's it's you know
a lot of talking I've been doing a lot
of explaining but this is how you can
find likely areas I got lost on a
fractal um so in in this in this um
frequently act section here um there's
uh some some explanation of fractals
what are fract
it's a super quick easy explanation um
it's about one minute long um and it
would kind of catch you up to speed on
that but the fractal is a swing Point
too it's a down move you see it started
at this
Wick a fractal is a swing point on a
lower time frame a lower time frame so
it's this here this high after this high
was put in we short it and put in this
low and then we left the area so this
becomes the area Left Behind for price
to come and tap into because this area
that was left behind mitigated a
previous
area so this becomes the new area for
you guys to trade
from and that becomes the new demand
area below so if we're look to give us
another like like kick up another leg up
or or a sizable reaction up we'll get
one here because this is still
responsible for the structural break
here so there can be multiple ones
that's responsible for different
structural
breaks because this is a structure
here this is a intermediary structure
this is a institutional
structure this is another type of
institutional structure from a higher
time frame this is another type of
time frame so that's why with every
swing that we have down and back up
price comes back to tap into it and goes
back
up because we're breaking multiple
structures but we're also returning to
those areas that are responsible for
those different types of structures
being
broken and that's why we have
Candlestick structure out to
intermediary structure out to you know
overall a major structure out to
institutional structure it all just you
know vibrates out what time frame do you
prefer uh swing points um use the 15 if
you're day trading use a 15 swing
point if you're day trading just just
take a 15
swing and and use that as an area that
you could potentially get a reaction
point from you know but the truth is on
the one minute you could still find
pretty good swings on the one
minute where are we
um over
here so this was coming up
so look at right
here this is how I spotted this trade oh
I'm going to lose all of my stuff I just
realized I didn't go back to add this
stuff on the chart but it's cool this is
a swing Point
here it's a swing Point here price comes
and Taps into it but
but look within here and this is how I
modify some of my swing points to get a
more accurate move this is Candlestick
structure
now you have this High you have this low
you have this
High you have this low you have this
High you have this
low you have this
low
you have this High put
in what are we seeing over here well
this would I really count this as a low
I don't
know no I don't think I
would all right so let's say it's this
this is so ugly let me actually
just there you go better so we have this
swing that's left behind right
here we said it was what this High
here no it was down
up down up down so it was this we have
this swing here price shifted down and
broke up above it right
here let me move this out the way now
shift the down broke up above
it right
here so I'm using Candlestick structure
to spot a swing in Candlestick
structure to take for a move
up so what I'm actually doing
is I see this larger swing
here and I could use this larger swing
as a guide for you know like price
coming down to at least the 50% so
that's at least right
here and within this area of the
50% I'm looking for an area that price
could potentially react
from so I
have I could actually use this snd here
this one candle
here price comes Taps into the 50% of
this snd
here and trades higher now that's when
you know Candlestick structure so I'm
going to do I'm going to come back and
do another teaching on using the
Candlestick swing points but you guys
need to be you know you guys need to
consider that if you take these swing
points they'll give you some sort of
directional bias so with this swing
Point here this swing down followed by
this move up I caught this move because
I saw this 50% of this swing point but
guess what within the 50% of the Swing
point if anybody knows the way I trade
they would see that I'm always telling
people about imbalances we have an
imbalance smack dab in the middle of the
50% of the Swing
Point what better IM balance to use than
that we got our scalp off of it right
here scalp up off of it we got our
double bottom for the second touch and
then we
longed to where we went today and this
is utilizing the swingo from Market
open so you can't you can't ask
questions like you know which swing
point should I use which swing Point
shouldn't I use which swing point is
likely which you got a back test it and
see how the swing points
react back test the large swing
points and the small swing points within
the large swing points so this is the
down move right here this that I
just this is the down
move
structurally sorry I don't know why this
isn't cing this is the down move
structurally and then we shift it up but
the real down move the real down move
within this this area this schematic is
actually from this high here to this
low this is the real down move that sent
price
up so you're using the larger swing for
direction for possible areas to spot
your reversals and then you're using the
inside of that area to lower your
risk now you have a double confirmation
already within this area this is
unmitigated this whole thing is
unmitigated here too and there's some
imbalance within here or whatever it is
that could be here that has not been
tapped into when price gets down to this
area
you often see a reaction out of it but
it doesn't mean that it has to be a
reaction that breaks the
high it can just be a reaction back up
to tap into some area up here because we
could have hit a supply area up here and
we know nothing about
that so this is why understanding where
you are in structure is important too
you know so I I hope you guys got
something out of that you know I that's
how I started trading and um you know I
have mentioned to you guys actually
where uh is it I had mentioned to you
guys um you know when when I
first where is it let me see if I could
find
it I'm trying to get a bear with me guys
is right
here when I first started trading this
and understanding this these were my
trades and if you look some of them
didn't get tapped into this didn't get
tapped this didn't get tapped this
didn't get tapped here but look at all
of
this and I told people you don't need
the left side to trade you only need the
right if it's trending
if we got a structural shift you only
need the right side and look I'm trading
up and down on this right
side up and down I'm counter Trend
trading trading with the
trend up up up up down up down up here
up here down here all like back and
forth
everywhere because I understood how PR
moved and you know now you guys kind of
get an idea of I was using swing
points and if you use that on those days
where we have those nice rocking
pullbacks use those swing points and
you'll see that you could you know get
quite a quite a bit of Trades you can
get involved in quite a bit of Trades if
you're if you're just utilizing swing
points I I usually go just like this on
stream and nobody knows what I'm doing
but I go just like
this you know and I I'll place that
there and most people have no idea and
then there's like a little tiny swing
Point within
here and I go okay but this Wick came
down and came back in so now we have it
there so we rule this area out and we
have this area if price does come below
but then we
see this one candle here is a swing
Point that's
unmitigated so we use that zone
there and then we have a larger swing
Point
here at this
area and this is where
we kind of look at what price may do
when it comes back to the area and it
could potentially reject from these
areas back down and you're only
utilizing what's on your right side not
on your
left and and in in um in times of of
like high
volume a rejection like this this is
like two Pips right now rejection like
this can be a lot more it could be like
four 30 40 Pips from a rejection like
this and who's to say you can't scalp
that real quick scalping maybe from here
maybe to the imbalance here which is
like 30 Pips in the in the New York
session and from this imbalance back up
to take this High here and then from
this area here because this is a swing
point and we know price comes and Taps
into the swing points and rejects out
maybe back to some imbalance
here and then from whatever imbalance or
from whatever Zone to maybe take the
highs because these are mitigated
already so if price trades above this
area these are previously mitigated
areas so we know we would be assuming
the high and that's how you create the
narrative around utilizing these swing
points as look at this look at this
rejection guys swing
Point that's what I'm saying like I I
try to stress to people watch what I'm
talking about like watch the videos that
I'm teaching with because I'm saying
things over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and it's
right in front of people and a lot of
the times they miss it because these
little things that they're just not
noticing this is right in front of us
this rejection right here would have
been a 30 40 pip rejection in the New
York session I just placed that line
there and said we get we could get
rejected
there and then guess what we could let
let's say we get rejected here let's say
we come here we tap here let's say we
come back to this imbalance
we come back up here reject out of here
come back to some area here let's say we
take the high here we assume up guess
what come back down to
here maybe some imbalance here maybe the
imbalance directly above and
continue and we are noticing the
areas that are forming the
trend forming so let's say we got a
rejection
here came back down to here back up to
here we are looking to the left to give
us the areas that's providing us with
the retracement we are looking to the
right to give us the areas that are
providing us with the
continuations and that's how we play the
zones to the left but the zones to the
left are meaningless if you don't
understand structure and if you don't
understand what Candlestick structure is
that's why I have Candlestick structure
in that playlist it's the first video
that's there it is so very important for
you to learn Candlestick structure
because it's the fastest way to get into
your entry and it's at the earliest time
that price is Shifting that you can get
into your entry with candlestick
structure so you I want you guys to just
um consider that there's more teaching
on these swing points because it goes a
lot more in depth insanely in depth you
guys might think that you learned
something today
boy and girl if there's any girls in
here you don't know and and anybody else
who identifies as anything else you know
you guys don't know you know like it's
it's wild it goes very very in depth and
you know I I want you guys to to
understand how to get involved utilizing
these areas and all it is is Swing
points that they're mitigating that's it
all the are swing points you know so
it's best to use the 15minute swing
point or an hourly swing Point as well
um and more more times than not you get
reactions from those so let's say we use
this swing Point here look at this swing
point I just noticed this but let's see
if it works this swing Point here
remember this Wick we're not using this
Wick we're using this to this this to
this swing point this to this look at us
let's move this
over what do we
get from this Wick here to this Wick
here here
tap and we make our way
up when you start to understand how to
mix and match the Wicks and the swing
point and all of that other stuff it
would begin to open up your eyes in
terms of like so many areas on the chart
that you could trade from that you had
no idea and you can just create little
setups from it oh this is a scalp here
but if it comes back up here and Taps up
here this is a short to continue but if
it comes down here and Taps here this is
the scalp and maybe it comes to
here and Taps here because this is the
s& Zone responsible for the structural B
to the left side maybe it comes in and
Taps here and gives you a double bottom
here but look we might have already got
a tap here so maybe that's why we
started to flip bullish because we
tapped into this snd here so now we know
that we're flipping bullish from tapping
into this snd and we look to get
involved on the downside now so now what
we're looking for is potential areas for
price to come back to and give us
touches
on with one being
here you have this one here was this
mitigated nope you have this one here
this wasn't mitigated either but price
just tra above
it so now you wait for it to come and
tap back into here now it could come and
tap into here and continue up it might
come and tap back into another area
there and continue up then might tap
into another area there and then shoot
up out of
nowhere and
then come crashing down to break the
trend and now we're going downtrend and
we're hitting the middle of the Swing
points
going
down and this is why understanding
structure is important because you would
have an idea of which swingo you're
using and why you are using that swing
Point that's why the structure videos
are very important so this will help you
but those structure videos will maximize
your learning I promise you will
maximize your
learning you know so yeah it's it's uh
it's crazy let me let me go through some
of this too um stop loss below the wick
would be safe yeah because they're not
returning back there they're not
bringing people back to break even
they're trying to get them out shake
them out they're not giving them back
that they they're going to at least
bring them to some area of loss they
might have been able to hold to but
they're not taking them back to to their
Break Even they manipulated that area so
they usually just test
the the body of the candle that
manipulated the area they don't test the
wick or go below the bottom of the wick
because that's the area they used to
shake people
out um yeah I have friend that only
trades based on ISR confirmations or
Divergence uh they called me sometime
they wait to take they wait long
time to make a good trade but it's a lot
of money to trade
left it
behind in between yeah I mean you know
like people utilize their own systems
and they have their own risk involved
and and they make money yes but we're
talking about like being able to make
you know an upen amount of money and
also be very very accurate with it so
you see guys see how I said we tapped
into a bullish area and we would end up
going bullish I said that all of this up
here was already mitigated so we would
end up going through the area and I said
that there could be a poti potential
rejection here back down but then we
could still end up just taking the high
above so you would just look for the
first the rejection
there you know at this area and it can
just be like a momentary rejection
something quick something short you know
um and then you can get a run of the
high after but it's all because we
tapped into the bullish area responsible
for the structural break so that's how
we understand that so if we knew that
and we saw this pushing up this could
have been an a scalp on a New York
session just taking that little short
move there could be like 50 60 Pips you
know just understanding that oh we're
about to run this whole area because all
of this is mitigated already lunch meat
right here you know so that's like
noticing those things to the side and
and finding ways to to you like stay out
of certain um snd zones comes from
utilizing these swing
points because most people you might
have somebody who has this snd Zone
here why are we not using this snd Zone
here because if you move it down to
where this swing
is
here price already mitigated it at this
candle
here we already got mitigated this swing
already got mitigated
so when price comes back up here most
dummies are waiting here for an order
block to be tapped into and price shifts
down
but it's the move that they're coming
back
to shifted down came back up tapped into
it left this whole swing is mitigated no
matter if this order block is up here
unmitigated the swing is mitigated
already
so you know price is going past this
area and then we end up taking the highs
these are equal highs right
here equal highs get ran later equal
highs run the low yes but when it
returns to it it runs
it based on what area of structure it's
in so we run this High We tap up into
this is the second tap of an imbalance
to the left so we all know that this is
usually just a retracement back down and
then we go through the area so now
noticing that that we're rejecting from
here we know that it's just a
retracement down maybe into some
imbalance here maybe into some sndas
down here but then we know we're going
to trade higher because this is just the
second tap of an imbalance to the left
and it already took out the high of the
area here so we get the retracement down
then we come back up above the area and
do we get reject Ed from an imbalance
here right here maybe who knows we'll
see what price does when it gets up
there but we have it we're pegging for
it to run this high but if it doesn't
run this High that's okay we'll adjust
our
bias and that's how you know like this
all kind of um works together you know
for for everybody to kind of understand
I hope you guys are you know holy
effing uh yeah I say some of you guys
are are understanding um you know what
what I'm saying right now
um let me
see oh oh AE said he wants to touch on
that example when when I'm done um
anytime this happens it's price always
going to take out the highs that were
created um it just depends I mean if if
we have this low put in and we're
breaking structure to the top side if
price doesn't take out this High here
and we get a rejection from up here the
rejection is usually like you know you
you'll see it like
this we get a rejection out of there and
you see it's heading back down if we're
heading back down and we don't like
create a flip
here if we don't create that flip here
and begin to wake up make our way back
up this is being ran and often times
this will get ran coming back down to
this area often times this will get ran
because it would be a weak low if failed
to put in a new high this is the lowest
point here and price is banking on this
point to be strong enough to Deliver
Us from Eva no just kidding Deliver us
into a new
high and we would end up
delivering and this would valid validate
this low right here but if we get caught
up here and we begin to short from the
area and we break structural lows on
this trend we break structural lows if
we break structural lows you better
believe that we would be coming back
down to liquidate the area and continue
lower but when you back test this and
you see it enough you would be able to
make certain decisions in real time on
how you can engage into the market and
what system based on your personality
can also you know like like create that