all right um
and guys before we start i do want to um
take a minute to tell you guys that
um i'm not a financial advisor i do not
have credentials to be a financial
advisor i do not even take
my financial advice and i'm not
expecting you guys to take my financial
advice because it is illegal to give
financial advice
when you're not a certified or licensed
financial advisor so
if you and if you are in need of
financial advice
contact your local financial advisor
and they'll be sure
to
help you navigate the world of trading i
can't promise you that they won't be
working for the billionaire class or any
special interest but i will say that
they certainly will guide you in in some
direction within the financial markets
and because that's the way our laws are
where you can only receive financial
advice from them it's best for you to
follow the law and
you know go to them so um
now that we have our bias
this is our one hour bias
because you you can get the bias from
different time frames not just
you know um
a specific time frame you can get your s
and d's from from the time frame you're
trading on but you could also get a bias
from where
you have an idea of of price going
um
you know on on other time frames so to
help reinforce whether you're looking
for buys for the day or whether you're
looking for sales for the day
all right so
we have this area here let me explain
this this trade real quick for you guys
um because you you might see it happen
to the top side here but let me just
explain how i saw this i mean this is
obviously you know where the market
opened up but what i realized
with this particular area let me move
this just in case you guys
may not be able to see it what i
realized with this particular area is
you see price shifts down
price ends up taking out the low
that's here
it took out this low with this body
closure below the low
then price flips to the top side
and what did i mention when you have a
flip to the top side after
a break of structure to the downside
that you have to look for an area of an
important low
that price may trade above
before retracing
so
when i saw this push back up
i saw this candle take out this high
right here
now why am i using this high
i'm using this high
because
this is intermediary structure
so this is a low
sorry this is a high this is a low
this is a high
this didn't give us a low here you see
this little wick here because it didn't
go below this
but this did
so
what do we now have
price possibly returning
to the upside
so
we break this low with this
wick here
i'm sorry this high we break this high
with this wig here i haven't had my
coffee as of yet i'm so sorry just a
little
uh disoriented and and i'm gonna get it
together uh my coffee's being warmed up
now
but um
by me of course so i'm gonna have to cut
from this and go get it but um
you know you have this high that was
taken out
and then price traded back within the
area
so
what i usually you know mention on this
channel is when you have a high a
previous high that was taken out
and then price trades away from it
usually you're getting a pullback into
the area that price just came from
or price just created you're getting a
pullback into that area and then you're
taking price long so i had
this particular
price price wasn't here yet but i put
this line here and i you know put this
arrow heading out of the area
and
you know what what you might see
is
price looked like it was going to return
to that area
after the pullback but what did i
mention i mentioned
that you have pullbacks when highs are
ran
you know you're not playing the high
with a a you know sell limit order here
to come down you're not doing that but
you're just observing okay this high was
now taken out
so price could potentially shift back
into this area
we did get a shift into this area but
price quickly moved away so what do we
have we end up having an entire area
that
is unmitigated
here
unmitigate it
price didn't return to this area to
mitigate this area before leaving
so
you have a small imbalance here you have
price and an unmitigated area so this is
an area that you could potentially trade
from
when price comes back to it whether it's
a reaction from the area whether it's
you know um
[Music]
you know just it
it runs from the area all the way to
take out a high now once you get in on
this you're gonna look when price comes
into this area you're gonna look for a
bullish flip this same type of flip that
we just observed where price went up
took out a previous high traded back
into the area and then left this same
type of thing here should happen if
price chooses to come down into this
area mitigate it and then leave you're
gonna have this happen before price
leaves to take out the new high
or the new low so this is why you pay
attention to
these areas where price flips and just
as i mentioned
i said that you could possibly have it
on the top side which that's exactly
what we have
we have price trading higher
this is an important low
this is making some some highs and lows
in here but there's no body closure
above
to solidify this low yet so price can
continue to come down into this area
until here
this candle closes above the high
of the low that was established
so
because this candle closed above we have
a stronger indication
that you know price is going to continue
higher
it closed above
it did not make a lower low after it
established this low it did not make a
lower low it actually made a higher low
so then
we have price
come up into this area
right here we have price come up into
this area and what does it do create
another high for us so what's what's
established here
the new low
is established here when a new high is
created a new low is validated i should
say that
when a new high is created
so
we had this new low put in and we had a
new high created and then what happened
the low was ran
so what are we looking for
when the low is ran
we're looking for price to retrace back
up into this area
and we're taking it short
so a lot of people
really don't understand you know like
they have issues on on where to get in
from with trading from certain areas
and
it's just because they're not really
noticing the price action
going on
in this
so
when you have an idea of the price
action what's happening
right now in this moment with price and
you're monitoring it this is the one
minute so you have to pay attention to
this because it all happens fast
but
you have
the hourly now you could examine the
hourly and set up a
an hourly move
just based on this alone
we went to the hourly and saw this s d
here we saw the hourly take out a high
to the left
we said when price trades above a high
usually have a pullback after
this is on the one minute that we're
watching this pullback but
we got the high taken out on a higher
time frame
so because it was taken out in a higher
time frame we should end up having a
trend
back into this area before price pushes
up
again if price is going to push up again
how do we know price is pushing up again
we know it when we notice this same
requirement this same setup
on the downside
and when we notice that on the downside
it gives us time to set set us up for a
buy
as well as set us up to get out of this
trade because now the retracement is
finished and we possibly trending to the
top side
and we don't get out of the buy
from what you know when we catch it
below we don't get out of it
until
we see bearish behavior created up here
and then it lets us know
let's get out
so
you know in that explanation
you have this
as the area of entry you have this
as
the stop loss
the high
as a stop loss in which you're looking
to take the short from and where are you
shorting to the next possible area
which
there's this possible area after price
left it
there was no mitigation to it
this entire area here
price pushed to the top side so what
could you potentially have
you could potentially have a movement in
price that
comes here
you know or
you might have it
i don't know come here
so let me take this
put that there
and
you put that there and you just you just
see which one is the more likely area
for price to tap into and go
a lot of the times it's an area where
there's an imbalance that's near do we
have the imbalance yeah we do right here
it's an area that price hasn't come back
into do we have the area that price
didn't come back into yeah right here
you know and and a lot of people call
this choppy but if you really do pay
attention to what's happening here you
have one low
put in
and then you have a series of lows being
created and ran
so when price is manipulating the lows
it's showing you that it still wants to
go to the top side
and you get that where is the
established low here
because price never came back to this
low so guess where they started buying
here
and after they buy
all the way up
they begin to when they get to a
particular you know area that they're
ready to get out they begin to dump
selling their profits
sorry
after this push-up because remember we
can't move the market retail we we can't
like you know us trading on these little
accounts even if we had you know 100
million dollars to trade with we're not
moving this market at all
this is a market that the bank's moving
so the best way to trade this market
is to trade
with the banks
use these little footprints that they
leave behind these are these are little
small
things that that little small footprints
that they leave back here
for us to be able to learn to trade from
and
as we're using these you know like you
you can't do something and
and not leave any evidence behind
there's always something left it's like
a
a kid stealing
cookies out of the cookie jar
what do you usually see
crumbs of cookies all over their face
hands dirty or jar left open or one
cookie missing but either way within
that scenario
you always can figure out
where the evidence was left
where did they slip up
and
you go back and and you you analyze that
and that's what i've seen
trading in these markets
in in all of these markets that's what
i've seen
the little footprints that they leave
behind so i know other people like to
use white golf other people like to use
ema's divergence with the rsi all these
different things these different
patterns stuff like that you know i've i
got rid of all of that i started that
way and yeah some people can be
profitable with that you know but
an easier way for me an easier
understanding for me
is
using
these little footprints that are left in
the market now timing these
is is incredibly you know
scary and and anxious sometimes because
what you have is
you often have
you know where sometimes you can get a
fake out here
because look you have
you have this low right here
you have a high
here on this candle
so if you look
this candle here came
just above the high like a little let me
let me actually zoom in so you guys can
see it so you think i'm lying and making
up stuff
right
here
this was our low
and
this actually so no look at that
this is our low
this is our high
why because it's low in too high and
then low is created
so
this is our low
this is our low this is our high
we come down here
we shift
price downward and we create a lower low
why does price still go up
you might be wondering yeah why does
price still go up
after we took out the low
the reason why is because we didn't put
in another high yet
look look at this this is
this is the last low
this is the last high
did we get a candle closure
above
sorry did we get a candle closure above
this high right here
no we didn't
no candle closure above the high before
the low was ran
so because we didn't get a candle
closure above the high and then the low
was taken out
we're not taking this trade
we're not taking the pullback of this
trade into the continuation down
because we first need
a high established
and then
a low taken out
and after the high is established a new
high that's supposed to come from over
here it did not come
after
the high is established
like it it broke structure to the upside
body structure to the upside you don't
have that you just have a candle
that closed here we put in a low here
and then we came here
we don't have a candle closure above
here
above this high
so
technically
when
it drives below the low we're not
looking to take the pull back into this
area not saying that it can't pull back
into this area and go because it can
but the likelihood is is much smaller
when
there hasn't been a new high established
before running the low
and that's why i said that when we were
here i would like to get a close above
this area or a couple candles within
this
area so if i get a close above this area
and then the lowest ran
then
cool i could look for a pullback and
then take take the trade down
but if i don't get a close above
then we're still going high
and we kept going high until here
and what did we get we got the low we
got the candle closure above
the high
candle closure above
and then we trade it back below it right
here
where do we trade back below it on this
candle
actually i'm sorry this was our this was
our our low i'm sorry forgive me this
was a high
this was our low
this was the new high this was the run
of the low price pulled back
and then we take out from this area
and now we look
for some bullish behavior to this
downside
and that's how
you like if you were in this trade
and you were expecting it to go down
here and then you had price shift up
right here
and come back to this area
you know a lot of the times you might be
trying to figure out well is price gonna
push
all the way back up to this area and
take me out
there's a possibility that's why we
partial out at certain areas
of price
we'll partial out at certain structural
areas
low here
some people might partial out here you
know or some people will wait to partial
out down here hoping that price gets
there and if it doesn't they get taken
out of break even cool risk-free trade
you know you didn't technically lose i
mean except for the commission
you know but
you got to make sure that you you take
some profit off of the table
runners will get whatever other profit
that that you know you you didn't get
but there's multiple setups that happen
and when you have these multiple setups
happening
you can partial out at all these
different all these different trades
that you you're going to take
you can partial out on it
so this was before the market open this
trade down here was after
um
the market opened
and then you have another setup that's
there
so
when you have all of these different
setups
this is actually where i thought it was
going to reject from but price still
pushed higher
you you tend to get these setups
to where
you know you're
you're catching major moves 161 pips
117 pips 126 pips and you can partial
out at half of those partial out at
different areas
now with with this particularly coming
down i did not partial out out of this
because i actually saw
this low get ran
and because this low here was ran
i realized it'd be another pull back up
and then when price gets to the area
that you can actually trade from you get
a strong rejection out of that area
then you get a return into the area and
then
a push out so most people are probably
wondering why didn't you take this trade
here
right here
stops behind here behind the area
why didn't you take this trade up
somebody could have very well taken this
trade
right into this area tap and it goes
a lot of the times
you get another pull back into the area
and that's where some traders see the
double bottom
and then they jump in to go
and you do oftentimes get a pullback you
know sometimes when prices strongly
reacting from that area you do get a
second pullback into that area before
price continues
and that's exactly what happened on this
side
so
if
if i was told
to well well if i
created a bias and was like you know
what let me just trade from this
particular area
i could have
but
if price didn't go where i was expecting
it to go which was right here
then it would have came back and stopped
me out
stopped me out right there and then went
in the direction that i thought it was
going in
and this is why you want to wait for the
confirmation of
bullish behavior what is the
confirmation of bullish behavior look
price came down
price flipped
above the last high
ended up taking us down here below this
low but then you had another push up
how did we get involved in this because
we spotted right here
that this high
was being taken out
so we had a pullback and it took us
right up to our area now could we have
taken this long yeah
further yeah we could have
but that wasn't that that wasn't the
area that i was targeting you know so
it's all about a matter of of managing
it because
right here
you know i got out but yes i could have
still stayed in and waited until i saw
some bearish behavior take place within
this area
and if price came out of this area
and i'm still in this trade i know that
you might have a pullback back into this
area here and this is where i'll get out
and get in a cell and then take it down
but i need to see
the bearish behavior take place in this
area to know that i'm selling from it
just like it did up here
i need that to happen
and and what you have
you you had that here remember i said
there's some bullish behavior that you
want to pay attention to
what do we have you know within this
intermediary structure here we have
right within here
low high low high
low
run of the high
not just this high but this high
ran it
pushed up wrapped back around into the
area
and then
took us
for a long backup
so
this is something that you want to pay
attention to because it helps you to
manage the trades that you're in
it really really helps you to to stay in
these trades like there's some people
that will cut their trade here
and then if price ends up melting
further down to this side it's like oh
man i should have stayed in and what do
they do
they turn around and they try to jump in
on another trade here
and when they jump in on another trade
here
when this low is ran what are we
expecting to happen
we're expecting to pull back into this
area so
they go chasing
down
down here when this low is ran they go
chasing it hoping that it's gonna go
further oh man bearish momentum coming
out of the area yeah gotta get in on
that
and then
price
triggers them in runs the low and then
take us back for a pullback
and now your stop loss is right
because more than likely you would have
put the trade here put it behind
a previous structural area or even
possibly put it behind here but who
wants a stop loss like that
who wants a huge stop loss
hoping that price doesn't come into the
area
but then you don't know where price is
going
that's a whole bunch of uncertainty
in this one trade if you were running
and chasing it
so we had this bullish flip to the
downside
and now we're looking for
possibly
a bearish flip
and we may not get that
you know we we might have price
pull back up into this area and and just
continue to go above because our
original bias is that it's coming here
within this this s and d zone
and the imbalance that's between this
area
but
how do we know if it's not going to go
there
we know that by observing if there's
bearish behavior that takes place
anywhere that bearish behavior takes
place up here anywhere that we notice it
then
we'll flip our bias and and that could
be temporary
that bears behavior up here it could
certainly be temporary
because it can just flip bullish just to
come back mitigate this area and then
it could flip bare sorry come back
mitigate this air and then flip bullish
again from this same area and this is
what i'm talking about with multiple
trades multiple setups that you could
use
you can use multiple setups within just
a day's worth of trading
and not even a day within a couple hours
this is the one minute time frame
so between now
and
4 p.m
when you know all volume kind of leaves
the market
between now and 4 p.m there's a bunch of
quality setups
that
you can get with this
a bunch of quality setups
you know again we we saw this here we
could have took the tap in that area
and took it up to maybe this s and d
this probably would have been my partial
area y or this would have been the
partial area one because this is
um the previous high
that we're running from this area so
when we run the high we know that we get
to pull back into the area
so
i'm partially out at here because i know
this this is going to come back to me
anyway
so if it takes me out at break even
i'm looking for the next setup what
happens this is all within let me look
at this this uh
so from the time price came into here
to the time that
we got a second entry this is 16 minutes
16 minutes
two possible entries two possible setups
here
within 16 minutes
after taking a full set up into this
area
161 pips
one lot size that's 161 dollars on a 10
loss size that's 1610
that can certainly
work for you short move one minute time
frame
this happened in
43 minutes this is in no volume
this happened in six
so trading in in times where there's
volume that's something that you want to
make sure
that you're doing so
you know you have faster setups on one
minute
this you have to wait a pretty long time
to get to
so
you know we have this happen
plenty of times around
this this map this happens plenty of
times
and when this happens you have trades
coming from those areas
because you you have
you have this retracement
you have a long
going into this retracement from here
let's say your stops was were behind you
know the area
what did i say i like to see
the candle
you see this this candle here the
bearish candle went down the next candle
opened up
took out the low of the previous candle
and then traded above
what did i tell you about the areas that
i like to see trades coming out of
i like to see that and it gives me
confidence to stay in past this high
being ran and to stay in up until maybe
the s and d area that's that's up here
the unmitigated smd zone
because i have specific rules to
when i'm finding a setup
and when i'm executing it
so
you know you you have this area that you
could have potentially
trade it from 78 pips again 10 lot size
you know like this is this is making
more than people make in a week
just with these rules and using these
very short movements
because this is
this is what six minutes
you made somebody weekly salary in six
minutes because of precision
because you chose to go the extra mile
and learn this as much as you could
and now
you know like the these are so easy to
find everywhere they're so easy to find
like i see people say oh you know uh
you know 31 860
is
an important area
and if price doesn't hold there
then
we're gonna have a huge drop you know
and they and they make their predictions
based on the lowest area
that
price is in
you know currently
and if it does run this area
yes you may have a drop into this area
here because obviously all of this down
here is unmitigated you could have a
drop into this area you could have a
drop into this area
but we know that when it runs the low
first
we got to be careful because
it'll run the low and then have a huge
push back to the top side
so it's best not to get in on an
impulsive trade like that
but this is the stuff that people are
teaching
you know other traders to to trade with
i know um
you know i i haven't started making
short videos yet explaining this but i
do want to make shorter videos that you
guys could go over and learn
more and more from um to be able to
you know time
these these different entries in the
market is you you got to have a bunch of
exposure to it truthfully speaking like
over and over you have to have hours of
it
in the room
sorry i am
i had to uh
get out the kitchen he loves rummaging
things in the kitchen
so he goes to his playroom but um
you know you you you have this
to where this happens and look look at
what this has given us
this hasn't given us a high yet
the price broke above
so because this hasn't given us a high
as of yet
we're still bullish on this
this is the last high this gave us the
low
there's no high above this
just a bunch of wicks
now some people see wicks as rejections
like right here
some people would take this area
and be like okay this is a this is a
major rejection area and they'll go like
this
there was some support here
broke through
some major rejection area
and their rules are simply if it gets
rejected from here once and trade away
if there's a second rejection
you take that rejection
out of the area
and you target this low
so
they're taking cells from here and
they're putting their stops just above
an area you know like somewhere up here
like maybe the first first high above
this or possibly even the the last high
that's there
and they're they're hoping that
the trade leaves the area here
they're hoping that the trade leaves
this area and
doesn't come up here to their stop loss
so then they see price breaking above
the area and it's like all right chad um
you know this could just be a fake out
it just might poke through and then come
back down
you know like that they're making up all
these different
things as to what price could do in this
area
and it's all off of their own opinion
what price can do
it's not off of
what is price showing us right now
what is price showing us
and what did i mention when price wants
to go bearish this is this is not
like
i'm not ever
supporting this style of trading
anything so even if this does go
in this direction
you know i'm just giving an example of
it i do not trade this way and i do not
support this type of trading
because
it it lacks the skill and the awareness
to sit there
and pay attention to what's happening in
real time
we're just saying okay it's going to
come here reject come back here and then
we're going to trade it coming out of
this area
that's very easy
to
to analyze and and to hope
that this setup works
that's very easy for anybody coming in
oh look at the areas where it's support
and in turn resistance
it's very easy for people so people are
gonna be more inclined to to learn this
way
and trade this way
but
there are other ways
to
get to the same conclusion
up here
where
you know when you get to that conclusion
you're sure
of the trade coming out of this area
you're not just hoping and that's why
when when they have those little things
here this is exactly what they do when
they have these little things here they
go just like this
and i and i see a couple traders do it
too they go just like this
they go like this
right here
and i go oh yeah chad we partialed out
at you know what whatever whatever it is
21 pips
21 pips let's go chat everybody is
writing w's in the chat or or whatever
it is that they're putting in the chat
and
this is this is what they're doing this
is how they're teaching people to trade
now it's just runners we're going to let
the runners run
yeah it was a good day
with just this
this is the quality of
you know like the years of experience
that people take to learn things in this
industry they come in this industry and
they look at this
they start trading this way
and they catch a little bit and people
like yeah made so much money on that
movement you know it's 20 pips so if you
were trading on a 10 lot size with 20
pips you know you have 200 bucks
but if you were trading on 100 lot size
then
you know you have two thousand dollars
and when i personally trade i trade on a
40 lot size
so you can understand
the numbers that work out
you know with
with this
it all comes from
having that particular skill set
to be able to understand that this is
not the way to trade
because if this was we we could teach
five-year-olds this and they could
retire their parents
just doing this
i see them do this in in in roblox and
in in
in a
minecraft this is child's play
that's not how you trade at all
and that's not how you teach people to
trade
because what indication do we have that
price could potentially be coming down
we look at what price is doing right now
in this moment
and we look at the areas that price
might have tapped into
so
if you want to take a look at
what price did and
and where it went
we see
that price hit our supply area right
here
this cluster of candles here
price hit our supply area
tapped
then traded away
now
when we see all of these trade all of
these these you know candles around our
entry
seven minutes worth of candles
you know a lot of the times we may see
you know five minutes ten minutes
sometimes just
going sideways in that area
before
price ends up
taking us the other way
but
we don't we don't get in because it
tapped our area because the same way it
tapped our area is the same way it can
go right through it
so we don't get in when price is tapping
the area that's catching a falling knife
where we're getting in
is
when we start to see
the bearish behavior that we discussed
when we start to see that playing out
because what what might we have in this
area
if price wants to go down
what might we have
in this area
what we may have
is
price shift
out of the area
let's say it shifts out of the area
runs the low
that we have as an important low
then it could take us back
into the area
and then take us out of the area
like that
so
if we had a run of this low yes
that that is something that
you know we should consider doing
when taking this trade not just because
it tapped here
because we had
rules that we followed in terms of if
price produces this here's how we
respond to it
and
this is what you get
this is how you get safer entries into
these areas now
although i had mentioned that this is
you know a um
a supply area you could also adjust it
to this here
why because we have this low
and we have this high
so within this entire area
between this low and high when price
trades away from it you have to look
and and get an idea of where price
usually reacts off of
and
whatever area while you're back testing
you usually see price react off of
you would go and start to utilize that
area on these pullbacks
and not just the pullbacks you would
utilize this area down here in this area
that wasn't touched you would utilize it
down here so you already have the
anticipation of areas set up but it
doesn't necessarily mean you're you're
catching a trade from there
you're watching to see what is price
doing in that area
before i take a trade from there
is it giving me
any type of of
bullish behavior
coming out of here
you know is it giving me any type of
bearish behavior coming out of here
and
when you start to notice that
then you start to see that
you know it lines up
and as i mentioned down here
i said that usually
when
you get strong rejections out of certain
areas
you usually have
a double
entry
or or a double tap
within this area
so you get the double tap
and then
price takes us out
usually that's what you get you know
when there's like a a strong push out of
a particular area
um
we we had this
you know where we got in here
then price came back up towards the
entry near the entry
and remember how i mentioned you can
catch this by up to this area
but you want to be mindful of what
happens in this area because then when
you start to see
some bearish behavior start to take
place here
then you will go ahead and take the
trade out
yeah you you'll start to see this
you start to see this
so
we have this
as our high
price shifted above here
this being actually let let me
let me use this and
and actually mark it
out uh
this
i should have probably used this let me
so you have here
so you can take this
and this
this didn't have a closure to this
and we have a tap here
yeah let me just double check
actually this might be it here
wait let me see sorry i'm just checking
the level so i can give you guys um
accurate information
uh so
you have this
this
is
low
this is a high
this is a low
now it's here
so it's
here but with an intermediary structure
i'm conflicted because this candle here
gave us both a
no i'll keep this
yeah i'll keep this so this is the low
that i'm expecting to be ran this
important low
if this low is ran then we could have a
reversal to the downside
if this low is not ran
then
we're just going to continue higher out
of this area the same way that we did
this area
because you see it kind of looks the
same the slanting upward
you get a pullback and then price shifts
higher
you have the slant again
upward
you get a pullback and there's a
possibility that price ends up shifting
higher
above this
so if price shifts above this
we have the possibility of
let me see
there's a possibility that this high is
ran
and what happens when we run highs
we run the high
and then
we pull back into the area and possibly
continue
but that's just what our bias is
we actually look at price to see what
price is doing
when it happens
and that will determine whether we're
taking the trade from that area or not
and the structure at 10 30 but the
structure and long entry at 10.50
is a little confusing
1050 entry
is based on structure to the left
the 10 50 entry that's
here
oh you're saying that you're you're not
understanding
why there was an entry here anthony
correct
i just want to make sure um
because if it's this entry we use this
entry on intermediary structure not
necessarily here
this
this trade we were taking into this area
because this was a possible area that
price could react from to the upside so
that's why we took this trade here
and this particular entry
right here
is because we were looking at
um into i don't know if you were here
during the explanation but we were
looking at
you know intermediary structure
so
if you look at these these wicks these
wicks are highs and lows too
these these wicks that i'm drawing this
line on these are highs and lows too
so when we have these highs and lows
coming down if you go to like the second
time frame you'll see it exactly like
this whole thing but it would just be
within this area when you come back to
the one minute time frame so
we had the run
of this high right here
we ran that high breakup structure to
the top side
so when we get that break we're
anticipating a pullback back into the
area
and then we're taking it long
and
where do we take these long to we take
these long to
the these lungs to unmitigated areas
that price could potentially react from
that's where we're going so with with
this in particular the reason why i
pointed to sorry it's actually here this
area is because
if you look at this
this right here is
this is supply
this is a supplier this one wick right
here
is the supply area
there was no mitigation so you know
price shifted towards the downside
and
the next candle that opened did not go
into the area it traded away from it
so because it traded away from it it's
considered a supply area it wasn't it's
it's an unmitigated area an untouched
area
and you also have this here
as well
but these are more so like the the
smaller ones these are more so on the
seconds time frame the previous time
frame
you know like like something lower than
this
so if you were to go to i don't know
this is the one minute maybe you wanted
to go to one second
on the one second within these areas if
you drew these lines and went to the one
second you would see this as larger
areas like this with a bunch of you know
pullbacks going to the area that is
going in
so
with this we we noticed that based on
candlestick structure
not you know secondary structure or any
type of overall structure it was just
within candle structure itself
but we have mentioned that if we saw
some bullish behavior happening down
here then we would look to take a trade
back up but this happens all over the
map happens down here happens down here
you know it happened up here this is how
we got involved into these trades
because
where they were happening the areas that
they were happening in
this is how we got involved so yeah this
is
it's it's structure but
this is structure really on a lower time
frame and you probably have to be a
little more advanced
sometimes to to be able to
monitor those time frames because they
move so fast oh my gosh like could you
and and it doesn't even look like it's
it's um it's candlesticks it's just like
little lines you know little green and
red lines really
but if you use this um
no gap candle then it would create a
full candle on that time frame
but if you if you use that time frame it
takes a lot of getting used to an
adjustment it's like a crash course
going to the the one second it moves
extremely fast so you just want to make
sure that
you know you can handle price moving so
fast in that direction so again i
mentioned that these these little wicks
here are um
[Music]
you know s and d zones on on smaller
time frames so what do you have you have
when price goes into this s and d zone
you get a reaction out of it
look this wick this candle with this
wick came up in here
this one came down and went out of that
area
some people are just taking trades from
here people would with you might have
people with zero spreads
they're just taking that
that six pips could be six thousand
easily
if
you knew how to to trade these areas and
trade the reactions away from this that
six six grand easily
just on a little small move like that of
course you need more capital but
when you look at these s and d zones as
i mentioned in in some of my other
videos when you look at these s and d
zones
oftentimes you have it to where there is
a reaction when price touches it
so remember how we mentioned that this
was our s d zone here this was our
supply area
you have price reject from it and look
at this rejection 61 pip rejection
you get a six pip rejection from a
second's time frame
but here you get a 61 pip rejection just
from the zone from the zone alone
not trying to be dr seuss or anything
but you you get a a reaction from that
zone where you could get a quick scalp
off of
so
these areas can definitely help you with
that
uh i'm always looking for an abcd and
didn't
see it there
like the short entry things oh okay yeah
no i i understand what you're saying um
that's what like you know the i believe
it's elliott wave theory or something
like that um so for me
those theories just just make it easier
to spot certain things but ultimately
you want to like grow out of that and
just start to look at it from
candlestick structure when you're
looking at candlesticks when you're
reading so fine-tuned
that
you can get an idea of what could
possibly happen with
candlesticks
then
and that's on a microscopic level then
you know as a whole things start to just
you know add up and become a lot
different for you
starts to look different you know
there's just
a bunch of stuff that
a bunch of possibilities that you have
just knowing that you can apply the
fine-tuned candlestick structure to
you know the the overall structure
because now if you go to like the 15
minute now you could use candlestick
structure here in the 15 minute
and you could start using this for
you know trading the same way
so if you have you have this high
i mean you have this low sorry this high
is presented
you have this that comes back down
and doesn't take out the low
but we don't have a new high created
because a high didn't go above this
so when a high goes above this it
validates this low
and
when this low
is broken
then you'll have a pull back into this
area and in a continuation outside of it
and that's how you read it on
candlesticks
so if this if if this doesn't give us
another high this is not the low that
we're looking for to be broken this is
the load that we're looking for to be
broken
and if you can learn that with
candlesticks
then
you know
when when you're trading on on like a
one minute time frame and you're overall
looking for like structure within this
then you start to get a better idea of
you know what's possibly happening
um in price and you can catch these
longer moves from because some people
think the one minute time frame is a
time frame that
you know you trade like very short
scalps from they think it's it's like
that
you know you're you're in and out just
within a couple seconds oh that's a
scalp there okay
oh yeah i got a short move there you
know like that's all they're doing
all right 10 pips i'm out that's good
i'm good with that they do that exactly
and a lot of it is because they don't
actually have an idea of
you know where price is going have an
idea of structure
have an idea of
what is our target
and this area was our target
and when we got to our target
now we look to see if there was some
bullish behavior that was happening
and that lets us know to get out so if
you were in this trade and you were
coming down to here and we came all the
way here but ended up flipping back up
we got a retracement back
sorry we got a retracement
right here
so now this becomes where you get out
of course this is not going to just come
straight back and hit your stop loss
unless like some type of high volume
news happened or whatever it is of
course it's not going to come back there
and do that
but
you'll have it to where price will give
you an area or a landing pad for you to
get out
and not have to get out short of profit
at 64 pips you were able to come back
and get out at
you know 167.
so almost double of what you would have
got out if you saw this high right here
so you you create rules to it
i went back and see the structure on the
five second chart yes that's good you
know you you could definitely
and anything that i say go back and test
it because it's you're gonna see it in
real time
like go back and look at whatever it is
that i explain go and reproduce it for
yourself and you're going to see results
you don't have to pay for this you don't
have to
you know have any conversations with me
about it you don't need to talk to
anybody just taking these principles and
these concepts that i teach and i'm
telling you trading will become so
simple for you
extremely simple for you
you know it doesn't have to be hard
learning this is hard yes yes it is oh
my gosh i
i remember the times where
where i would just
stare at charts for hours now every now
and again i'll just go back and look at
a chart and be like okay that's probably
going to happen and just draw something
and then go back and and take a peek at
whether it actually happened like i do
that on a lot of different um
pairs that that i don't necessarily
trade
you know like here's gold right here
let me show you the same thing because
this works on everything not just um
forex this is on stocks this is on uh
commodities this is on everything like
futures all of that crypto
whatever you want to trade
this all works on it
it works the same exact way
the same exact way so
you know we we have it to where
we get
this we have this high
then we get another low put in
and what do we do we take out
the high
that was validated by the new low that
was put in
so
we had price
come up around here i was expecting
after price went above this
i was expecting price to come back into
this area
but it didn't
right right there and then when it
flipped above it didn't
but this was another area to just
consider if price came back into it so i
had put this here
you know placed my
stop loss right above this area
because this is such a small area that i
i did not expect a reaction
that would put in a new low
from right here
so this did come here there was a
reaction that took us down but this
reaction took us down into
the trade
that we were taking
and if you wanted to minimize your stop
loss this is because i didn't go back
and look at it so this is the type of
trading essay people do they set up an
area and then they wait for price to
come back into
but
if i actually wanted to minimize the
amount of pips
that my stop-loss was
then i would begin to look into this
area
so i see it to where
according to this candlestick structure
let me uh
show you
because i feel like i could show things
better than i could tell it and and
showing it would be very helpful for you
guys so you have this area here you have
this low this high
this low this high what do we have here
a break
of the low
and then what do we get we don't get
another low
we get a high put in high is ran
now this ran three of the highs
quick push up
on the second time frame that this looks
like trend line touches going down
price runs
all of the trend line touches
so
you have a lot of traders who trade with
trend lines and
they don't understand that price is
just storing up liquidity
to
come back and run it
and that's exactly what it did it ran it
now granted this is the seconds time
frame so the run on this is is not
necessarily
that deep i guess this is 10 pips on
gold so
it could be depending on what your lot
size is but that's why you manage your
risk
we had
back to what we were saying
a run of this high so when the high is
ran
we're looking for a pullback into this
area mind you this is candlesticks alone
like we're not using large areas for
this so you have a run back into this
area
so we take
sorry we take this here
we place it to like like i said when you
go and back test it you'll see different
areas that respond more than others this
might be the 50 this could be the 70 80
so
this maybe on the 80 would have been a
little more precise in the tap either
way you're looking for price to come
into this area here we don't know where
it's going to stop but then take us long
so our stop loss is directly behind this
area here
and we're looking to target
whatever area that we believe price is
coming to so price already came to this
area here
we're not necessarily looking for this
area to
to be the area we trade from but what
we're looking for
is
areas that have volume in it
and i could
you know just highlight it for you
there's volume in this area here
there's volume up in this area here
there's volume in this area
and there's
i would say maybe more of this area
volume here
so we're taking our trades and em i know
you had um actually just earlier if
you're still here um prior to coming on
the stream
um
we're take we're targeting
areas with volume in it
so because we know there's no volume in
these areas what are we doing
we're bypassing this
we're looking to take this to the next
possible area of volume
so if you look at this
this is
a 1 to 10 10 to 1 whatever you guys want
to call it
this is 99 cents for your stop loss
you know nine nine nine pips
nine pips nine pipettes you know
whatever you want to call it but this is
this is 99 cents on gold i'm saying that
it's you know it's a dollar stop loss
or 9 pip stop loss almost 10
and you're taking this up to an area of
volume
you found this here
and you were able to minimize your risk
when price came back into your area and
you looked for the flip
but if you were just a trader who
preferred to wait
and
just have the order trigger you in
you have your stops behind here and your
targets is the same the volume
look at the difference between these two
trades
both of them are great trades
one had way less risk than the other
it's ten to one
this is four to one
this if your stop loss was hit you'd
have been out in 10 pips
this if your stop loss was hit
that's 25
pips and remember with pips the
measurement of pips could mean anything
you know depending on the lot size
you're trading on
but
this is the reality of waiting for price
to get into your area and then looking
for an area to trade from you do not
need to have
limit orders or or buy stop orders or
what you you do not need to have it up
here
waiting for price to come to your area
here maybe
and you place your stop directly behind
here and then you get
ran out of the park
ran out of park and i see this happen
with a lot of traders on stream every
morning my morning routine is to go and
check the traders who traded in london
session
and every time that
i'm done trading
i go and check the traders who trade in
the morning session
and then i realize that there's
barely anybody to trade in the asian
session and i guess because the volume
is so slow and they're not able to
really like
jump in with an impulsive movement
but the asian session follows
you know rules that follow structure so
if you get in on the asian session these
moves are a lot more cleaner
and they're shorter too in terms of like
you know if you were getting in on an
area and where the stop loss would be
they would be sure to stop losses
you'd have like like 13 pip stop losses
sometimes 10 pip stop losses
you know this one was 19 here that that
we had mentioned but
you'd you'd have a bunch of stop losses
that are very short i'm trying to find a
an asian session that i might have
traded in
but i don't see it
that's here
look at this
10 pip stop loss 189 pips in the asian
session
189 pips or or whatever that was yeah
189 pips
in the asian session
the moves are a lot cleaner
you know the volume is slower so you can
time the market a little better
with with these slower movements
but i had it coming up to my area
tapped in took me out
it doesn't have to be rocket science we
ran the two we ran the equal lows
we went into a particular area to the
left i don't know what that area is
um i don't quite remember i think i
actually had i had something here but i
i deleted it i i'll go back probably
later and look at it um but it was
definitely tapping directly into this
area because i had this here
um probably from the left and
tapped in
then what
what happened
that made us know we could possibly go
long from here if we wanted to
we had the shift
remember candlestick structure low high
low
run of the high
come back into the area it's probably
like 80 90 percent
and then take us to the top side so
that's how you can find buys in well
sales into buys or buys into cells
because you're you're placing these
rules
on areas of interest for you
this needs to happen first in order for
you to look for a trade not a tap into
the area
a tap into the area does not need to
happen
you need to notice
some type of pattern
taking place when it gets to your area
to give you confidence to get in and
you'll realize that you stay out of a
lot of losing trades because of that
you do not end up with a bunch of losing
trades when you have those rules and
when you follow those rules
like price dipped down here
took out this low
but then came above here
it didn't run the high
so because it didn't run the high
i know that
this is still bearish
if i had the high ran then
price would come back into this area i
would get out here and then take a trade
long from this area
but because i still saw that price was
still bearish even though i had this
huge push down followed by this huge
push back up
it still didn't take out
the structural area needed to to flip
bullish so i knew this was still bearish
and that's what you get and so you have
price pushing down here
now you see
the bearish flip
we get one flip here and if you want to
play it safe you could wait for a second
one
because remember i said around areas
that you get in you sometimes get a a
second touch of that area and then price
goes from that area
you could wait for the second touch if
you want to if you're not feeling too
confident about it
you can just wait for the second touch
because even here
price dipped
no sorry it just
came right out flipped back up and then
traded down of course this would have
been some
you know a scout possibly here but um
if if i had an area here
you would have price shift below it
come up touch
might reject the way and come back and
touch a second time and then finally
leave the area so because you have that
sometimes you can just wait for that
you can just be patient on that and
you can catch a trade from a lot of
these different areas and not get
stopped out because you're prematurely
placing you know um stop losses and and
take profits when you don't even really
see what price is doing
you don't really have any understanding
of what price is doing
so look
we have it
it came all the way back to
where this high was remember i said i'd
like to see a couple candles between the
area before it returns
to get an idea of
knowing whether we we possibly have some
you know some bearish momentum out of
this area
and we have that so we took the first
trade here
and there was sure enough a possibility
to take another trade here
and why is that
because
we have these series of lows and highs
taking us up but then we have
a break
down
and here's one thing that i've been
noticing i don't want you guys to to
take this entirely for for what i'm
saying now because i'm still
trying to figure it out but i'm i'm
telling you guys because i'm very
transparent with my system and my
information and i want you guys to be
able to look for it as well and maybe
you guys might find a system that's 10
times better than mine you know who
knows but
you can incorporate this in it because
if you look at this low that was taken
out here
you know this one just
you know took a crap coming down into
this area
you know and then push back up
you have two areas to trade from
you have this low here
that was taken out by this move down
you
you have this low this high you're
looking for price to come and tap back
into the area you see we got this tap
here but then you also have this low
here
that this took out
so now you could start looking for your
pullback
within the range of this low
and this high
because this is as far as the candle
went
when it broke structure to the downside
so you could you could use
this if you wanted to now with using
wicks there might be a little more fake
outs than using a body because if you
use this here the body came below
this right here
where is it right here
you see the body came below
and then what happened we have to pull
back up
so we we get the pull back up
we get an area in which we're trading
from we get the exact thing that i like
that i said i like to see i like to see
a candle take out the previous high and
then trade back within it
and then we had
a low right here and then the next
candle came up take out the high and
trade it back within it
so that's still giving me some
indication that it's bearish from here
and we end up
taking a trade out of here
stops directly below above here
and the area that we were originally
anticipating
is possibly there
and we'd be taking it down into this
area
because this is an area that we possibly
anticipated it coming to
but then we're monitoring this
to see is it going to give us a bullish
flip to the top side
and if it gives us a bullish flip
we'll wait until price comes back into
the area
and then
we'll take it to wherever it's going
we'll take a buy up to wherever it's
going the buy can just be coming back
here why would it come back here look at
all of this imbalance this here
so the areas that have imbalance
are
more likely to be areas that price taps
into and trades away from
so we could potentially
have a tap here
and then we might see some bearish
behavior setting up
up here
and then we'll end up just taking it
short
but this is what you want to see
this is what you this is exactly what
you want to see
exactly like this
high low high low high
disrupted
the trend with this low
we're going to pull back back into this
area
and now we pull down
and
when price gets to our area that we're
looking to possibly trade from
now we're just trying to figure out
is it going to give us
a bullish flip
is price going to flip bullish
to take us back up here
and you might potentially have that you
might have that here
you could have that with this
flipped above the high
you could have it come back into this
area maybe this supply area here
possibly
and then you could have price
flip up just to go here
tap this and now it's away again
or it may not even make it to here it
may just make it somewhere here
in between here
and then
take us
back away from this entry
why because you could have double
touches
in in these entries
you could have price
certainly touching
you know an area twice before leaving
and being now that i i
got an idea of it this is actually the
high sorry
because we're going by the the
intermediary structure
and if you look
uh
yeah if you look right here
well this is technically not
a high it's kind of flat there
um but either way we have here as the
last high that was created before the
low
yeah last high that was created before
the low
but i think this might have been
let me see
this was a low
let me just double check
this is the so the low for this is one
one five four
the low for this is one five four okay
so this is equal lows
so it was actually this here
this was it here
and when i'm trading by myself most
times i'm noticing this in real time so
this is actually
this is the last high before these equal
lows were put in
and then price ran it so after price ran
this high here
with that wick
this candle opened up
traded to our area
what's our area
our area is
this here from this high
to the low that was put in
that led to the high being ran
so we come back into this area
here
and this is
where our entry is
right here
stops behind here
and
we're going long possibly to this area
or or wherever we said it might go i
think we have mentioned that
it could potentially go
yeah
here
but if you notice this in real time
look at look at how effective your your
trades are and if you are losing
look at what you're losing
you're losing 13 pips
on on just utilizing candlestick
structure and using that to scalp
and if you want to take longer moves if
you want to take moves that you don't
have to pay attention to
do it on the 5 minute do it on the 15
minute
those take anywhere from
[Music]
you know like 12 hours to
36 or 48 hours to play out
so but go because those take longer you
may not have to look at the chart as
much and notice things as fast because
they take longer to to play out and you
would just look at each candle closure
to give you the same story that these
smaller candles are giving you
so we get that we get this flip above
here because remember we said that that
was
this was a previous high too
but then we also get a flip above
this high
here
so what do we possibly have
we might have
a play back into
here
back into this area and then a
continuation above
but again what are we looking at
what is the overall objective of
noticing this
we're looking to see
if price is going to
take us here
and show us some bearish behavior to
continue down
or
price pulls back in here
and then
run the high
and a lot of the times
we could have a pull back into this area
and once price pull pulls back into this
area
we end up pushing a lot higher because
as i mentioned this v-shaped pattern
that price usually makes
is a reversal pattern
it means that price is reversing from a
particular area
and that's only if the v shape is
completed
with the different structural elements
that are taken into account
so
we're watching this and observing this
but again
we had an entry down here
which was a part of candlestick
structure
there's a possible entry here
which is a part of
secondary structure
and
if we have a run
of these highs
or a run of this high let's say it runs
this high but doesn't take out this high
we might have a run back into this area
because the v shape was completed
and then we get a touch in this area and
we go long
but that's just us creating a narrative
or a story for what price can do
and if
it starts to play out with those rules
that we set
then fine
you know like though those are the
trades that that we will look to get
involved with those are the trades that
will look to take
you know and usually with areas that
that i often see
you know price
may have a reaction from or even run
you get it to where i mean we we
explained it earlier that sometimes
price would come close to an area and
then reject away from it
just like this
it came close to this area
then gave us a pullback after
so people looking to try and get in from
here to maybe run this high here
they got in here trying to run this
quick high but then got pulled back
so anytime price is getting near a
particular area and you don't know what
structure is doing
you don't chase these little movements
don't chase these little hives you don't
have to because you're gonna have so
many setups present themselves
so many setups within this
this is just between
10 and 12
that that these setups took place
between 10 o'clock and 12 o'clock
you know so so when you have
actually let me see
yeah no
so so when you have
things like this play out
you know you can create some confidence
in your trading to say hey yeah i could
definitely stay in the trade
i could definitely you know like
continue to take it further down because
from from what i've what i'm seeing
with price action
i'm not seeing anything that's showing
me
that price wants to
go bullish or go bearish
so because i'm not seeing that
you know i'm gonna continue in
to the area that i chose to get in and
i'm going to continue trading that area
now if you were to miss this area
there are other areas that you can trade
from price often retraces as it's going
down it's retracing
and heading down
so there's other high probability areas
that
price can go and touch before continuing
and a lot of the times it's areas that
have the imbalance
have the unmitigated supply area
and
you know you might have it to where
price
is not ready to come above these highs
so you might even get price shifting all
the way up here and it could put in a
third high for you
it's not a high or high but it could put
in a third high for you somewhere in
this area
and then continue to trade away
but these are these are things that you
just want to look for when
when you have this setup
you know or when you're when you're
using these techniques
to actually trade from
these things that you you want to
consider
to
either get in a trade
or stay in a trade
you know like
it's it's it's very very good to use
and and this area here remember what i
talked to you guys about in terms of
like
you know
what people use
to say whether they're going
short or long from an area now granted
they use this on like the 30 minute time
frame not necessarily the one minute but
they use this to judge whether
price is going to
you know either give them a sell coming
out of there
or
give them a
buy to go up so they'll wait for price
to go above the area tap back into it
and then take you long
or they'll wait for price to reject
twice
from this area
and then take it short
so there are many different
systems and formulas that they have and
that they create
for
you know
how they're going to
um
essentially
utilize the the price action and and
what they're going to get into their
trades with and you see look you got one
rejection two rejection three rejection
going in for a cell taking you out
bringing you up here
but you said that well they mentioned
that if there was a closure below this
area
you have price rejecting and closing
below this area
then it's definitely a cell coming out
of it stops directly behind the area
all right let's go gang let's go chat
and take it down and then it whips them
back up
why because we are absent of structure
we do not know what structure is doing
right now so if we're not aware of what
structure is doing
then we should not be just randomly
taking
these these things and placing them on
here
like look they go just like this oh it
used to be support
resistance support now a little more
resistance oh now we got the brake above
so then they see the sorry they they see
the brake above the area
here
and then go like this
all right price comes there
it comes back and tests the area and
gets rejected
we're going to take it long
just like that
and i'm not saying that
that this can't happen
because yes
this can this can very well happen yes
absolutely right
this can happen
but
if
you're just doing this everywhere across
the map and there's no like real
structure for you
then you end up getting stopped out most
times
you end up getting into where they're
like oh you know yeah that was a fake
out price pushed above but ended up
coming all the way back down below
oh yeah chad we got hit with a fake out
you know they they go like they do that
exactly
we got hit with a fake out
because they're not paying attention to
the actual price action of things
they're paying attention to
this little support turn resistance turn
support and there are people who are
profitable with it but if you're going
to use that
use it with structure
so we we had saw this trade here and
remember what i said i said if you see a
bullish flip
if you see any type of bullish behavior
that's happening
down in this area
then now you're looking to
[Music]
take price
long
so we we were discussing this
and
you know we kind of had it to where
you know we missed this one because he
was looking at something over here and
then we saw this area price never came
to this area but if you were in this
trade
and you noticed that we had this
pullback we noticed that this pullback
was present
before this high was even taken
so
your area to get out
here
is
on the pullback of this
and your area to get into a buy
is where you're selling out
now of course it wouldn't have been here
it would have more so been over here
after all of this price action happened
but you're selling out here
so now that you've sold out and you
bought in
remember we said we want bearish
behavior to take place here if bearish
behavior doesn't start to take place in
this area we're looking to take this
further and i said it could potentially
run the highs
so we have the highs being ran
and
no bearish behavior took place
for us to even consider getting out
yeah to even consider usb uh us getting
out
so what did i say you might have this
high ran
and then you might have a pull back into
the area after this high is ran
before running this
but this could just wake up and run it
and then fall
but we're we're watching price to see
how to manage our trade we would have
already been out of this we saw a
bullish flip here there's no reason why
you're staying in this if you see the
bullish flip you get out when it flips
bullish you get out on the retracement
of it when it retraces here that's where
you get out but that's also where you
get in and take it long
but you're not playing like that
unless you actually know the signs of a
retracement and
for me the safest way to to understand
that or to to learn that is with
candlestick structure the first thing
i'm going to do is see the retracement
on candlestick structure the second
thing i'm going to do is confirm with
secondary structure
if it's actually happening so we had a
small bullish break that's probably on a
secondary time like a seconds time frame
then we had a bullish break again on the
secondary structure
lower time frame flip
secondary structure flip on our time
frame that we're trading on
pull back we didn't get the pullback
exactly into the area that we were
looking for
but
we had an indication to get out
and we had two signs candlestick
structure and we had
secondary or intermediary structure on
our time frame
two flips on two different time frames
letting us know that price is is
confirming again that it's going bullish
so we got two confirmations and that was
two ways to get it
just like you might have two
confirmations of
the um
the flip here
tap into the area but then saw the flip
and that's your second confirmation and
you take it long
just like you have that
you also have
other confirmations that you could use
bullish flip on a lower time flame
bullish flip on the time frame you're
trading on
and we're taking it long
and where are we taking it possibly to
our targets here
but we know that price isn't going to go
straight there
so what are we looking for
if we know price isn't going to go
straight there
we said that we wanted the highs to be
ran first
and when the highs are ran
we might have a bearish pull back into
the area
and you could have a pull back into the
area
before
it going long
but you also want to pay attention to
these areas
these why are these areas important
areas
because according to intermediary
structure
you have
the low you have the high
you have the low created you have
another high being put in
so this is an important low for us
now according to candlestick structure
this breaks a lot faster
than
[Music]
than uh
you know the
the secondary structure
this breaks a lot faster
a lot faster
so this isn't
technically a low here
because this wasn't a high this was an
equal high
so because this was an equal high this
never gave us a high and then a low
so this gave us the same high
gave us a low here
no actually this this doesn't count as a
low this validates
as the low this right here to the
downside so in terms of candlestick
structure
this is the low
that this gave us when it broke above
and then
now you have a break above to here
this becomes
the important low
so as you keep seeing price break to the
top side
you want to make sure
that you're spotting areas or updating
those areas as your protected lows
protected lows is is
the area where
smart money where the banks are trading
from
so you get a protected low here
right here
and now you have this high
and you know
if we tap into this area come back below
take out this low we might have a
retracement back into this area and then
trading away from the area
and where could be we be possibly
trading to unmitigated areas but when
you get to these areas you want to make
sure
that you're noticing the bullish flip
in this area because if it happens in
this area then you know that
you can take it
further you can take it long you may not
be able to take it to the high
you may be able to take it to another
area that's that's possibly somewhere
here
that price may get rejected from and
then go
but you want to see the bearish behavior
happen on the top side first
and then you know all right i'm getting
out
and i'm going short
you know so there you go you you have a
tap into this area
where we we
talked about this entire thing we we
talked it all the way through
with
the reasons as to why
we got into any of these trades or why
we would have gotten to any of these
trades
and
you would be able to be profitable
because your timing its patience
it's patience because it pays
and the part that they
don't really tell you about is the
is the deafening silence the fear of it
possibly not getting to the area that
you want it to go
the fear of what if it goes back towards
my stop-loss the fear of i just lost
four days in a row
now i might lose five let me just sit
out
and that's what messes us up with
with trading
this way
that's what ruins our mindset
when it comes to approaching the market
and then we come in here and we don't
actually see certain setups that we can
take
because our mind is just somewhere else
but now whether i'm in a good mindset
whether i'm in a bad mindset because
i've learned this so much and because
it's so burned into my brain
now i know
that even when i wake up from my sleep i
could immediately come into the market
and find a trait
i don't do any of that top-down stuff if
i just want to come in here and just
scalp don't even care about what's
happening on the high time frame don't
care about
you know using my brain muscle at all to
to make any moves
i may not care about that at all
and i may just want to come in and get a
little scalping going on
this is the exact system you can do this
with because you could do this with
scalping you could do this with swing
trading you could do this with any type
of trading on any type of time frame
this all happens the same exact way and
if you want to know if the market is
you know bullish or bearish for the long
term
this is exactly what you do you start to
analyze what exactly is happening
so what do we have
with
this time frame we have the low
we have the high here
and then we have this low that drops
it's validated by taking out this low
and then we have a trade above
so
we shouldn't be worried if we see price
shifting up
and then
there's a pullback later on into the day
where could the pullback go
the pullback could possibly
go into this area
right here
and then
take us further
maybe up to here
or maybe this can just continue to run
this
take us down here
into this area
there's no low here price opened up and
just kept pushing
so we have within
this low
which is at 31 200 and we would possibly
have
this high
which is at 32 600 and price can do
whatever it wants in between here it
could range each day next week in
between here
we just know that this is the area that
it's ranging in but if we do get a
pullback
before taking out this high
and the markets the market can go right
to the high at like 575 let's say
and then start to pull all the way back
here
into this area
at 31 6 31 7.
and everybody's like oh margaret's
fallen again it's bearish the bears are
in control the but the market is it
shows that there's a there's a potential
flip
happening
so if there's a potential flip happening
that's not a bearish market that's a
retracement to continue long and if you
were trading on the stock market
that's the area that you would be
loading up your stocks on
right here
at this pullback
you'd be loading up all of your stocks
on that area and then you'll see a
substantial increase
in in your stocks
if you just waited for timing
why are we expecting a pullback here
because also there's possible imbalance
from this wick
all the way to the next candle open
which is monday or sunday i think it is
sunday in the afternoon
next candle open
you might have the next candle open up
and come in to feel this imbalance
that's created
or you might have price just wick back
into this area
close here
or even close here if it wanted to
and then sunday or monday's candle opens
up and takes you further above
so it's not a continuation of
bearishness unless it goes below thirty
one two hundred
there's a possibility that it runs there
but we stated that our bias was bullish
for the day why
because we saw that this high was ran
and we said we could possibly make it up
to this high that's why i said the the
analysis in the mornings is literally
like two minutes
because
we have our bias for the day
and we end up dropping down to
the one minute i mean sorry the one hour
to pick up a little more of our bias
and
what do we have here we said that this
was an important high to run
right here
which yes i mean we see that it was
important there was a rejection from
this area
that took us down
that rejection that took us down you
guys remember where
where that was from right
let me go back to this sorry
right here
you guys remember where the
that rejection was from
here in this trade
that we took
in this trade coming out of this area
heading down
to here
then flipped bullish
and this is where you get out
and then
you have the bearish i mean the the
bullish
flip that takes you up to what the area
that we're trading from and what did i
say when it taps this area i said
because
it'll run this high and tap this area
you could get a rejection away from it
what do we have exactly when we tap into
the area a rejection
and this rejection away doesn't mean
that this is gonna come all the way down
now we have all of this to fill up no
this this rejection on this what was
this a one hour area no that doesn't
mean that
doesn't mean oh we're gonna go from here
all the way to running all the lows
we could have a rejection out of this
area and price push further up
it can go just like this here
here
and then it comes here creates a weak
high
takes out the low
comes back in
retraces
and then
takes us down to
the area that we're looking to trade
from whether it's here
or whether it's this second area
or whether it's this third area down
here
but we have all this room
in in the coming day or week or whatever
it is we have all of this room here
to trade within
so this is 32 3
and 31
4 or 31 3 if if you want to just
keep it exact
so yeah
you have all of that areas all of that
area that price could trade into after
being rejected from here but then make
no mistake it could also go up into the
middle of the area and then reject out
of there
and take us down to
whatever whatever area is going to
mitigate
and then a continuation or a break above
this
so i know a lot of people are bearish on
the market because all of the falling
that is done over the past you know
whatever time um like i said we got a
bullish flip earlier
um
last night actually yesterday then we
had price push up a little more um today
if you look at the s p the s p is what
all the stocks follow every like
not all of let me actually give factual
information the indices follow s p
because if you look at the indices
right here um this is actually s p as
well but this is s p on the the stock
market this is spy this is an option
that
people trade but it's a mirror of the
actual smp market so this was the s p
market this is
you know you see
we started out opened and had this huge
push up and that's crazy how how far was
this push
768 pips since we opened
that's outrageous
i mean some people catch these whole
pushes up
usually me at scalp in between this and
probably end up with more than this
whole push
you know because you can time a lot of
these moves
so you can be buying and selling on the
market
but we had this push up
and if you look at
the other stocks i mean sorry the the
other indices
we had the same push up
nasdaq
same push up and this is all from 9 30.
japan
same push-up
germany
hong kong same push-up they all follow
each other
but they mostly follow
this smp here the us500
so if you ever want to you know kind of
like get an idea of what could be
happening or what may happen next in the
market time it with this
time it with with us 500
and when you time it with this since
this is the heavy mover in the market
and this has stocks that are on these
other stock exchanges as well
this moves those other exchanges
so this is the second thing to kind of
you know give you an idea of
maybe the market is is bearish today and
and i will say though there are times
that
this is pushing up and other markets are
pushing away
japan might be pushing away because
they're in recession or whatever might
be taking place you know germany might
have had a terrorist attack or whatever
it is or london you know hong kong could
be dealing with covet and all of those
things are shifting these markets down
but this market is still pushing up
but the likelihood of hong kong dealing
with covet and having issues that will
affect our market too
because we're a huge consumer
um when it comes to the the products
that that the con the country has
so
you can time this during a new york
session pay attention to this during a
new york session
and this will kind of be your guide on
trading any other indices that you
possibly trade because look all of them
are retracing now
each and every one of them are retracing
they all have slightly different levels
you can see because some markets are
open and some markets are not
slightly different levels
this even super different level than
than s p has
smp has this little bit here which
consulted sideways but kept pushing
up you know and they have this huge dip
followed by this slow
you know push-up
and that happens because
they're not trading right now within
this this market it's 12 o'clock the
trading day is done
but their market still follows ours
because all the money intertwined in
these different systems and stuff
there's
you could definitely use this as a guide
during a new york session and if you're
trading in the asian session
here we go use hong kong use japan
use these to to trade the asian session
trade with asian pears because there's
more
money more volume involved within that
time frame
because look at this let me let me
actually just show you guys this i know
you guys are probably like shut up and
go to the charts but this is is useful
information for me this is how i was
using six hundred dollars to make a
thousand dollars a day
because i was paying attention to to the
things that happened so look at this
this is
seven o'clock right here
this is seven o'clock
asian session yesterday so this is eight
this is
seven
right here
look at this look at this madness
look at this
out
rages
you know why this happened
because hong kong came out and said
well shanghai sorry
shanghai one adopted bitcoin as a
virtual currency within the country so
now it's legalized
to
own the asset as a virtual currency
after they were just going through a
bunch of banning and relisting and
banning and relisting so now
you have that push up that added into
that
you also have it to where they're kind
of getting their covet situation under
control
because before it was affecting the
market
their covet situation
was tanking the markets this was back in
and this is not even just
if i go to the daily it goes further out
but it was tanking the market
but their covet situation got better
and look how quickly the market rebound
you know you have it coming down to this
area
a day and 18 hours i think that said
a day in two hours
you know or a day in an hour
recovery was quick because those things
happen in simultaneously
so if you want to trade in the asian
session
you could use these principles in the
asian session i can go i don't know just
somewhere random uh
and see look just to be transparent with
you guys
i i mean i wouldn't have been trading in
this session anyway this is this is
spread hour yeah so there's there's no
inhale that i've been trading that so
let me move away from that
um
you know so you
i mean this is just trending up really
the the way that i
would have probably gotten involved in
this is
you know until i saw something bearish
possibly let me see
uh pushed up came back in ran the low
nope that wouldn't have been taken
uh and and i'm i'm showing you guys this
just to
you know be transparent with you guys as
to
you know what trades that i would
consider taking and
what i wouldn't consider taking so this
one here this is possible let me see
right here
to here
you see in that just missed
yeah that just missed it
right here
wick flew above the area came back in
just missed it and left
so there there are times where
your setup wouldn't actually
happen the the way that it's supposed to
and that's okay
that's fine that's okay
you know so
this obviously was was
through the asian session and into the
night that this slowly moved but this is
hong kong
the pair that i've seen that that moves
a lot better
in a lot of um you know those asian
sessions are this japan session look
look at the bias that i had this was
yesterday
took a trade here yesterday in the asian
session this was not the stop loss i
don't know where exactly the stop loss
was the stop loss was here
right here let me see
yeah the stop loss was here
the stop loss is right here
and
you had a trade come right into this
area what did i mention
about
the flips
you know you have this low
the sideways
movement that that could be a high
possibly
you know but you have this low
comes up
trades below gives us our pullback but
what do you also have another high being
taken out this high
so what did i say about these highs that
are taken out
that could be the thing that that's
causing the retracement
the high being ran so what do we have
here
we had
this high ran by this wick price pull
back into this area
here's
where
your stops go
directly behind there
and you take it long
obviously when i saw price push up above
this and push up above the area to the
left i said that it would push further i
had this yellow yellow candle here
before this even started and um i said
that it would push further possibly to
these areas why because remember i
talked about volume
you can take it to these areas that have
volume
and that would have been the target you
see we got a little rejection out of
there but then
what do we have here
little rejection out
then we have price trade above
and what can we see this as
price traded above the high
after giving us a new low
traded above the high we're looking for
price to come back into the area
and then we're taking it long
so that's another entry there
and you just follow that system without
and any market whatever it is that you
need to analyze anything that you need
to look at
you know anything that you'd like to
trade i'm telling you you know this is
forex this is stocks this is everything
out there
everything out there
this is everything what did i say that
that we would have here i said that if
price came below here the protected high
we would end up going bearish and
possibly going bearish into what area
what area that i said we could go
bearish into
the original area that we spotted that
price didn't pull back into look at what
this bad boy did
came
touched the area
i left
68 pips
after touching the area
i said we would have a pullback in there
i said when price doesn't come back to
this area you save it
you save it for later
and when it makes it back into this area
then
you take it long
and you could either take it long from
this particular area here
from this area here to another area
which is i always say you know look to
target the s and d zones or the the
structural highs
you know since we don't have any um
really here that's
that's um
you know like a stronger area of
structure this is not
so
i wouldn't have been taking this to the
high i would end up taking it to the
midway
and then the reaction that i get out of
it i'm watching to see if there's a
possible cell
coming up within this area
you know high low high
low high
then we well actually this is high low
high
i wonder which one came first let me see
yeah which one came first
so it looks like the high then the low
so this took us further up brought us
down
okay so
we'll we'll take a look at this
you know take a look at this and see how
price responds to it
and you could potentially have it where
price may
i don't know
come to like this area or maybe even
this area
the potential that price taps back into
the s d
rejects away from it
and then takes us down a little more
and this is trading against the trend
because what we might have just flipped
bullish
so if we just flipped bullish
this may not necessarily be an area that
you're shorting from
until
we see some more bearish behavior
but what we took out this high
now we didn't get anything there
and we didn't get any retracement down
here
so
this would technically
you know still possibly be bullish
unless
we see a low ran
but again this low was ran here
so that puts us in an area where it's
you know possible catch 22. we have this
that comes up sometimes
you know these seconds areas that that
it runs and we want a body closure below
which we got right here a body closure
then we had to push up and remember what
i said the weak high usually runs the
low we could potentially have that
and with
this area here
and having your stop-loss directly
behind
you know like the
the traders on youtube you know you
you would have garnered 15 pips or so
you know
and partial out oh good job chat you
know
we hit the money
you know and this is just because you
don't know where it's going
or you don't have an idea of
what potentially is happening with price
so
you could have
price go
[Music]
down into this area a little further
and then
come out of the area
because we know that this may not be the
possible final rejection what might be
the possible final rejection this here
this area
and this could be the final rejection
to send everything down
from here
that's a possibility
because we still didn't have price come
to this area
so we could have it go up to this area
tap
come down to this area
and then take us up into
this area here
and that could be a possibility
with the movement of price
so it's
taking out the lows
running the highs
running the lows again
specifically some of the equal lows
possibly
coming back into an area that it left
earlier today
and then trading long from it
and that's how you create a bias
for
what could potentially be happening with
price
and even though i have this
i'm still looking
at price overall
i'm still paying attention to in here
so yes i see it i see this happening i'm
not jumping into a cell right here just
because i i had it possibly going down
to this area then back up
i'm not doing that
because that's reckless
for me what i'm doing is
waiting for price to come to my optimal
areas
the areas that the prices is most likely
to react from
not trying to catch a ride with price to
you know the areas that i'm going
so if this invalidates and this pushes
up to here
it doesn't necessarily mean that the
rest of this
is
is not true
it can just be this one area
and this area can push into here tap out
of there run all the lows that it was
establishing along these areas
run all the lows
take out all the stop losses here run
the lows on the bottom side here
tap into this area that went unmitigated
and then start running the highs from
the top side with the people selling in
so that's why you never stay
in a trade
on this time frame and expect it to go
within a daily time frame because
there's a bunch of pullbacks within that
area to get there
and
you know depending on where your stops
are it could easily get hit
so more than likely you want a pullback
that that's going in a daily direction
and you're hoping to catch the top or
the bottom of that
and how do you catch the top and the
bottom with that with these same
principles that we teach every day here
on this chart
every single day we teach these
principles
and you could use these trading
anything and the way you become better
at it
is
truthfully speaking the more time that
you put in
if you put in
a good amount of time
to study to learn and observe these
things happen when they're happening i'm
telling you your whole life will be
changed
your trading style
you'd find it that it's a lot easier for
you to come into the market spend an
hour a day maybe an hour and 30 minutes
and then just get out of there
no reason for you to stick around
and you'll learn that
you know with
with things like this
i remember what i told you guys about
the the equal high here
i mentioned with the equal high
that or or at least with the highs that
don't necessarily take the high that
it's going to run
it comes close to it
inches up and then trades away
because you have a lot of traders that
see these candles pushing up and they're
like oh that's a great time to get in
wow let me jump into this
and what happened
there they're stopped out
yeah they stopped out
so you want to pay attention to to these
equal highs that happen because
oftentimes
you know
like i said you have a huge push away
from that area so you don't want to
chase it
and then you end up with like this three
candles pushing up go directly to the
area come back down
and
this one candle here is like 20 pips
inside of it 22 pips in this one candle
so you jumped in trying to chase on this
and it pulled you all the way back
which could potentially pull you further
back to maybe even the the area that we
discussed here
and then you
take the l because you realize that it's
a possibility of it not coming back or
you over leveraged
and now you have to hedge in a cell
while you're in this buy and you don't
know where this cell is going
meanwhile you don't even know where the
buy is going either
so you don't want to chase these because
then you end up in those predicaments
where
you know now you you have to cut your
loss you're unaware of it if it's going
to come back
and if it does come back
you might have been in a cell just
trying to stop the bleed
you know so you you just you just want
to be mindful of that and
that would help with your trading go
through my earn and learn series i'm
probably going to add this into the earn
and learn series as well but go through
the earn and learn series there's so
much information
on my playlist the earn and learn
playlist so
much oh my gosh people are like why
aren't you charging for this this is
great information
for people to learn and actually trade
from no because it's it's free i make my
own money
trading that's my job to trade
but i love i'm very passionate about
teaching and i'm very passionate about
helping people understand things that
they may not necessarily be able to
grasp without somebody helping them and
why is it that you know everything needs
to be a charge we're in a recession or
we're heading into one it's gonna get
worse
you're taking people money so you could
make money on top of the money you
already make
doing trading
unless most of your time is going
towards actually
helping people consulting people then i
could understand where
the
you know the charge is coming from
but i could come on and do this any time
of the day i could have insomnia i can't
sleep and i can get up and trade and
make money and be profitable you you
guys see all of this coming out go into
any youtubers channel search their name
raja banks uh
control fx
uh champion pips all these different
people which i'm not saying that they're
bad traders and i'm not speaking bad
about them but i'm saying go into
their streams look at how many trades
they take a day
that might be sufficient to take one
trade for them
but for me
since i trade on one minute and since i
have such precision with with the skills
that i've developed
i'm like hey why not just
you know trade any time of the day take
any amount of trades that i want to take
you know like people like don't over
trade don't have
don't because if you over trade what's
going to end up like all of that please
cut it out leave me alone like
just
i i don't care about that
at all
because skill is skill regardless of
what environment you're in
that's why when when
gifted children are taking exams
for for giftedness watch this candle
here um because it just wicked below the
candle to the left and could possibly
start to pull to the upside from here
but with gifted kids when they take
exams they take them to even in
kindergarten they take them to an
entirely different school with
different staff
and
nobody that they know
and when they when they take that exam
they're in in an environment that's
completely unfamiliar to them
and
why do they do that because when you're
gifted
it should show in every single
environment that you're in
your given it your giftedness
should show in every environment that
you find yourself in
every single environment and i think
that this is possibly going to shift
down from here because this might be a
wike off
um
up here so you could have a shift
further down into
this area here
there's a possibility just because this
looks like distribution right here this
is a distribution schematic so if you
were still in this trade
there's a possibility that you can take
it to
you know these areas this being the
first area here because this was an area
that wasn't tapped in to
remember i mentioned that that we might
have
the trade come into this area and then
leave it there's a possibility that it
can
again these lines that i use they're
just essentially
you know giving me some guide to what
price can do
but price doesn't necessarily have to do
that
price can do
something else
what we want to know is
we want to see
bullish behavior remember we discussed
that
we want to see bullish behavior
happening down here
to get some idea or some indication
that we should get out of a trade
so look at this 10 pips
for 96
taps right into our area
that we were looking to short from
up here now we did mention this area
here too but did we see any bullish
behavior here
no
we didn't
so if we don't see bullish behavior
we're not looking to get out of a trade
you can take it and close here and and
maybe a
partial
and now you have runners heading down or
you can just continue to hold if you
understand what price is doing but as i
just mentioned i said this looks like
distribution up here so this could
potentially take us further down
the first area being here which this
bullish i mean sorry this bearish
engulfing candle coming through this
area is not a good sign at all
like i would
not even have any hopes
for
price coming up from this area
to target the highs
because this candle pushed directly
through
the supply area that's here yeah it
tapped into this one
but it could tap into this one here
to take us back up here to take us back
down here
and when you understand that when when
you have rules that that shows you that
i know all of this seems crazy to like
somebody that might have just came on or
something but when you have
the rules to this
then now you begin to get some idea of
how you could trade this and what do i
mean by rules remember we said that if
this low was ran
this low here
we had this candle in the beginning if
this low is ran
which we had the run of this low here
we could potentially be shifting down
but after we ran this low what did we
have a push up
and we made a higher high now according
to institutional structure this low is
the protected low
but this low
signifies
some sort of trend reversal for me or
some sort of trend change intermediary
trend change
not necessarily overall trend change
because this may be
institutional structure on
a higher time frame here here
here this is the last low here so you
have this low this high this low and
then this high that was put in
so now if we run this low
which that's what we're doing now
now that could mean that institutional
structure
is shifting
the larger time frame structure
and what you could have
is that price trades up here shifts
below
and then
after it shifts below we get a
retracement back into this area here
and then
we get a short
to
run some of these lows
maybe this being the first low ran
we get a short here
but where could we possibly short to we
could run this low immediately touch
this line and then immediately push back
up
if you don't get a candle closure
below the low
then it's not a break of structure
i don't consider it a breakup structure
the candle needs to close below it to be
considered a breakup structure because
that's how you avoid less fake outs
so
you know as i mentioned i said that this
would
if this ran this like this with this
bearish engulfing candle you know that
price is going to continue to go through
the area
and what do we have we had a run all the
way into this area here
and we could potentially get a run of
the low
again
this is a wick that ran this low
like i said i need a body to close down
here and not a body to just close like
you know just over it i need a body to
close like further down like somewhere
in this area
if i get a body closure
then that's a break of structure for me
and
then price is reversing to go short
but
if price doesn't come back to this area
and break the low
i'm not expecting it to come short down
here i'm expecting it to continue long
and that's how you
you um
you know set up your rules
uh do you trade with real money right
now uh the watcher yes i i do trade um
with real money i don't trade prop firm
you know demo i'll use you know like
through the night if
if i'm just like trying to figure out
where something is gonna go and i want
some gratification for
for the trade actually playing out um
i'll use demo uh sometimes but um no i
only trade uh real capital
um if i'm not like learning
if i'm actually trading then it's just
real capital and it's my own money that
i'm using i'm not using um
a prop firm or or anything else and i
understand i'm not saying that it's it's
wrong for for um
you know other people to to use prop
firms because if you don't have access
to the capital then you know of course
is a no-brainer you can have a 200 000
account
if you are skilled enough to pass the
evaluation which those are nothing when
it comes to the way i trade here those
evaluations i i could probably do one in
the future um to show how easy they are
but um
you know you can take that
use that money to trade build up your
own account and then move forward with
your own account but i actually
started to um
build up my own account just using six
hundred dollars so i would use six
hundred dollars a day and i would make a
thousand dollars on oil just using six
hundred dollars and then i would move on
to
being able to like
you know
make larger amounts of money throughout
the day build my account
um take some stuff out for profit but
then now i'm so precise and fine-tuned
that i don't necessarily need a large
amount of money in my account if i have
a certain set amount of money i could
make
20 30 40 000 a day if i wanted to with
just a smaller portion of money rather
than having
all of the money in
in my account
so uh no i don't i don't know traders
reality um i've never heard of it is
that like some type of uh group or
something like that i'm not too sure
let me see if i could uh find them on
youtube
traitors reality
uh no actually i don't
yeah i don't know them let me turn that
off
look him up on youtube all right
let's uh
oh what happened here
sorry about that
so here he is
uh traitor's reality
let me just
take a look at this
um does he have any live trading let me
just
any live streams maybe
okay yeah he does
reversal i just
i mean so sorry about that guys i didn't
know that
the sound would
be like that let me just turn it up a
little
guys then we bit start looking towards
these previous vector zones that we've
been talking about in the streams over
the past few days okay
this is the last point for bitcoin to
show its worth
can bitcoin hold this point and i hope
it can ladies and gentlemen because
we've had too much blood on the streets
yeah he he has some um
pretty good analysis from what i'm
seeing here he is utilizing the
imbalance which you know i use at times
too i see him using a little volume um
actually with bitcoin he's on the daily
so
um
[Music]
let me actually go there
uh
so yeah it looks like
uh with coinbase this came down to 25
000. i did have it coming to this area
right here
you see this area i had it just
mitigating the area and maybe giving us
a balance to the upside this was clearly
a manipulation
you know with this like there's no way
you look at anywhere on the map and it
happens at the like the most high
profile
uh moments
um within some of this price movement so
this here
like there was
absolutely
nothing really in the market
like anything globally that should have
shifted price
um this way this is
i didn't expect this to happen but now i
do have it to where if it runs
um this high here then we can get a
retracement back into this area and then
we can go along
so
he's right about this area holding this
area would need to hold give us a
bullish flip and then take us further up
but it could just come back into this
area here
um into the 39 area and possibly
uh
here to the 45 area
so these are two areas the the 39 and
the 45 46 area
bitcoin could possibly bounce back up to
have a huge push-up and then a
continuation down
so if there's anybody that got in at
these areas or maybe these areas up here
it'd be back to break even but if
anybody bought down here they could sell
out you know kind of like up here or
maybe up here but yeah i'm gonna um
definitely look into that guy
you know just to
like learn a little bit more about him
because a lot of the streamers i tend to
watch a lot of them
and when i watch them
you know i kind of get an idea of what
the retail space is learning what people
are learning on trading and i try to
like
you know
shape those into better methods to trade
in like when i always talk about the
head and shoulders and all those double
bottoms those different patterns that
people trade
i can show you how to trade them
using better technicals
rather than just the shapes of the
pattern so um
you have mentioned luna
um
i'm guessing it's luna usd
damn luna went to hell
is this really in the negative let me
check another
chart maybe
whoa what the
yeah
i was actually gonna buy some luna up
here when i was like in the 70s
yo this is crazy
what a fall oh my gosh
see this is why you manage your wrist
though have those stop losses i'm sure
this probably happened real quick let me
go down to um the one minute time frame
and
oh we we do have so we do have a pop to
the upside okay that's this not looking
so bad but it looks worse than the fall
look at this
and mind you this is um
[Music]
this is one minute candles you know
wow
because look at how large they are
in the dissension
and then in the area that it finally
found support at i guess i could call
the support you know just
yeah this this is oh no this oh yikes oh
my gosh
any bag holders that were here you know
like
i'm i'm just
i want to say a prayer for you
you know i
i hope that god comforts your heart
because it's never coming back up here
again i can tell you that much
you might as well just get out of that
when when these happen
you know in in a lot of different
instruments
you will never
see the return of this again never like
this
for for all of existence
luna is never
returning to this market
ever again like
no
yeah it's over uh if you have any luna
and it's this in profit
you'll get rid of it if you want to day
trade it you can i will say that um let
me go to
yeah if you want to day trade this you
you can you know day trade it if you
want to
but it's
it's not looking
the best right now
you know like you
you could have a possible
uh
dip into this area
and then get like a little bounce up
you know or a possible dip into
this area because price didn't return
there after it flipped
and then possibly have like a
sorry about that a stronger bounce up
um to here if you were to trade this
using you know the one minute um
that's a possibility
um i would probably wait for it to
let's see
pushed up ran the high
came back into the area
so this ran
yeah back into this area you have this
short
that engaged from here see this stop is
too high though this is this is the stop
loss is way too high
and and then possibly like
targets somewhere out of the area maybe
this this structural low here
um you could potentially have that ran
because this was the low that
took out the load to the left that's a
possibility but
you know other than that there's there's
no way
i'm not that's coming back yeah 6
trillion is the supply yeah that's
that's way too much
unless they were looking for for it to
be a currency that they were adopting
to
to use in a specific car a specific
country and that country
you know
was was using it as a legal tender or
the other way that they could have
utilized this was that
they could have used this for a banking
infrastructure network like the u.s
federal reserve
to be able to
run most of the money that they have in
circulation electronically so
that would have been a way but yeah
that's that's way too much it lost all
its value over
um you know that excess imprinting
you know no function as of yet you know
there's a bunch of reasons as to why
um that
that happened but yeah you definitely
want to stay out of things that
that are over inflated like that that's
why i told people doge isn't going
anywhere
doge is going to stay
exactly where it's at or get worse
because there's no function there's no
utility other than what sending money to
someone else that they don't have to use
that there's so many other coins that
are way faster
than doge
you know so that's just something that
that you um
want to consider
when
when buying these these cryptocurrencies
you just want to be careful of that so
this could
this could either
uh go here
to again assume the high
or this can just be coming to this line
here
to
to continue running the lows
that's a potential
so if it does that then
you know you could expect
a bearish continuation into this area
yeah that's it was under a million
before the crash so it seems like
somebody you know there's a quick amount
of money somebody got out of that if it
was under a million and it printed to
six trillion that's that's crazy
but um
this is the end of my stream guys you
know always love talking with you guys
engaging with you guys i think i want to
push the stream back further than 9 30
because i see that a lot of people
they're still on throughout like you
know the the 10 30
time frame or or even 11 30 there's more
engagement that starts then so
um you know i'm thinking about moving
the stream back
for a certain time uh did i see your
question do you know about the lovely
market makers yes i do know about the
market makers
um
you know and the way they do things to
their job is to balance the market but
they tend to manipulate it a lot on the
behalf of
um certain clients so
you know i do know about them yes
um
but again uh you know i'm here every day
9 30 to 11 30. i'm thinking of moving it
back to maybe 10 or 10 30 so things are
a bit calmer and i could immediately
come into the market and start teaching
and then you know i could end somewhere
around one
you know so there's there's a lot more
opportunity to get into more trades
between 11
and 2 o'clock
because those are the steady hours of
trading and the more volatile hours come
in between two to four and
nine to eleven o'clock so i can do that
if if that's a better way to teach and
and it's a slower way to help people
learn
um and utilize these concepts
yeah that's exactly what it is it's it's
the liquidity providers that
that they're definitely making money
on the behalf of their clients as well
as
you know screwing over the retail
investor so
yes they they do manipulate price you
know a lot um especially citadel citadel
blackrock all those different companies
they they are not working for us at all
so anything that they're doing you want
to pay attention to and guard yourself
from those practices because their only
job is to create profit for the people
that they're working for
so um or or the special interests that
they're on the behalf of
so um i'll be back here tomorrow
probably 10
um like i said you guys can reach out to
me on instagram on twitter on telegram
all my links are in the about page i do
this every day all day this is my whole
life so if you guys ever want to reach
out and ask any questions in regards to
anything you guys could always
you know just
come there and and you know i'll always
be willing to analyze anything real
quick analyzing takes less than two
minutes for me so um you know you guys
could always reach out to me then if you
like what you saw you could hit the like
button subscribe and
turn on the notification bell i'll
probably do some surprise streams in the
future but this is the format that we do
streams in every single day and we have
so many trades here that you can take
and
actually be profitable with you know i'm
always just helping you to nurse the
trade helping you to understand the
direction the timing the the flips the
momentum this channel is specifically
for
education and it's education the right
way
not
education the shortcut way so i'm
glad that you guys stuck around you guys
listened in i hope you guys learned
something from this if you did
don't hesitate to hit the like button
and i'll see you guys tomorrow at 10