oh
[Music]
let me actually check
the uh
the sound
where everest my phone has gone
um
hold on guys
mmm
so bad
oh yeah
all right what do we have here
[Music]
let me actually bring this music down
soon
all right there we go
hopefully things are looking a bit
smoother
uh you see the rejection
here look at that
straight up straight down
rejected in the middle of here
always good to pay attention to that i
came what's up how's everything you know
thursdays are usually uh
uh being
less engagement kind of days you know so
i'm happy when i
see good people coming
oh man what a night how was your night
uh
how's your morning been
i just got my coffee i'm actually trying
to finish it before
they come in with the questions
tell me why
i was in jamaica and
i got some blue mountain coffee and
the quality isn't even the same nothing
they really make out there is the same
you know anymore i don't know if they're
commercializing or what but
the quality was not the same
all right
you know i always wonder if i should
catch the um
the thursday
uh crowd
uh later in the evening
because i realize thursday
is a struggle for
most people to get up and
you know
take care of their priorities you know
friday is coming at the end of the week
and thursday is usually a struggle
look at this
so does angela go from
there to there
yep so that top the imbalance there
morning sean what's up how's everything
gonna wait a little bit to do the top
down
i just want to get a couple more people
in
yeah i swear
the market is something else
you know like once
once you learn that algorithm oh my gosh
it just goes
it's like it goes everywhere you tell it
to go
man
i gotta stop drawing these so far out
though
i'm gonna um start uh
next week i'll start
you know some um private zooms
uh like
specifically for the individual
and um
you know people that i think that are
um kind of far ahead
uh i think i'm gonna teach them
you know like or try to get in
everything that that i know
um because i want
you know people to be able to teach this
to other people you know like for me i
can't
something can happen to me tomorrow and
you know who's out there really doing
this
not a lot of people
you know so
i want to um
be able to teach that just so more
people know
what's up good morning berea good
morning i say berea because i don't know
is it
good morning how's everything
exactly that's exactly how i see it as
as passing it on like
you know i i wholeheartedly believe in
that you know
like i said anything can happen to me
and
then what what benefit does anybody have
with with this i
i go with it you know always say that um
the graveyard is the richest place in
the world
because um
you have so many unwritten books
and so many you know
unreal some so many recipes that were
not passed down so many
movies that were not created songs not
written like
ideas sat on
and all of it
it's with them you know uh
that's good i'm glad to hear that
everything is good in here
um
how old are you if the minus accident
i'm 30 30. i just turned 30 uh uh
january just now so
you know i know that forex space is
filled with um
a lot of younger guys um
and there's a lot of older guys in the
the evening crowd i think that just has
to do with um
them having to work during the day and
only having time to trade in the evening
but
yeah i'm like in between the space of
like the older people who trade and
the younger people who are like
influencing with it
so again this this whole thing here
you know ranging sideways totally
tradeable
easier trade amari what's up how's
everything easy to trade i actually have
my um
so when you see me look down i have the
chat right in front of me so i can be
more responsive to people as they're
writing
um
but yeah this this is totally tradable
you know within all of this the the
market opened and i these lines are all
here because i literally called all of
this
just like where it's going after it taps
there you know then it came down here i
said it could tap this fractal and i
said if it comes back up here you could
probably tap into this s and d but if it
goes past this it'll come into the
imbalance here got to tap of the
imbalance got the equal high too
so you know we're running the lows
we ran both the lows this one and this
one
tapped into this area that i had when
the market opened
um
now it's just you know moving between
this low
and this last high
so essentially you would just wait
not like the retail wait for the
breakout but this is this is where it's
at it's within this area
um
you know so you can just wait um
for this to come out of course
but if it does go above
this um
all of this is mitigated up here already
so if it does go above this it could
likely try to take the high
because all of this up here already got
mitigated
within this area
let me see
yes yes that's exactly what we are keep
we're the bridge yes
and the problem with it is that the
bridge
it's often made to transport on top of
so
we get trampled by both generations
gen z the boomer generation we just like
we just get slapped back and forth
between them you know
it's either we're too old or too young
yes that's exactly it
yeah we're here in the middle
it's like the middle child feeling of
the world at least
i'm going to do the top down in a few
guys
like i mentioned the top down is always
always important
always
um let me actually see how long this
delay is
all right they did the delay is not that
bad this is great
you see what i'm saying
this is why you pay attention to
mitigated areas
i said that
if it runs this high
it's probably going to try to come up
here and take this high now we just made
an equal high impact remember equal
highs
are usually
you know liquidity
that's being stored
so usually before they run a high
they'll get to it push away from it you
know momentarily and then oftentimes
come back and run it um
but i have mentioned that
you know this area was already mitigated
here
so if it took this high you could expect
that push up to here but once you saw
this this little rejection you already
know that um ict actually teaches
something called inducement i believe it
is
um
i don't know if there's another word for
it for for other traders but you know
inducement is essentially
the concept of price
trading to take out the high
and what you have is
people see it going to that direction
and they want to jump in to go just
above the high
and then price trades away from the high
and once they see it trade away from the
high
they're in drawdown and they jump out
then they try to jump into a
cell and take the cell down now it's
buying back up
you know like it's it's kind of like
that um so it's based on our psychology
you know like humans we have this fear
of missing out
fomo they call it you know and that's a
very real thing we do have the fear of
missing out look at all the homes that
they're buying and look at exactly
exactly
activating buy stops after taking the
high see i didn't want to explain it in
that technical way you know but yes yes
that's exactly what it is it's
you know buy stops up here you know
cell stops up here there's there's a
bunch of stuff here stop losses that are
back here
you know
people getting involved up here thinking
that it would run the low then it comes
takes them out
up here and they could possibly even
still reject from up here and take these
lows out as well you know but that's
exactly what it does like this is why i
said that um
pips of persia
has a good video on liquidity
and i mean once you understand liquidity
then
there's a lot of stuff that you like a
lot of trades that you tend to stay out
of or you know where it's going you know
how to
like attack that trait
you know so
that's a and i always say that you know
like any time you see a a long-standing
you know like low or or high that was
there that that like a lower high
that
that has to do with the structure
you know not just any lower high anyway
but that has to do with the structure
there's always a run of it and then a
huge push up you know so it could run
the low then have a huge push up
and then later on return to the low so
yeah it's activating you know the buy
stops
the sell stops you know depending on the
side of the market you're on like yeah
it's it's essentially trickery like that
that's all it really is you ever saw um
uh what's this guy uh
i forgot his name but i know a lot of
people you know play those little cup
games after him um
you know they have where they place
something on the table and they take the
cups and you know like you think it's
one and you you think you know it was
that one but then it's not open the cup
is not there start mixing it around
again open the cup again it's not there
but you swore it was under there you
know
that's exactly how the market is like
they they play on on your psychology
that same way
you know so
this is this is why
you know paying attention to to this
stuff is important like especially in
real time this is why i teach on the one
minute
rather than teaching on the higher time
frames because everything that happens
on this time frame regardless of where
we are in the chart regardless of
whether it's a reversal from the bottom
or the top or whatever you'll see on
every other time frame but why wait
10 15 trading days to understand one
concept when i could teach it all here
within like 30 minutes you know to an
hour
and then you can just come back and
learn it over and over and over again
you know and learn it in real time
that's why i do what i do because it's
real time
i don't believe back testing is helpful
yes
but i do not believe there's some people
that back test and they kill it
and then they come to the live markets
and it's like
they looking like scooby-doo out there
you know so
i pretty much try to break that barrier
between like
understanding things in real time
and and just like perfecting a strategy
over what has happened in the past
you know because you wanted like
liquidity grabs are there in the past
but they don't always look the same
so you just got to make sure that that
you understand that when you're back
testing yeah the the ict order block or
demand zone might be hit
you know but
when you come to the live market what
happens when it doesn't get hit
how do you respond to that
now you're kind of stuck between not
really knowing how to
you know manage yourself in in a trade
so this is why i like to teach in live
markets i get that it's you know
loquacious and and long-winded but
you know if you could sit and and learn
and just
watch what it is that's that's going on
then i'm telling you it it will change
your life forever
like you may not have enough time to do
that now but this can cause your life to
become
you know it can cause it to go in a
direction or in a way of now you have
time to do everything
you have a time to do whatever you want
now you have too much time on your hands
and everything that you do can be
replaced with a service
you know like
own personal cook
you know your own maid don't have to
worry about cleaning up behind the kids
you know have your own driver like those
things yeah that's that's not the goal
yeah some of those things could be you
know little superficial or whatever but
if it if it takes away from your time
and causes you not to be able to grow in
other areas
then that's not something that's good
for you and that's
95 or that's probably a little too low
99 of jobs out there
are like that 99
you work five days only to have two off
sometimes you work eight hours sometimes
you work 16 hours
sometimes the work is heavy sometimes
the work is lighter
all for the same pay
you know like no i i
like i want people to break out of that
because
you are worth millions of dollars to
that company
you are worth
millions of dollars
to that company your position alone
you're worth millions of dollars
so if you are indeed worth millions of
dollars to that company
why not go and create that for yourself
you know
and that's why we're here
what's up nicholas how's everything
that's why we're here
to
to learn this to master this
and then we create a freedom for
ourselves
i always say that um
washes and balance here between here
guys um you know but i ultimately
probably have it coming down into this
area um i often say
i'm good nicholas i'm good
happy to see you around i i love seeing
you i love your enthusiasm craig what's
up how's everything craig i was i was
extremely tired i meant to answer your
text but you killing it out there boy
you killing it
yeah craig craig is uh
got it uh i met um
you know when i traveled and uh
he's been on it like every day just
trying to learn and trying to master and
i know he's gonna get it you know he he
he already is further ahead than than
like
a lot of people who knew nothing about
it and just started learning he already
is further ahead than a lot of those
people you know so
craig keep coming through with your
enthusiasm and
and your hard work you're gonna get it
brother
you see what i mentioned here guys let
me see if it actually tapped
that um
that midway point
yeah look at that
see i said watch this imbalance guys and
went back to chat my mouth
these these imbalance plays a really
good like quick plays that you can just
grab a quick scalp from but this one
obviously took us above both highs
but this is this is what i'm talking
about with we're in balance and where
you know um
displacement and absorption
those things you want to make sure that
you you pay attention to or you try to
get within your um
you know style of trading because that
can be very very beneficial for you
uh in in the discord will there be a
live trading room yeah so um that's what
uh the the um
media guy is working on the
he's wondering if
there should be live channels in there
or not um i think that live channels
would be pretty cool to have pretty
important
um
you know so i i think that that's
something that we will do just in case
you know like there might be somebody
else that that wants to go live in there
i mean akeem could probably want to go
live in there and and you know just show
you guys some of the stuff that he's
working with you know and that not a
problem
you know so i think that that's a
component that we will have in um
the um
the
discord
let's do this top down now guys
no doubt akeem i'm glad to have you on
board
yeah so so oh that's right yesterday i
for remember how i told you guys that
media like like news events do not
matter
at all
i told you that you do not have to pay
attention to whether news is good or bad
technical analysis can
show you those things
so yesterday let me actually uh
where are we
let me show you guys this
let me um
let me actually bring this
uh
down bring that music down
let me show you guys this
uh why is this small
because we marked up areas yesterday
um
oh why did that just disappear
all right here we go
yeah we we marked up some areas
yesterday
um
that kind of you know displayed this
where is it let me see if i can find the
volume
yeah look at this hey guys
these are some areas that we marked up
yesterday
when we were doing the top down
so we mentioned that there would be a a
huge bounce off of 32
whatever it was i'll go back to the
chart now and show you guys
um
so here's where it was
we had mentioned
in the top down
we talked about this trend line and and
how they manipulate trend lines and
stuff
but um we had mentioned that we would
come down to
thirty
thirty thousand two fifty three
and we could potentially have a huge
reversal up
to the top of this area to take this
high
and if you look
we tapped right into this area
and pushed all the way up and
immediately took out the high now this
is when fomc started apparently
you know they raised the interest rates
and and there was some other discussion
about tackling inflation and what could
happen over the next month so you tend
to get a lot of that whip sawing
movement
you know um
tuesday we'll come back in a few minutes
all right no problem brother
uh yeah i just went untouched
yeah exactly the the top down i have
mentioned that how they usually you know
create or store up some liquidity around
here and they end up running it this was
the whole trend line i told you guys the
whole trend line can be ran
so look it taps right into this area and
pushed up immediately to this area
right here
from this to this
641 pips
if if you just you know this is why i
always say take a picture of the area
screenshot the area whatever it is you
need to do but i have mentioned that we
would probably come up to this area
first
and mitigate this area above
and then come down
news started we shot straight up tapped
into this area shot straight down where
did this area top
i had an imbalance all the way over here
this is why i say these areas you gotta
you guys got to pay attention to these
areas that are untouched because they
can surprisingly give you strong moves
out of the area and and you don't even
know why like oh it didn't hit a demand
zone or it didn't hit a supply zone in
the order block you know didn't hit a
fractal so
what what can it potentially hit like
you have those huge pushes from the
middle of some of these areas and you're
wondering
why did it just shoot up from
from just the middle of the area it
didn't find support on anything you know
and that's because these imbalances that
are here so this this imbalance is from
june 14th
and if you go all the way over
when price started to whip saw
so it hit the area that i said it was
coming to
and then it went straight to the next
target
what's the next target right here
this top this is the next target the
imbalance that's to the left
because everything else already is
mitigated through here
every maybe not this area here but
everything else is already mitigated so
why would you be looking i told you it
would run the whole trend line
so if it ran the whole trend line it
found some support right here
pushed back up and i put this when i saw
this accumulating here i actually put
this arrow here and i said it could
potentially go up and touch into
you know this snd that's right here
because everything else was already
mitigated this s d is mitigated this
one's mitigated this one's mitigated so
i said that it could potentially go up
touch into this s and d that's exactly
where it tapped bam right there
pushed away
had a second tap on on you know the line
that i originally drew to
you know had a little pump up but i
would have saw that this was only
attacking the imbalance that was here
would have got a short from the
imbalance and then look pushed all the
way down into the area that we marked up
and then immediately shot up there
and this is why top-down analysis is
very very important because yeah i mean
i'm not always right
but you have to consider
like if
if you guys are watching and seeing
somebody on stream like
you know call it from this direction or
that direction or that direction like at
some point like there has to be some
type of belief that yo nobody else is
doing this like
you know maybe i should
you know bunker down on whatever this
guy is teaching because
this is happening right in front of our
eyes
you know and that's why i do it to not
only you know prove
prove people wrong which i'm not
necessarily here to prove people wrong
i'm trying to my the end goal is to help
people become wealthy you know but
you know if you guys are seeing this
happening like i would double down on
this information i would double down on
on
you know what's being given because
like this type of quality
you know it's either you're paying for
some type of mentorship
you know for this or or you're just not
getting it at all
you know because i i remember all the
things that i've been taught and i still
see those things like do you know how
hard it is not to see a head and
shoulders pattern i still see head and
shoulders batteries i still see double
tops double bottoms i still see all of
that but now i see it from a different
view
now i understand that double bottoms are
manipulated double tops are manipulated
you know so
head and shoulders patterns they
they their absence of structure they
have no actual technical
um structure in it other than that you
can draw it and it looks like one
you know so
i still can't get rid of those things in
my head
but
you know when i learned how to
trade in the manner than a trade
i actually
you know was able to put some rules to
those things and then if price followed
those rules then it's like okay yeah
that's a head and shoulders pattern yeah
it's a double bottom yeah it's a double
top
and
it needs to have specific rules to it
now i don't use those patterns to trade
anymore but if if you
give your your patterns or whatever it
is you trade with some structural rules
then they could definitely work out for
you i do believe trend lines can work
out i'm not saying only use trend lines
but i do believe trend lines can work
out if you're using structure with it so
structure supply and demand
only thing you guys need only thing you
guys will ever need
so um
let's do this top down now uh i guess i
can delete all of this
um because i have a whole video
explaining this
so let me get this out of here
and um
[Music]
go to the daily now
what do we have
on the daily
well just more sell no sell-off sell-off
sell off
oh we did run this low
yeah sometimes
i told you whenever we run a low
sometimes you might have some lingering
around the low
and then price would just fall out of it
and that you know that can happen
sometimes too
like right here
you had to run of the low here
you had some lingering around
and you fell came back up a little more
lingering in the area this is a daily
candle by the way so
um you know one hour four hours these
are probably you know right across this
area and then
falls
i don't know why it happens that way
that's just something that i've noticed
um
so this was an area that i had price
going to
right here
yeah
this was an area that i had price going
to but if you look that full body is in
it so
i would actually
mark the low
of this area
because it looked like it looks like
that's what it's that's what it's
potentially coming for
or i would actually let me let me
actually put another line right here
um
here
yeah watch this top right here
because if you guys look
this remember i said these wicks can
sometimes be hidden supply and demand
zones
so we could have a tap off of this
or or even within this you can you could
even come i don't know like
50 of the way within this maybe
let me see
yeah it could even come 50 of the way
um within this let me actually put this
here a little price balloon
sorry i have like ocd sometimes so i
need to
get the exact number
come on stop shaking hand there we go
all right
so
[Music]
this is the daily
um if it passes through this then it's
probably just gonna
run this low here
um
and it could have a tap and a swado push
up so it's 879
768 and 653.
um
so let me go to the four hour now
and look across the way because we have
like nothing here
ah
so on the four hour look at this wow
on the four hour we have this here
we have this area what is this uh
8 23
on the 4r let me just mark this over
here
so we have an area at 8 23.
8 23. oh i forgot to turn back on the
music my bad yo
because my kid
is annoying so i understand
um
so we
oh look we just grabbed that low though
um
i told you sometimes we grab the low and
then have a push back up
so watch that let me go to the hourly so
we have this area here 823
um
and everything is all the way back here
jesus and the christ of nazareth
all right so this is the last down area
here so let's jeez these candles just
get longer and longer down here
so what number is this
uh
nine i'm 790
it looks like
do we have anything here
so 790
790.
doesn't this feel like the price is
right or something
okay
looks like we're pushing down to this 79
area here
uh now we got to go all the way back
here come on roll the wheel with me
everyone
the music sounds on brand right wow i
can't go back here on the 15 minute oh
my gosh
geez
all right yeah i have nothing back there
15 minute one allowed me to go there
guys so we are falling in this abyss
and we only have these larger time frame
areas to work with
um after that like i
i mean this is a lot of space within
here let me actually just um
place some
some lines here
um
remember these are just reaction areas
i would wait until the one minute shows
you
that it's reacting to reverse from these
areas that's what i would wait for
not not the actual touch of these areas
because these are higher time frame
areas so with the higher time frame
areas there could possibly be drawdown
on the lower time frame
while the higher time frame still looks
like it's just a wick that that went
through the area
so just uh be mindful of that
only on the one minute do we play like
the exact touch of it if it's anything
higher than that
then
you know we want to wait till we start
to see price flip
and when we start to see price flip
within that area that's when we make
that decision
not
from the higher time frames
so we want to see price
tap into one of our areas and then start
to sideways consolidate
um
did i ever
no but we've we pretty much was working
through this entire thing but yeah
obviously we're
we're shorting into some of these areas
that we just grabbed on the top down i
don't know did anybody need me to to
stop and let them screenshot the numbers
or something or did you guys
place them already
if anything they're right here again
these are higher time frame areas so
these higher time frame areas
you don't want to see a tap and go
because these areas are not from this
time frame the tap and go is on
the one minute i would even say the five
minute not these higher time frame areas
so
you're essentially looking for a
reversal point or a continuation
whenever it is that you're trading these
and sometimes within within these falls
be mindful of price doing this you see
this wick right here
be mindful of price
this wick here
be mindful of price doing things like
that um that's just to feel the
imbalance that's there so you have a
quick push up fills the imbalance and
then continues to trade away so just be
mindful um
when you see that huge push up on the
next candle that opens
see if i was on the 15 it could give me
a little more accurate
um
like a more accurate area to this but i
hate that trade-in view actually has
you know only a limited number of data
you can go back to
um 29 715 okay that that works
715 so that's about through here yeah
that that would that would be consistent
29 7 15 i think that's the
the middle of um the s d that i have on
the on the daily i think it is
so yeah see i i know you know what you
talking about brother
so that's that's overall um
the the area that price can bounce and
have that huge v-shape recovery or
reversal from
so price will create these little areas
here
continue to fall create some more of the
areas here continue to fall and then
you'll see price go up to those areas
and potentially react from those areas
too
so yeah
it um
let me actually place these numbers
closer for us to see so i don't have to
keep
scrolling out so bam
bam
and then this
remember this is the low let me actually
just make this red
so it stands out differently
and
then yeah so it already fell through
this
here
and and this is also what i love about
these reactionary areas um
what i love is the fact that
if you ever
like end up in drawdown
because this was a wrong area for you to
trade from you know or or you just
impulsively got in and still went
through oftentimes it does give you that
opportunity to get out at break even
oftentimes it goes back to the area or
get out like a little bit in profit as i
usually say
so um
yeah that's what i love about using
these zones that even when they go
through it oftentimes they return back
to it
yeah exactly exactly john those my
favorite areas
that's why i only only take trades from
those areas nowhere else like i'm not
not interested at all
um
i don't care what i see that's like
these areas are highly highly optimal
like you know the areas that you want to
um
wait hold on i think this is here
yeah the these are the areas that that
are highly optimal like the areas that
you want to make sure that
um you trade to and from because
they often give you that that chance of
redemption if you are wrong
rather than just chasing like some
people see this huge push up
and then they run and and they chase it
you know and they want to get in going
there and then the market just moves
back on them this way and they end up in
drawdown and they get out
and then like i said they get in the
cell
and then it starts to
log
when they now they cut two trades in a
loss
and then they wanted to see it go up a
little more and they started to see it
push up a little more
and then they got into a long and then
it tapped an area that they did not
recognize or know that it would probably
react from and then it starts selling
and
three trades in a row like you're just
out that fast account blown whatever it
is like happen that fast
because of your impulses
and that's how people are i'm you guys
didn't make me finish my coffee
unacceptable
see look you see how you had this bounce
on this area now with this i will say
that
this is why i go down to the lower time
frames
because on the lower time frames
with these areas they actually start to
just move up a bit like you'll see that
on a lower time frame might actually be
like 804
but
because it's from the higher time frame
um the the wicks that are used on the
higher time frame are often bodies on
the lower time frame so the bodies would
get me more accuracy
than
the um
the actual wicks would
and this is why you know with this these
are just areas
that you're looking for things to happen
and not necessarily the touch of the
line but if i find it on a one minute
then yes it's the touch of the line
let's see did this
nope
it wasn't there so oftentimes
the first you you'll see you'll see
three different types of reactions
within these zones let me actually say
this um
i think this would be good for for
people trading you see three different
types of reactions within these zones
the first one being hold on
the first one usually
usually is um let me actually move this
the first one usually is
the tap of
the smd zone
oftentimes you get a tap or you come
close to it and then like super close
i'm talking about like a pip or
something close and then you trade away
from it
so you either get the top or or just
like just below it but most times it's
it's the top usually get a rejection on
the top
usually the there's a there's a
rejection right and this is why i say
targets can be
you know um yeah it's it's the midway
most times when you're taking that trade
at a distance
but
targets can actually be
just
the bottom of the zone first
that's the first target
if you want to partial out whatever it
is you can do that on just the bottom of
the area alone the second area that's
usually hit
is the middle of the area
so when you grab this area you take the
middle of it sometimes it could even be
like the 60 70 percent
you take that area i'm talking about
just just
maybe the middle at least the middle and
above consider that
and that's the second type of touch
that you can get
where it taps into this area and trades
away
the third one that you can get
is that price can actually
just wick up above the area it can still
go above this area
and then
it doesn't close up there it immediately
starts to go down that is absorption
slim what's up how's everything man good
to see you brother
my face always lights up when you come
in how you doing man
lately i haven't been able to follow
your live streams
uh your live show
too much because of work
yes yes exactly yeah
you what soon has probably been since i
resigned you resigned slim
oh my gosh i'm happy that you you uh
chose yourself i'm happy about that
so
yeah hold on john um for me i like to
zoom in
one minute to be more accurate exactly i
like to zoom in and be more accurate on
one minute two john that's exactly it
like it it helps with accuracy you know
when you come to the lower time frames
now you can refine too much sometimes
and when you refine too much what could
eventually happen is that
you miss certain moves when you're
refining so low so you want to make sure
that your refinement stays usually i go
all the way down to the 15 when i'm
doing the top down and then i'll move
forward with trading just from the 15.
so
i usually refine to the 15 and then come
down to the one for entries but anything
on the one like using the one minute s d
zones to trade long from or short from
you know for quite a distance you don't
want to do that um unless you have a
higher time frame bias that exceeds it
like let me show you last night i took a
trade on um
uh gj
um
let me see where is it
i know i took this trade last night
better show up
oh right here right here yeah yeah this
is it
yeah
wait was this it it was on the 15 minute
i think
and i took this trade like like not even
following my rules
let's see yeah
so um
i saw price falling out of here
it was like like on on this particular
um
you know area here i saw a price falling
down this candle opened
and i was like um
yeah it was this candle that opened and
i was like you know what
you know it looks like it's going to tap
onto this area that's down here because
you know um it was an unmitigated area
so i said
maybe i should just take a short
directly to this
no wasn't this
i'm tripping like highly
that was another thing that i had it was
it was up here look at look at me acting
a fool explaining that was a real
explanation for that trade by the way
but that was not last night's trade
so okay it was here yeah yeah it was it
so um i went to the 15 minute and i took
this area right here this entire area
here
and i said um
price can potentially come down and tap
into this area but i was kind of looking
for um
if you look up here
yeah price was falling out of
this right here this is what it was it
was right up here it was risky risky by
the way because i'm getting in into the
middle of an area but since i saw on the
15 minute that it was potentially coming
down to here
i went with the 15 minute bias and i
actually just short it from here
now i would not recommend
anyone
just shorting because they know it's
going to an area or longing because they
know it's going to an area so i had a
short here and we were playing around
with in this area and i was like let me
just go to bed you know and i'll just
wait for price to to tap down here so i
woke up this morning and it actually
tapped um in this area and it was a very
small lot size that i took on this trade
i just wanted to
wake up to the satisfaction of being
right so
you know i
was able to just jump in on a quick
short you know up in this area um and i
saw all of these areas down here and of
course you you got little reactions from
these areas even this one here you know
this one might have scared people and
been like oh you know it's pushing up
it's about to flip in reverse but
the higher time frame is always king so
um i actually
um
stuck with a higher time frame bias um i
was probably already asleep somewhere
around oh yeah yeah it was it was moving
up here that's right so it was already
heading to sleep around this area um and
then price still came right down and
tapped into this but i always say that
you know
you got to make sure that when it taps
your area you want to see if it's
flipping bullish if it's not you could
stay in because look at where this
ultimately went
down here
so
from from a little trade that looks like
you know let me catch a ride to you know
like
what the absolute heck
is going on here you know like
like this is
this is crazy you just jumped in on a
little scalp and it just happened to so
you want to always make sure that the
time frame that you're trading from
you begin to see a bullish flip
within that time frame
and if you don't see the flip on that
higher time frame
then you're not getting out so if you go
to the 15 minute here
this is the area that we said price was
coming down to
right here
did we get a flip around here when we
tapped here we tapped into it went up
tapped into
the next area and then left
didn't even give us like any other
movement around here just began to shore
after tapping into the next area so on
this time frame
we didn't get any indication
that price wanted to flip bullish until
you know possibly somewhere down in this
area
and when you have that like huge push
out of the area i i talked to you about
like the the v-shape recovery so now you
could have it to where price taps up
into this area here
and comes back down into an area
somewhere below here
whether it's this area here
or this area here
it could potentially just run this high
tap into this area and then swing back
down into this area before
trading higher
or when it's coming down from from up
here it can just go straight down here
like run the low that could happen too
you know that's a possibility
because this is the last high
um that was put in so if this high is
ran then it flips bullish on this time
frame
you know but again it can just come tap
back up into this area
and and find the smd that's responsible
for the break of structure which is this
one here
you know it was this one um as well you
see price came up tapped into it and
went further but now it pushed through
that area um so this is another area
that it can give a reaction to like i
said it can go back down to this area
here
and then
come out of the area and trade further
to run the highs if
it's going to do that
you know it would do it within that
sequence
you know so um
if anybody trades this i would i would
you know look to get involved with that
but you want to see a flip with that if
you were in from up here and this pushed
into this area
and went back short again
you know that's fine i mean granted you
should have took profit down here or
somewhere within one of these areas but
you know like if you were within within
this area then you're just watching all
of this happen you want to see a flip on
your time frame that you're shorting
from to know whether you should get out
or not
and that's what some of this you know
would essentially show you so you put in
this low
you put in this high
you put in another low
and then you run that high so what do we
usually say when that high is ran we
come back into the area before trading
long
so if anybody was in this trade from up
here and they happen to come down here
but miss the area to take profit in and
it comes back to this area there's a
possibility that it comes back into this
area
and they could still maintain some of
their profit or they can just they could
have just gotten out in profit waited
until it came back up into this area and
then potentially
short it back down to recover the profit
that they lost and this is all from the
15 minute time frame
you know so
it's finding the higher time frame bias
and going with that
um let me actually go back to the chart
that i was using um
i have until september 2nd last day of
work to become extra profitable
well we're going to have some uh
some some live trading
um some uh
zoom
you know trading i'm i'm gonna you'll
probably select a few people that
you know feel like is is really
understanding and getting the concepts
and i'm gonna like teach them everything
i know in his totality
um so you guys can get out there and and
stream and and get like mass produce
this information get it out there for
everyone to to be able to
um particularly learn from
so you see we get the tap on the area
then we run the middle of the area
you know because it's actually it's
actually this area here if if i'm being
honest
yeah this area
but we tap into the middle of the area
and then we trade out
and then now potentially we could run
the area too come up into the one that's
directly above
here
and then what can we do start the whole
madness over again tap into the area
first at the tip of the area come back
down into this area
you know here
and then come back up and tap into like
the middle i told you it's anywhere from
the middle to like the the 90
often
tap back into that area
come back from that area back into an
area here like this is literally how
price can move
you know just just using these areas
like this is how it often moves
um
marine branch what's going on man what's
up what's up
what's up bahrain
um
hey man i'm from brazil just past
somebody thank you for yesterday's live
it helped me a lot hey man i'm glad that
it helped you i love you know hearing
how how this is actually doing things
for people because i see how much
garbage information is out there or or
information that's just undeveloped or
not even like processed fully and it
really trips people up and this is
people's money we're talking about you
know like hard-earned money that people
made to
to like
you know try and trade and and
learn this essentially so
you know for me i want to make sure that
whatever i'm given
i'm i'm treating it like it's my own
money that people are using and i don't
want to lose my money so i don't want
you to lose your money either so you're
welcome man uh uh you know be sure to
check the earn and learn section i will
say the june second and third stream is
is a really good stream too if if you
liked yesterdays the june 2nd and third
stream is like phenomenal amazing you
know so you you should check that out
too there's a lot of sauce in that
so um but thank you for that thank you
for for coming out and saying that
brother
let's see so
we go up
we tap into this area here
the middle point of this area
and and be sure to follow me on
instagram guys if if you have any
questions about charting any questions
about hey is this direction right or
wrong you know like and you guys will
get like the most up-to-date you know um
things when it comes to uh instagram as
well because
um i'm gonna start posting more on there
in terms of trading but then that that's
probably where i'll announce that the
discord is done start sending it out to
everybody and i just want to make sure
that the discord is not finished when i
have to go and like do something take
care of something i may not be able to
stream but you guys might be missing
some of that information so um you know
follow me on instagram i'll definitely
be able to analyze things for you that
you send to me you know just want a
quick chat i'm i'm down for that you
know but you know be sure to you know
just follow me on all social media
platforms i love talking with people
analyzing things for people um
giving people resources that will give
them the right information like i always
talk about smart money source and pips
of persia two great guys that teach
amazing concepts and that i've learned
some of my stuff from as well you know
in terms of like liquidity and stuff
i've learned that from them so you know
you guys want to check them out also
and uh if you if you like what you see
so far
go ahead and like that button hit that
like button like the video
subscribe if you haven't
and uh also turn on notification bell so
you can always get the most up-to-date
information every time i post on youtube
thanks walter i'll definitely be sure to
um to add you in there and again you
guys can reach out to me for anything i
love analyzing charts us 30 gold
whatever it is it doesn't matter
anything i love
just being able to analyze whatever it
is that that i'm looking at i'm actually
in love with charting so
you know you you guys will definitely
benefit from that
so you see how we got the rejection in
the middle of this area guys
you know i talked about
how we get different types of rejections
you know we get the midpoint of it
oftentimes we'll get the touch of it and
then sometimes we'll get the push right
through the area but it's not
necessarily the candle closure so
this is a supply area with this wick yes
but you also have
this area here too
this area is a supply area also you know
so you have one right in front of the
other this might have mitigated it just
a little bit but i kind of like to see
mitigations of at least like 50 60 or
more
to to like judge whether
like this is this is an area that has
mitigation already and there's there's
no reaction that's going to come from it
so i pretty much like the the the 50 of
this area
i like to see that but if anything it'll
come back up to possibly this area above
here you have another area right here
and again these these are targets as
well to trade too
you know if you're in from any of the
moves down here like this was a great i
mean i i teach this all the time on this
channel but i talk about these little
flips
you know you have price coming to this
area
let me show you guys real quick
so you have this low pudding
you have this high put in you have price
come into this area and we flip out of
this area here
so what does price do come back down
into this area i told you it can come in
all the way to like the 90 sometimes
and then
lungs out of the area to to an area
above let me get rid of this sorry about
that
yeah then it longs to an area right here
so all you do is
take the area left behind
right here
and you're looking
for sorry it's not here it's it's this
actually i'm tripping sorry about that
guys take the area that's left behind
right here
the area when it flips up take the area
that's left behind
and all you do is look for it to tap
into the area
and then take you out of the area and a
lot of the times what people tend to do
is the candle this is the red the the
bearish candle the bearish candle that
goes into the area
if you place a buy stop or buy limit
just above it
like here the momentum your your stops
would be like behind the the candle that
went into the area the momentum when
it's leaving the area can take you out
of that area
but if this bearish candle continues to
go down
you can just cancel the buy stop or the
sell stop
so now you you don't even have to bother
you know utilizing the the um
the buy stop or sell stop because price
is still melting through the area
and you would just realize that that was
an area that price was not going to
trade above so you could utilize that
she is a nicholas you you utilize that
to be able to um
you know get out of certain trades that
like this is if if you were in this
trade right here
and you placed you know your your order
here stops behind here
and you targeted you know you're
targeting whatever above it could even
be you know this particular area up here
you know possibility for price to come
to this area but this was the area that
i had mentioned that broke structure to
the downside so oftentimes this area
tends to be a little more
um have a little more importance
um than
you know any of the other areas because
it's the area that actually broke
structure now although this may be very
small you could still have a possibility
of making it up to this before it
rejects
back down you know to here so it's a
possibility
you know but yeah the these these little
techniques kind of keep you out of
you know being able to like like being
in losing trades you know it can cut it
down by like half you know just just
waiting for the candle that goes down
into the area
and then
having the push out of the area and you
get in on the momentum of the push out
of the area
rather than catching the falling knife
here because if this continues to go
down it just hits your stop loss you're
out
but
if you had put it above here yes it can
take you in and still come back for your
stop-loss and take you out yeah that's
true too and you're risking a little
more with this too because you see how
your stop-loss is 32 pips here versus
your stop being only 16 pips here so
there's there's more risk on a table
which would result in a lower lot size
but often times you know like if you're
right you have this momentum pushing out
of this area to the next possible area
you know that if it ran down into this
area and pushed back up out of the area
we could have a little resistance in
this s and d zone above here actually no
this is not i this is a line i drew
yeah so no um you know within this area
you see that if it pushed out of this
area and took this high then you know
it's going to trade back up above why
because there's mitigation
within these areas
all this is mitigated so at the your
target at least
could have been this high or even this
high because this mitigated this so you
take it at least been this high
or potentially up to the midway of this
s
or to this s and d here and see how we
just ran the high of this snd did a body
close above
uh yes it did so we could potentially
just be having a
rejection from this area
tap back into
you know some other area below here
this is mitigated
uh
yeah this is mitigated
this doesn't have mitigation you can see
some resistance down into this area but
then there's an imbalance between here
and here so watch that there could be a
reaction back into this area here
um but if
if it goes through this area then
i see it probably going here
and if it doesn't go here
then it looks like all of this is
already mitigated so um
you could potentially have it to where
it runs the low if it doesn't stop
through any of these areas uh here
so you you get this resistance here
because of this fractal
that's here
let me show you guys
this fractal
this
wick that went up price
opened up on the next candle and then it
went down so this is a
this pushed up and this created a down
move and then went up
so this essentially is like a
you know hidden area where there's a
demand below and that's for that goes
for all of these fractals
all of these fractals can be demand
areas below or supply areas above so you
can have price react off of the fractal
alone like here's another fractal here
now they don't hold as strong as the
full body snd zones you know but you
still get some type of reaction from
them sometimes you know so here's
another fractal here wick down wick
above and then there's another fractal
within this area here
and this is why i was saying that if it
doesn't hold it at any of these areas
then it could potentially look to run
the lows into this area because there's
mitigation here already there's
mitigation here already
there's this fractal this fractal and
this fractal let me actually move this
um
out the way
uh
yeah i gotta do better with um
with messing my charts up
uh let's see so look even here
this is this is what i try to explain
most times
to you guys you have this low you have
this high put in you have this low you
have this high put in slightly higher
than this but it's still a high put in
we run the low what do we do come back
into the area we came to about 70 80
percent of this area and then we traded
out of the area
so if anything
this could have been just a quick move
down to one of these areas whether it's
this fractal whether it's going to go to
this fractal it's a quick move out of
the area and if you understand
candlestick structure
that makes your trading so much more
powerful let me move this that makes
your trading so much more powerful with
candlestick structure because if you if
you look at it um
let's see it's
and then trade it below it so
[Music]
in terms of candlestick structure it was
this here
so if you were able to identify this in
real time then
you would have been able to grab a quick
1 to 4.6
quick 46 pips 10 pip stop loss
just noticing this and noticing that the
next area is potentially this fractal
that would have been a quick trade out
of the area
and you know that if there's a
equal high within this area it
oftentimes results in in the run of the
low
if it doesn't hold
within this area here
so
no knowing candlestick structure can
teach you that and in my may 13th video
that's um the video that i actually um
taught in depth candlestick structure
um so candlestick structure is is very
very important when it's around these
these like the areas of your entry so
you can find your entry just using
candlestick structure alone
if it gets to a certain area that you're
looking to trade from you could find
your entry from candlestick structure
so with this you have let me show you
with this you have this low
you have this high you have this low
then we run
the high
so we potentially have an area here
that has gone
unmitigated
let me
i don't know why this isn't
yeah we potentially have an area here
that's going to unmitigate it
here now depending on how this candle
moved
this could be mitigated because often
times you have it to where the candle
will go and break the high first
then come back into the area and then
push back up and you can't see that in
in reverse you can see that in in real
time maybe if you use the replay
function to show
how it
how it opened up let me see
yeah you see pushed up and came down
into the area mitigated the area and
then left so that's why you have price
didn't return to this area and continued
to trade up because it already mitigated
the area
so if you would have saw that and this
is what i'm talking about like being
able to spot things in real time and
quickly if you just saw that in real
time the move was here the stop was
behind here
and you're going up to the next
potential areas that price could
potentially go to so you have this area
you have this area
and you have
this area here being
this area here
that you could potentially
you know have targets going to
and you see that this is the last low
this is the last high
this is the last low here
so this area is very very critical
because we could potentially run this
high and if we run that high
where are we looking
for price to go
we're looking for price to potentially
go here
if we run if we run the high
could potentially tap into this area and
head back down and retrace somewhere
into an unmitigated area here
but if we get rejected from here
there's a possibility that this
rejection from up here is essentially
and i don't even know why i didn't
mention this to you guys there's an
imbalance right between here
in this area but if we get rejected from
up here and we begin to
take out some of these lows through here
then oftentimes what will happen is it
would result in the run of the load
because
this is a major area up here so you have
you have this protected low
you have a protected low here
you have another protected low here
so with these protected
highs and lows
um
one thing that i usually mention to
people let me actually just move this
over
one thing that i mentioned to people
with the protected highs and lows
is that
if price ends up running them now this
this is a protected law if price ends up
running them
then what usually can happen if this
comes down it could potentially have a
reaction at this area here
all right let me move this sorry
you could have a reaction at this area
here because this was the s and d that
broke
um
structure to the upside here
so um there could be a reaction
within this area
um
so with with these protected highs and
lows what happens is
if price runs these these these are the
areas where you know
big money smart money corporations banks
whatever you want to call them got
involved and they started to buy price
up
into the
the structural break above
they started to buy up into here sold
off a bit and then bought up into here
so oftentimes
these are protected and they're not
willing to allow price to go under here
because this is where the stop losses
are
but oftentimes if they do go below here
then you'll see that you might have a
retracement up into the area and it'll
continue to shore out of this area so
you just want to be mindful of of this
and this looks a little
this looks a little dodgy to me within
this area only because like you have
this huge selling off but then you have
some buying and then quick selling into
it and then we buy up and then we
quickly sell so this whole area here
um
maybe i can just take this and put it
around it um
i don't know let's see how it reacts to
the
the area here you see you see how i
mentioned that there could be a reaction
here but oftentimes with this like i
mentioned yesterday sometimes these are
placed as fake s and d zones
so with the fake s and d zones they
create them
and move out of the area and obviously
as retailers we're expecting to be able
to trade higher from it and we get
railed
because
usually the s and d zones are the zones
that there was a huge amount of selling
going into
and then you started seeing a huge
amount of buying coming out of
those zones are the zones that they have
their stops behind those are the zones
that you can you know kind of look for
uh reactions to come out of
you know so
let me see it you see how it touched
into this one here
and now you see the push up from this
zone right here this little one here
and it just railed through that one let
me see uh my honest opinion that area is
getting wiped out
that area never pushed up to any highs
yeah that's what i'm thinking you know
because trend line liquidity
usually there's some trend line
liquidity
that's involved then you have this like
push up from this little this little
consolidated area you have this huge
push-up usually you know that's a result
of um what do they call a displacement
and um
you you get a tap into you know whatever
zone that's up here
and then you get a huge selling out of
the area so yeah that that could
potentially um happen and yeah because
it didn't you know um take any highs i
always say that you know the equal lows
often the equal highs oftentimes result
in a run of the low sometimes being the
first low but we can't discount this s
and d here
right here within this area
because this is a protected low
so they could still be trying to take
out the highs
if they come back and find support
around the low that they originally had
to where they started to to
buy up into if you find support here
oftentimes you'll have that um
run some of the highs
that could potentially happen
so you know those are things that you
just want to pay attention to when you
get to some of these s d's you want to
see good s and d zones be zones where
they sold off into and immediately
started buying up
not to where they bought up and then
sold the next candle and then bought
after you know that tends to i mean it's
a little bit dodgy you know a little
sketchy like they did the same thing
here you see how they sold here they
bought here and then started selling off
again here so when you go up into this
area you realize that this is sort of
like a fake zone sort of and you might
have it to where price
pushes directly through that zone
because it's just a fake smd there
so you want to make sure that there's
there's at least some sizable movement
going into your zone and then
it goes out of it so that's a more
likely area than like a more likely area
here than you know an area like this
and that would help you stay out of you
know certain traits
but yeah that that's exactly what i was
saying um i came i'm i was thinking that
if we tapped up into this area here we
could potentially come down into these
areas and find support but if we don't
we'd end up running the lows
but you you just want to look at what
happens within those areas that you get
to
that's what you want to pay attention to
what is happening within the area that
i'm looking to get involved in and when
you see
a certain type of you know flip or or a
certain type of pattern that happens
within your area
that's when
you're going to involve yourself in it
but if you see that there are already
mitigations to your area if there are
mitigations that are there already
you're not looking to get involved in
that area yes this area is
you know a a quick it was a quick scalp
up you know if it tapped into this area
and you you had a huge push-up yeah
about a 40-pip scalp up
you know you can play that as a quick
move-up
you know from an area like this but
when you look at
you know the charts overall and you
begin to try to figure out like what's
going on with price you know within some
of these areas
you start to understand
from a larger standpoint what
potentially is happening so if you look
we had
we had this high put in
we had this low put in
then we ran this low
so after running the low we're coming
back up into the area and like i
mentioned you can come into like the 80
90 of the area sometimes so this is why
when people are using the fibonaccis and
they're saying it's
it's gonna go to the the 61.8
and and fall from there yes
there's a there's a possibility that
that happens and yes that happens more
time than not
but do not use that absence of structure
you have to make sure that you're using
it along with structure
to be able to benefit or from from a
tool like that to be able to benefit
from from utilizing something like that
you want to make sure that you're using
it with structure
not with
with you know just your own volition of
what you think price is going to do when
it gets to that area so we go up into
the 90 of the area here
and we reject away from it
now we know that we created this trend
line here
going up trend line liquidity going up
here right here could be a fake pump to
another touch of the trend line
and then
what you have happen is
sorry there was just noise that was
hearing yeah this could be a fake touch
to the
the the trend line you have a push up
and then what you have is a run of it
the same thing that happened yesterday
the the run of that that trend line that
we had you could potentially have that
so yeah let me um actually no we can't
even go to the higher time frames to
look at anything down here because
there's really nothing back there so
this is just on the higher time frames
that that we have these areas
and it's just you know some stuff within
here of course you could still scalp too
if you wanted to you know like i said
there was a touch of this zone
you know pushed up you're able to get a
quick scalp there um
there's an imbalance within here
within this area
um as well as um a fractal just below
the imbalance
you know so
maybe it could tap into the imbalance
you know stops behind the fractal and
then
have a
retracement up before coming down yeah
there's a possibility
you know even coming into this area here
like yeah so that would make the fractal
a little more likely because the fractal
is more so you know positioned within um
this area that price traded out of so
yeah that that's that could potentially
happen too let me see if i um
could actually take this
uh
yeah yeah
yeah okay yeah
so you could potentially have some sort
of reaction within this area if it does
come down here
you know you you could have a reaction
within this area remember we still have
this s and d holding we had a double
bounce on it so we want to look to
probably see if it's going to come up to
this fractal maybe hit the middle of
this imbalance here i got to do better
with moving my my lines out the way um
so we have three potential areas we have
this imbalance here
we have this fractal here
and then um
the snd above
so let's see what what we get within
this area and guys if you can uh go
ahead and like this video
is good for the algorithm you get
these videos out to some more of the the
other traders that are on the other side
of um
retail and smart money and it'll
actually give them
information that's like beneficial
to them beneficial to
to their life you know so you guys go
and do that let me go back and check go
real quick i'm
wondering if i
[Music]
so you see what i'm saying guys like oh
my gosh like this is
this is this is why the discord is going
to be powerful man oh my goodness
you know so
so i have price coming into this area
here um
and i essentially said if we tapped into
this area
we would go long from this area but i
first had us tapping into somewhere up
here
which
um probably more so did it run this low
so if it was this low if i saw it
actually run this low before coming here
then i would have had it going here see
i tapped my line exactly
if it ran this low i would have had it
coming up to here i didn't see it run
this low yet i just saw it tap into this
area and go up so if it ran this low i
would have been like okay we're probably
going to retrace into this area first
and then short and where we where would
we begin to short we would short from
here
to this area but i also had this line
and i said we could potentially come out
of this area and long above the high
either way even if my short was from
here
and
it didn't touch and it immediately went
to the area i still had a plan for when
price got to this area here
and what was the plan for when price got
to this area here the plan was that
price would tap into this area stops
behind the zone
and then you can take a long out of the
area to go up here
look at this this long is from last
night i like i always said i like to see
you like a double bottom within my area
or equal low within my area for price to
push up but if you look at this look
look at this this is this is crazy
this is from last night
into
actually early this morning
right now
this is thirty dollars that gold move
so that's about some people call it 300
pips some people call it 3 000 pips
depending on you know their metrics but
this pushed all the way up to this area
just from coming to an area that i
marked out
and i think i might have marked out this
area on a 15 minute
yeah right here on on the yeah it was
here i actually was this it was this i
said that you see this long wick right
here
from the top of this area to the bottom
of this area
i always say that i want to see
mitigation at least by 50 percent
at least
this tapped into this area
and then went long out of the area just
from the 15 minute time frame i noticed
this so i saw the break of this low
after taking this high i said okay if we
run this low we could potentially go
back up into this area and then short
but where can we find support down into
this area and then we long out of it
look at that that's that's wild exactly
on on a one lot
three thousand dollars on one lot just
finding this this huge move here and
this is just stuff that i randomly do
and go back and check later on i don't
i don't actually like you know i'm here
watching the charts and i'm like yeah
well gold is going to i don't trade gold
you know i really don't care for it i
love us 30. you know but i really don't
pay attention much to gold because
like i mean all you need is one
instrument one thing
you can find six
thousand different variations
for one
thing that you are trading
so
if if you can
find 6 000 trades within one instrument
why do you have to trade a bunch of
different things you don't need to why
why diverse
why diversify
just stick to one thing you you know
what's gonna happen with that one thing
stick to that so if gold falls back gold
could potentially have some
support here at this smd
that's here
i could potentially um
find some support here and then uh
continue to push up like this
but sometimes uh before i go to bed i
just look over the charts see what's
been going on maybe from a higher time
frame because the asian session is a
little bit slower and then i'm like okay
this could happen i could tap there and
then you know go to that area
let me come back tomorrow and see if it
happened
and then i come back and and these are
very real trades that people can be
taking you know like
this it's just i'm so random with it
these are things that if this was with
with uh uh
you know gj i was i was very random with
this even up here i was very random with
this said that it could tap into this
area possibly and then continue to short
out of the area
very very random i saw this equal high
here
oh boy when you see that equal high or
equal low in your area you know it's
about to blast off and once you see the
rejection out of that area yep you could
definitely look to run the lows at least
the first low at a second and i always
say that each and every time once you
see that you could expect
the if you didn't take any highs you
could see
that that low being ran so this is stuff
that
i'm just randomly throwing here like
there's there's no like uh let me
actually look at this see if i have any
trades within here no i don't i usually
send them to to my friends every now and
again or just sends them to people you
know being like oh this may happen i
don't know you know just
look at it yeah let's check back
tomorrow and and it happens that exact
way like almost always so i i know that
the discord is going to be very very
powerful
um for us because i just randomly go on
charts if anybody asked me for a chart
to look let me see there was um
this
no was it odd cat
was it there was somebody that asked me
some time ago about odd cad i think it
was
yes it was odd cad
so i had mentioned that
we could potentially shift up from this
area
and you know push back down but i had i
think i said overall that that we were
bearish on a day this is back to one of
my streams like it's it's all on there
you know and
you know we definitely tapped right into
my area
up here and then shifted downward and
this was just from a four-hour
perspective i've never
ever traded on cab before like ever like
some of these things that people ask me
to analyze
never ever trade it but
i i analyze i
you know i back test on i i make sure i
i sharpen my strategies just just
utilizing this but i don't see look this
is probably
yeah like this was early in the year
we're still using these kind of fibs
look at this this is so funny
yeah this is early in the year wha what
was i doing here
i don't know was i
i don't know what i was doing was i
fibbing the high and low here
was it like this
hey was that flipping the last high low
yeah i think you see
look i was taking the last high
in the last low
and saying that price would come and tap
the 61.8 percent and go
this is the type of trading that i was
doing um
you know within like when i was first
learning retail concepts i was utilizing
like stuff like this and i'm like okay
if attack taps to 61
then it could potentially go to the 27 i
think i used to say and i used to say if
it goes to 61 it might reverse from
there
this is so interesting that you can go
back and look at like the stuff you used
to do
you know versus
like what you do now there's there's so
much growth so much growth you know like
even utilizing like um
like these little order blocks at the
time i was learning order blocks and i'm
like oh okay if it taps here then you
could short from here look just rail
through that area
and tap the area above so this is this
was just the way that that i was
learning um
people here might not even know but you
got to pay attention you got to pay
thousands to learn what you yes this is
exactly what i'm saying
this is exactly what i'm saying you you
have to pay
thousands of dollars for this
information like like people charge so
much money to to share things like this
and and for me i'm just like i'm robin
hood not not the you know disabled to
buy button robin hood but like you know
i'm i'm robin hood like i'd rather
people know and understand this to gain
a sense of you know financial freedom
for their lives and i say that because
when when we have issues such as like
you know high crime rate and and and
like we're dealing with thefts at an
all-time high when it comes to like just
baby food and and just all these
different things you know a lot of it
comes from not being able to afford
those things and some jobs people are
working it's it's not enough look at
inflation man it's it's destroying some
people destroying families
and and i can't bear to know that that
you know
i might be
taking a vacation to jamaica every two
weeks or whatever it is but people are
suffering
you know like i can't stomach that i
know other people might be able to but i
cannot so i'm like you know what instead
of focusing on fatting in my pockets and
and you know like charging people for
something that
i don't necessarily you know need their
money for if i claim to be profitable
i would just go out there and
actually teach people
show them these things you know help
them to learn this i always tell people
go back and learn through through the
videos that i have go back and and watch
that stuff go back and you know like
there's so much information i'm talking
about and and you know i try to tell
people that i don't try to be you know
arrogant or cocky or anything like that
but
there is so much information in there
that it's literally like master classes
you know like that type of information
you cannot
come by for free you will not find it
and people will just give
small portions of it even if you are
paying for it and not give you the whole
thing
and for me you know i just want to make
sure that that people understand people
people learn people you know like
like find their way out of these things
you know and and for people who are
willing they have something that they
could learn that could take care of them
for the rest of their life tell me if
you apply yourself to this the rest of
your life
you can learn something from this you
see how i just mentioned that there was
an imbalance here i'll tell you guys be
mindful of the imbalance this right here
look at this
i have mentioned this imbalance and i
said that you know some imbalances you
tend to have reactions to
so if you see the tap within this area
we hit this area of imbalance
and look we traded all the way up to
where the next imbalance
that was here let's say you just traded
up to here let's say you just took it to
to
right here from the imbalance quick
scalp right up into this area you start
to see some resistance you got out
cool 30 pips
30 pips just from the top of this
imbalance
but you're you're aware of why there's
some push out of this area so if you
were in this short coming from here look
at this i keep talking about uh
these these uh these concepts i just see
them everywhere look head and shoulders
i can't get it out of my mind i don't
know why like it it's just
it's so funny that this happens like
so so yeah you you
you know they they believe that it's
it's coming back to you know where it
came from which it could potentially
come back to this area yeah but like i
said
we're using this absence of structure
it's like a 30 win rate on it there's no
way that that i would use this but you
know these things that i i make note of
and i mentioned to you you can go back
and look and see
you know like
see how how they react in in
what is a back testing
or
you could also utilize it
to be able to
you know like learn scalping techniques
from what forward testing
just see how they react to those areas
so you have another imbalance this here
this is actually when we first came on
and the market opened i had mentioned
that there was an imbalance here we
tapped into that area and look rejected
out of it then what do we do tap up into
this area here
within this area did we hit the line
exactly no but we went into this area
tapped in and look we got an equal high
here what do i say with the equal highs
equal highs often result in a run of the
low
we had a run of the low immediately
after
so i don't you know
i was on the i think i was doing the top
down um when this was happening but this
is something that i say over and over
and over and over again in all of these
videos it's i'm helping you to manage
your trades in real time helping you to
find areas to get in helping you to
understand that this is what happens and
price does this like each and every time
price does this you know you might have
like that that one or two percent you
know miss on it where it goes to it and
just like steamrolls through it whatever
like sometimes you have that but it like
i said one or two percent
so i'm telling you something that's
extremely efficient
extremely efficient and you could
utilize these things to be able to you
know like scalp from be able to like i
said
10 pips 20 pips
that's different to different account
sizes it means something different to
people but
those high value you know pips
you could have higher lot sizes on them
and just get a quick reaction out of the
area and you're good so let's say you
were on like a
you know a 10 lot you know and you just
took that quick quick scout from this
area to this area granted if you have no
spread then you took home you know this
300 dollars
if you do have a spread you might have
took home 250 on that but then when you
saw another top of the imbalance here
and you ended up taking it down and you
saw there was some resistance some
rejection there
420 bucks if you have a zero pip spread
and you might have to sacrifice some
more pips you know for for the spread if
you don't have a zero pip spread but
then that's like 350 380 bucks
on these little scalps
little scalps
and if you want like a point one to take
like the longer moves or or a 0.5 or
whatever it is you know you can do that
now i trade on
um
you know like a a
100 lot you know or sometimes 400 lot so
those values are a little bit different
for me um but so i don't i don't always
say i always said i need just 24 pips a
week depending on what lot i'm trading
on so yeah they they tend to be a lot
different well look at this stab here
guys watch this stab usually when you
have a stab of this
low and then quick trade away usually it
wants to go up so just pay attention to
that sometimes when it's consolidating
within this area that's just wipe off
happening within this area is weak to
strong hand transfer that's what wipe
off essentially is but you usually get
like a stab right below the area and
then a quick trade away above that kind
of gives you some indication that um it
wants to uh continue higher
so um just pay attention to that in the
areas of consolidation and that's from
the top side too as well sometimes it
happens on on the top side oftentimes
it's on the bottom side as well but just
you know pay attention to when that
happens because it's just a manipulation
of the low before it runs higher
so um
you know you also have this area within
here
this this s d where it can get rejected
from right here
just the zone
you know it can tap into the zone or it
could tap into you know um the uh uh the
candle
that's here as well
you know here here
you know so
i'm i i try to you know tell people that
these things happen over and over again
and you could utilize these areas as
scalps like these are high value areas
for you to just go in and out of the
market i don't stay into trades long you
know sometimes it might be three five
minutes sometimes
you know sometimes it could be just a
couple seconds because you know that
that reaction
just happened as a quick reaction and it
just took me in that area like if you
look here
if it tapped into my area and and traded
me away from this area by the time i get
down to this other smd here let's say i
held for those what three minutes
you know it's probably four four or five
minutes or so um
but let's say i held for that
just on a regular lot size that i use
this is nine thousand dollars
and i'm outta here three minutes nine
thousand dollars i think i sent uh
somebody on the chat i'm doing out him
but i sent him you know uh one of the
the trades um that i took
and i showed him that within three
minutes i don't know why this is here
what what is this doing here did i place
that there
i did not mean to place that there oh no
i moved it out the way um so yeah it
with the
the trade that i showed him it was
you know in three minutes it was six
thousand dollars in three minutes
you know like i don't know anybody that
has that type of
you know uh
minute salary or hourly salary or
anything like that the most i know
people making is like 300 an hour
sometimes if you're a great lawyer
you're like a thousand dollars an hour
you know but
even that becomes child play child's
play
compared to this so let's see you you
took you you had to tap on this line
here you push down all the way to this
area here
31 pips just on the top of that line
with 31 pips
and this is one candle
on my last size this is just three three
thousand dollars on one candle
this could be thirty dollars for someone
else this could be
you know three hundred dollars for
someone else
and whether it's three hundred dollars
whether it's thirty dollars that was in
one minute
which you have i don't know why this is
here what what exactly is uh is this the
imbalance that i drew
yeah yeah i think this is the imbalance
that i drew yeah so
that that could be thirty dollars in in
one minute
most people
that i know are we're not even most
people that i know are not making thirty
dollars an hour
an hour
and we're talking about your ability to
make it in a minute
that just off of these these little
you know high value moves
these little optimal moves
just off of that let's say we get
another scalp down here
look at
25 pips
just off of rejecting out of this
imbalance
25 pips
just over rejecting from there
i'm out bam
because i know what
it tapped this imbalance there was an
imbalance that was down here
and it came back to quickly fill that
imbalance
and then left
so if i had that in my mind and i saw it
when it happened
quick scalp i'm additive sayonara
and then remember what i mentioned about
this candlestick pattern here
where sometimes you have a run of the
high up here and then you have a short
coming out of the area
that's what you want to see sometimes
when you're grabbing these quick scalps
as well
if you're not comfortable with just the
touch of the line
then you can just wait until you see
that flick up above the wick here and
then trade below and if you waited on
that
you could have also had
33 pips
now if you understand that the numbers
that i'm using and and how all of this
is happening back to back to back to
back to back to back to back in real
time
in real time
you understand the richness
and the value
of this information
because this is just in real time mind
you this is an imbalance tap
look at where it's going look at how
it's falling
just from this imbalance alone
quickly saw that
quickly
saw the little candlestick pattern i
liked to happen and then we shorted out
of the area
was this two minutes
60 something pips in two minutes
six thousand dollars in two minutes six
hundred dollars in two minutes sixty
dollars in two minutes after you already
got thirty dollars here
and now you have 90 bucks in three
minutes
on a regular one lot
and and drawdown where
what
what drawdown
so this is why i want you guys to pay
attention to this because this is very
very real information that could
like
radically change the way that you trade
radically transform your life
to
you know maybe
trying to get out of a particular job or
position to now being able to
like create your own life create your
own routine daily
this is what
being able to master this and understand
this
this is what this affords you
this opportunity it affords you this
that you're able to work in a manner in
which you're very efficient within a
small area look at look at how long it's
been when did we come on stream
uh 10 maybe so i'll say right here
between 10
and 12 o'clock
so we've been on we've been on for two
hours hour and 50 minutes so so between
like within an hour and 50 minutes
look at how many trades
we were able to see
and and understand like
where price is tapping and and what's
particularly happening all of this over
here i have mentioned
you know that i saw all of this
happening in real time and you know i
have i had a little markup for it when i
initially came on um for you guys but
even within here i mentioned you have a
top of the area trade away you can tap
into the middle of the area and also
have another trade away but then you
tapped into this area and now you had a
long up here
then we took the high of this
this uh s and d so it gave us some
indication that it could potentially
trade higher because a body closed above
where did we go
we came down into this area
we tapped here for reasons i'm not sure
oh the the fractal we mentioned the
fractal was here so we tapped into this
area and then we pushed further above we
know we were going above this area here
because we had already closed the body
had already closed above so when we
pushed up to this area we talked about
potential areas where the price could
react from whether it was this line here
or this area above i said it could it
could react from just the candle or the
zone
we got a reaction from the zone
took us all the way back down here we
talked about the fake snd
we talked about
this area here where price could
potentially find some support on
but
then we mentioned that there was an
imbalance in between here and
potentially a fractal where price can
react from
so we had to trade away i told you if
you were in a short it's fine because
it's not giving you any indication that
it's flipping bullish so we tap into
this area
then we say okay there was an imbalance
here i have mentioned it this before it
even got here there's an imbalance here
price comes tap into the imbalance give
you a quick backup for a quick you know
um trade back up so you go from
imbalance to imbalance
you shift below you see we quickly run
the low and trade away from it
now we're looking where can we get
involved price is pushing up here
maybe you didn't get into the trade you
don't want to chase you get a reaction
out of this s and d back down into this
about 30 40 pips or so then we go up
into the imbalance up here
what did we do with the imbalance here
we tapped into it we traded away from it
where do we trade from imbalance to
imbalance
price comes back up
what do we have here
and i'm not saying use
imbalance for direction because
sometimes price doesn't always go back
to the imbalance right away
but the imbalances can be very helpful
so if you look here
there's an imbalance here price taps
into the area doesn't come to the 50 of
it
but then it trades away and it runs the
low
you know so if if if you're even
understanding that that according to
candlestick structure
this is making
you know higher
highs higher lows higher highs we run
the low we come back into the middle of
the area here
and then we trade below it
our first target is the low and possibly
coming further down this is
so this is gathering
imbalance
um what was it it was imbalance that we
mentioned we mentioned displacement we
mentioned you know protected highs and
lows so this is structure that creates
these protected highs and lows we talked
about equal highs if equal highs are
made then we could potentially run at
least one of the lows if not the second
low we talked like come on imbalance to
imbalance target to target like
all of these different things that we're
discussing in this one video
this one video and you can go back to it
and play it over and over and over again
and you can have your chart side by side
and you could actually see it on your
chart too it's something that you can go
back and test
it's factual
you can go back and test it i'm not i'm
not creating some small segment of a
video and telling you guys yeah if you
go back and look for this you know you
throw the fib to this high and this low
and it hit bam
and that hit was only one of the thirty
percent of the time that that happens
and everybody's thinking oh my gosh this
guy can trade wow so amazing
no
it's it's
it's just not a thing
that's not the way that that people are
supposed to be teaching that's not the
way that people are supposed to be
trading and this is why i do these
long-winded streams i get it it's very
long for some people to go back and
and watch because sometimes i go into my
little you know
rants and conspiracies and blah blah
blah but
it's still accurate information
accurate information that you could use
to further your trading
very very highly accurate information
and and if you get this in real time
then
you know that would be even more
priceless
to be able to have that in real time
because there's so many ways to approach
this particular trade here
because you see how i mentioned the
imbalance
now let's say i took
the high and the low of that area
i tap up into this i'm in a little bit
of drawdown
right here i'm in a little bit of
drawdown
you know 30 pip drawdown
but then we push out of the area
and
you know we're we're further into the
lower parts of the area so if i wanted
to use that i could
but you have to remember that
for me
i mean i say it all the time here on the
channel
i absolutely hate drawdown
like i hate it so much with everything
within me i
detest i'm disgusted by drawdown i do
not like drawdown at all and that's how
i learned to become so efficient with
trading
because of my disdain for drawdown
my disdain for losing i i'm not a sore
loser but
i like to perfect what it is that i'm
doing
so
that's how i was able to
you know start to learn this at within
such a short time
people take years to become profitable i
don't believe in that you don't need
years to become profitable with the
right information you can become
profitable within six months with
trading with me
and utilizing
you know some of the education that i
give in real time
you could be profitable within a month
like it could change your circumstance
but it's just if you're listening
to what i'm saying
listening to what i'm saying
watching it happen
and being able to take that and be like
okay i'm gonna run with that
i'm gonna manage my risk properly
because i don't know what you guys
account sizes are but i'm gonna manage
my risk properly maybe you guys can like
watch a video with um
with risk management and it'll teach you
how to manage your risk or each trade
that you're in it'll teach you how to
manage your your lots and stuff like
that to to help with
you know being able to take a trade know
how much you could potentially lose and
you know you look at what you're willing
to or what you stand to gain
you know so you can do that but if you
were just taking these trades from these
high probability areas that i discuss
look at this
this is a and five pips down
just from the top of this area and while
i'm just being loquacious and talking
105 pips down
six whatever you want to call it if
you're technical
and this is within nine minutes
so come on man
you made a hundred bucks
in in ten minutes
a hundred dollars in ten minutes
when most lawyers i know as i mentioned
their salary is 300 an hour
and you made that in 10 minutes
and some people make that in a days of
work
or or four hours of work
you know if if they're getting paid
pretty well
but this this changes the trajectory of
just
you being able to
[Music]
to like
just use this as like some side
investing to making it your lifestyle
because now you understand from from
just a different standpoint
you understand things and and you're
able to generate money just with your
brain what you're thinking
which you're thinking you're generating
money
guess what that is the 61.8 percent of
the range right in the imbalance exactly
and this is what i'm saying there's so
many
variations to one instrument
that you do not need to trade a bunch of
different things you can just take the
one thing that you like and you like the
way it moves fast or it moves slow or
whatever it is and apply these same
principles to and be profitable
and this is
free information it's free i teach this
and put this on youtube
every day
free 99 free
life-changing information for free this
is what i always say do not listen to
those stupid videos that
they tell you
you know these millionaire motivational
videos yeah you know me
millionaire you can be a millionaire
all you gotta do is put in the practice
put in the time put in the energy put in
the effort you gotta press through you
gotta push past your circumstances you
gotta realign and sacrifice all of those
things are great amazing awesome we love
it tell us how tell us where we're
putting that information to
tell us where we're putting our effort
to what where we're getting our
information from
tell us how to do it not just tell us
the the
the energy where with all the motivation
we need behind it
don't just tell us that
tell us
how to get there not just not just the
the mindset we need millionaire mindset
motivation blah blah people hear that
all the time and be like yeah i'm gonna
be rich one day
and then they go back to like not
putting that energy into anything
watching
you know netflix more than that
putting time into whatever their craft
is or or
you know like they don't spend enough
time
doing these things
to to actually become proficient at what
it is that they're learning
they and then they go on and they throw
on that millionaire motivation mindset
you know video
and they hear that speech and they feel
pumped for the day and they're like yeah
get into the bag the money you know all
that stuff that they say
to get into that which which is amazing
if you're getting to it you know like
yeah get to it feed your family do what
you got to do but understand that
i don't want anybody having
the control
of
being able to dictate
whether my kids eat or not
whether i get a good night's sleep or
not
whether i can attend to and whether i
can tend to an emergency or not
i don't want that power in someone
else's hand
because absolute power
corrupts
it really does corrupt
absolute power corrupts
you know like if you have the ability or
the advantage to to
like get into to whatever it is and you
have total control over it
it can corrupt
it's very very real it can corrupt
you know and and people don't understand
that but it's
it's the truth behind it and that's why
we have these jobs that we we end up in
these situations where things start off
great and then
it's like they understand that that
you need the job to feed your kids so
what do they do
they your humanity now
is
that they know you need them more than
they need you
and they begin to treat things that way
they begin to treat you that way started
off great but now it feels like a
horrible environment to be in but you
know your kids depend on it so you gotta
put up with it why don't i take that
type of stress
and put it in the markets
let the markets give me that stress when
i'm learning
it stresses me out enough
my kid is over at copying me while i'm
talking to you guys
but yes
why why not do that look so you see how
i put this line here and i mentioned
look at this 23 pips off the top of this
alone
off the top of this alone
23 pips i told you guys i just need 24
for the week
and i'm good
23 pips
off that top alone
and you quick with it
go in get it out
and it's all off of principles that you
have learned
things that you have seen over time that
you've seen happen over and over and
over again i told you whenever you see
this huge push-up followed by this huge
push down and you got both candles side
by side together like this i don't know
if it's on a lower time frame maybe or
something like that
and this is the one minute so it could
be like on a 15 second or five second
there's always something in here that
when price comes up into it you get a
tap in that area and a rejection out
even if it goes and takes the area you
still get a rejection from somewhere
within there and it could just be on a
lower time frame that there's something
in there that taps into and rejects away
from the same way we see the rejections
from you know these different areas that
we draw
nonetheless
you still
get a reaction from it
so if if you have this in the back of
your mind
quick thinking says yes you can get a
reaction look at it look at it on the
downside right here
look at it on the downside
you have this push down followed by this
push-up
price comes back in
taps into the area and then rejects
i don't know why this happens i don't
and usually it's it's it's when the
areas are slim like you have a
push a push up and then a push down and
also a trade away from it so there's
some space around it
usually you get a push back up into that
area tap
quick short out of the area
quick like that
so your scalping becomes different your
scalping is no longer oh i see it
dropping let me jump in and take it more
no your scalping is at high probability
areas
so we always mention
that when we get a run of the high
oftentimes we have a pullback
we also
say that oftentimes
when you get just a wick above the high
and then price starts to pull away from
it
oftentimes
that's a quick short out of the area
so you can get in on a quick scalp
but you have to make sure
that
there are targets down below what is the
target down below for this
here
mind blowing information
mind
blowing exactly it's an ict order block
on the seconds time frame
but mind-blowing information
mind-blowing why
look at this tap into this area
this one did not touch it
price went up
and came back to this area
tapped this area exactly
look at this
three pip three pips
draw down what touches this area and
pushes back up
42 pips
in two minutes
and i teach this stuff for free i i
i and if you go through my videos go
through the stuff that that that i have
placed there
you guys will see
that this stuff happens over and over
and over and over and over and over
again
bear market bull market over and over
and over again
over and over again
this could potentially be white golf
happening
right here
this could potentially be like off
you can get a dip into this area a tap
here or even a dip below it to tap this
line you know maybe just go below it
then i'm push back up
above
this here
if it taps below this you could get a
push back up above 904
and then
you might get another dip further into
these areas
before potentially going long out of the
area
but this is the area that
price traded out of when the market
opened
so we had some falling
we had price come back up to the area
and get rejected we could very well be
looking to
run this low overall
so whoever was in this short from here
they're still seeing that you know price
made its way up here put in a high
put in a low
ran the low
now is looking to potentially put in
another high
maybe within these areas
and then ultimately put in another low
so you're so fine if you if you were in
from up here and you you've got this top
like i said some of these taps can turn
into longer moves
some of these scalps can turn into
longer moves depending on how fast they
trade away and they don't come back
some of them can turn into longer moves
and it's just using these these high
probability areas these optimal zones
just using that alone
and once you once you're able to use
that and trade from that you start to
see things differently and this is why i
want to do a zoom soon of just teaching
zones
only zones i teach a bunch of stuff here
i teach zones i teach candlestick
structure i teach how to find an entry
you know what you're looking for when
price you know moves out of a particular
area so when it grabs a high usually
dips back into the area and if it finds
some support within that area
potentially runs the the other high that
that ran the previous high sometimes
that can happen so there's a bunch of
stuff i teach liquidity you know trend
line liquidity and like there's so much
that i teach on this channel is crazy um
but jones it seems like zones is
something that
that
or zones can be something that people
have the most difficulty with
so people are understanding the
candlestick structure that i talk about
here like this this is literally it
i i taught this on the the may 13th
video and i think the june second and
third video let me go back and make sure
june 2nd and 3rd is correct instead of
like hoping that it's not a weekend yeah
yeah thursday and friday
yeah
so
so i um i taught on on those videos the
the candlestick structure
and if you look
is this low put in
this high put in
this low put in
we have a run
of the high
so anytime we have a run of a high we're
actually looking for price to trade back
into the area here
and then this is where we get in
to go long
up here
so if we got in at this area
we're essentially looking to target the
high
but oftentimes you have a second touch
within the area that can still take you
up to a higher area to a higher area as
well
you tend to have that sometimes i told
you there's sometimes a um
like almost like an equal low or a
double bottom within your area of
interest so the first one usually is a
scalp the second one usually is a longer
trade out of the area
but both of them you want to see a quick
pull away from that area and once you
get that quick pull away from the area
then you understand that you could be in
for for a little longer
you know so
this one here
we just grab this high here
now with us grabbing this high
if we closed above it
then
that's a good sign
but if we just grabbed the high and
quickly traded away from and it was like
a huge wick you know left here then
obviously that's something that you know
you don't want to look for price going
higher look we just got that close above
and then we
and then we took out the high here so
instead if you tap into here you could
potentially come up and take out the
high that took out the previous high we
just watched it all happen just like
that
like just now
you know i hope that people like when
they listen to what i'm saying even if
they don't always like agree with a
hundred percent of it i hope that you
guys can understand that there is
so much quality
in the stuff that i'm saying like so
much
quality oh my gosh
just so much quality in in this in this
information that that i'm giving like i
really want you guys to unders look at
this rejection from this area
look at this
like this
and this has happened so many times on
stream look at the rejection from this
area
within one
minute
one minute
there's so much free sauce
sometimes i'm right into the scammers
and i'm like hey guys i know how to
trade i'll teach you for free just watch
my channel watch my stream you guys
could learn and get the right
information out to people
i'm always writing on their pages like
yo man
there's some great information here i
see that you called this out
and it wasn't that
you know you called out a losing trade
if you just learn how to fine-tune
what you're doing and you learn how to
actually analyze the charts
you can be calling some bangers people
will like
love your mentorship you could make so
much money even if you didn't want to
trade
but you can give people the right
information and you won't be you know
losing so many people
like i'll be trying to save all these
guys like come on this this is the right
information this yeah there's people out
here scamming but understand that these
banks scam way more than these people
these these governments scam way more
than these people out there scamming for
a quick buck both of them are wrong
but the government scams hurt society
way more than the scams that that some
of these guys are running some of these
guys are just trying to survive
but you don't have to survive giving
people the wrong information
you can give people the right
information too and survive
you know so
that's just something that
that i want people to
understand you know like i really want
people to to
like get
get a gist of to understand so look you
have this area here
you have this area here and then you
have another area above
uh
here maybe
no this this looks like this mid this is
mitigated already
i think there's a possibility of this
area being mitigated so just um
be
careful with this area
here
um the one up here
um
because price traded below this low and
then came back into the area before
leaving
and i guess that's what left the
imbalance it tapped off the imbalance
and pushed away come on look at this
look at this y'all look at
this is sauce guys
sauce like
diamond sauce look at this it tapped
this line and pushed away
this is oh my gosh man this is
wow
we're watching this stuff happen live
this is why i'm telling you guys
like share this information with other
people share the channel with other
people if you're in little telegram
groups share about how helpful these
things are if you're in facebook groups
reddit groups whatever it is hey this
guy's stream is helpful this guy's
stream is amazing i've learned some
great if you have learned some great
stuff if you haven't don't go out there
lying to people you know just to just to
do what i'm asking you know like if you
haven't learned anything from this if
you felt like this was poor information
you know for you you really didn't
understand what i was saying or doing
then don't share it you know but
if you have if there is any
um
substance
in what you've learned
don't hesitate to share this
like there's so much good information
that other people can get even if all of
us became profitable in this market
it's still not enough to move this
market
because these this is a market that
banks are trading and that hedge funds
are trading in
so
share this information with people
like
they they can learn from this too
i remember when i first started trading
um
you know i used to ask certain people
you know like what trades were they
taking if they could teach me whatever
it is
there was just like
never any enthusiasm to to like actually
teach me what i needed to know and
you know
i was a little discouraged i will say
that i was a little discouraged because
i mean i was just trying to find my way
and it led me to like going to learn
other groups and going to learn from
other groups and learn you know from
their trading styles and stuff and
you know it was it was just
it wasn't working
so there was people that had the
knowledge and was making money wouldn't
give it to me
or wouldn't at least teach me i was
willing to learn willing to pay for it
so they had information would not share
it with me
and then
you also had people who
you know like
they cut it out everybody making noise
because you want my attention then then
you have people who did not know what
they were talking about and were
teaching
and they didn't know what they were
talking about
like didn't know what they were talking
about at all
and
and and i understand the the um
the i don't know how i should say it
i understand the
the effort made
to to like help and teach and and and
you know like
teach people through things but if you
understand that that you're even afraid
when you're in a trade or you may not
know where price is going or it's
difficult for you to find a setup
whenever you come into
you know like in
an area like this or a chart or whatever
on any time frame if
if your comfortability is only trading
on one time frame
rather than
all of the time frames you know or or if
you don't have like your stuff down pat
to where you're you're
winning
i mean you're you're you're and you end
up losing more than you're winning if if
that's you
then you should not be teaching
you should not be mentoring you should
like there's more
to learn because this is
as we always mentioned
this is people's money on the line
people's money
is on the line
not just
you know
not just your popularity or or
whatever you can make from it or
whatever it is we're talking about
people's money that's on the line
you know like you you can't play around
with that
you know so for me i got a lot of
misguided information when i first
learned look at this i told you guys
these wicks sometimes could be hidden
um s and d zones
so you see how this taps up into the
zone gets rid there's the same thing
here same thing that we mentioned here
tapped up into the zone rejected tapped
up into the hidden smd zone reject it
you're like these are things that you
you guys want to pay attention to so if
you look there was a trade from here
going down to the next s d zone above
and then i mean we were talking so i
didn't really uh note this area but then
there was this other smd here tap out of
it again another 48. so so you
understand how you know like when i tell
people you know when i share with them
what i kind of make per day and stuff um
and what i choose to sometimes make per
day i show
like how easy it is
when it comes to these are all scalps i
don't even remember how many scallops we
even mentioned was was within these
areas from the imbalances to the top of
the zones the top of the
the uh order blocks or you know the top
of the
the uh
supply and demand areas the like
there's so many areas that price we see
price react from
and all we need is just the reaction
we don't need anything else we just need
to reaction
there's there's a lot of pips that you
can garner trading on this and when i
first started learning this people told
me that this was the hardest thing to
trade
because this is equivalent to like spy
if you trade options on the stock market
it's equivalent to spy do you think the
price respects and balances during
um new york stock exchange open um yes
you you do have it um to where price um
uh it certainly um
respects that because look at this right
here
let me move this here
i hate moving these lines because
you know they take away the history of
what i've what i've done what i've
called what i've said but look this is
the imbalance here
this is oh no this is not the open
this is the imbalance from the open here
so you see this price quickly moving
within this area
what do we get
tap of this imbalance
straight away
so yeah it does respect um
uh the
the uh the the price of like the opening
price because this is this is the
opening and then you have this huge push
out of the area
you know and then also
you have let me see if it actually tap
this imbalance here
so you have a tap right here at this
imbalance also
26 pips just over the top of that
imbalance
and of course you'd wait for price to
get to the imbalance a second time to
see what it's going to do
and
if you don't see anything you know
happening it continues to push you just
look for the next area to potentially
trade from so we had this area here
well not we i originally had this one
when the market had um
open but i wasn't streaming as of yet um
so i had this area here that pricing get
rejected from and then i have this
fractal here that price could find
support and potentially head back up on
and then there was this other imbalance
that was here that price could reject
from price rejected from it then price
came up to touch into
this s and d here this on a higher time
frame what is that like a five minute
snd
no that's actually a higher timeframe
and balance
look at this
let's just tap the higher time frame in
balance
and then left but this is exactly what
i'm saying these things you can find on
every single time frame
every
single time frame
we just got an imbalance from a five
minute time frame and saw that this is
the area that it tapped to go short
and took out the low
the imbalance from the five minute so
the imbalance from the higher time
frames are stronger than the imbalance
from the lower time frames but you can
trade imbalances on all time frames if
you have a particular system or
or technique with it
and
for me it's it's best to
you know look at scalping of these
imbalances and if it returns for for
something else so you see it taps into
this imbalance here and then you get an
equal high
here
so you know the equal high is resulting
in either the run of this low or this
low one of the lows that created one of
the highs will be ran oftentimes it's
the first low that's ran
from the second equal well the the
second high that was made and then
sometimes you have
the the other low ran from the other
high that was made
uh let me see um is it safe to say you
can scalp from the equal highs and equal
lows so oftentimes i do if i see a wick
rejection out of the area like a quick
move out of the area so look at this
here um
this is the equal high that i had just
mentioned
this here this here let's say you get
this push out of the area remember what
i talked about with this um
this little candlestick pattern that i
mentioned
down here within this area
sorry that was like poor drawing i'm not
an artist by the way
this area here
you see price go down you see price push
up heavy quickly push down looks like
we're gearing up for what an equal high
so what do i say oftentimes you see
where within this area there's something
in here like you know akima mentioned
the order block there's something in
here
that it often taps into and trades away
so here's how i was able to trade the
equal high saw the equal high
established saw an opportunity to get in
went short what did i short to possibly
the first low or the second low i'm out
done for the day
that fast
i don't need to stay on the charts
so let's see i get grabbed into this
area and i'm taken down look look at a
whopping 80 something pimps
what
just off of noticing this one little
move fast within five minutes this all
happened within five minutes
if you noticed it in real time all
happened within five minutes bam bam you
out
but you got to be exposed to the charts
enough to be able to see that and to
react with that in real time you got to
be able to to
you know have enough exposure
to to notice that to see that and be
like all right yeah cool this is where
this is where i'm trading from
this is what i'm doing
and you see all now this chart looks
like
it looks weird it looks like futuristic
or almost like all these different lines
minimalistic you know in a sense
um
but
there's a method to it
this is what the aftermath tends to look
like
but there's a method to all of this
so we know that
on a higher time frame if you look at
oh maybe like a 15 minute time frame
or a 30 minute time frame look at this
whole area
on a 15 minute time frame on a 30 minute
time frame maybe i don't know let me see
let me double check
sorry about that
so here's here's what streamers are
doing because they tend to trade from
the higher time frames
not only because they they probably
don't know what they're doing
but sometimes
i mean most times is that they they
really don't know what they're doing but
you know you
you have this area
and if you go to a higher time frame
people are like oh no this this is
ranging guys we can't do anything about
this you know
like maybe if it breaks above like this
area or if it comes below this area
we'll
we'll see but this is ranging no setup
guys and they just be waiting and
chatting for like four hours you're like
what what are you doing guys four hours
you're sitting there you know just just
talking
and saying that you can't trade any of
this
even if you felt like you couldn't trade
any of this go down to the lower time
frames and use it as an opportunity to
teach people
an opportunity to teach people about
price in real
time
utilize that
we can't find a setup from the time
frame we usually trade from but we see
that there's some consolidation
happening or some ranging happening
within here
use this as an opportunity to teach
people who are following you
what you know
not just wait around and have some
dialogue with them oh let's let's check
d x y oh the d x y failed about a
dollar so you know like
or 10 cents or whatever that that figure
is i don't know you know with it
stop copying me boy
yeah so
so i even chart this so i i get an idea
of like
you know
when our recession potentially is coming
um so i do have a tap up into this area
potentially and this could be the
rejection
um for when we begin to enter um our
recession
but i do have these levels down here
this is actually the weekly i'm talking
about the recession in america coming
um
so it's like right here look at how we
have we've had these huge pushers up
from like 2014 economy started growing
after our recession down in here 2014 we
pushed up into this area but
we pushed up abnormally i don't know if
this is due to like war or whatever it
is war usually fields the dollar um
going higher because most people who are
sending aid to other countries they're
sending it in
the dollar
they're they're not really sending it in
euros or pounds or anything usually most
debts that are paid abroad are
in the u.s dollar
um so
you know with this when they're sending
aid when they're you know they have a
bunch of money for war but they can't
feed the poor
i'm not a rapido but yeah they have that
and
that's when you see you start to see the
strength of the dollar start pushing
and then when we're not in any conflict
or any wars or anything like that
you know
we end up
losing
some sort of value
you know we um
pulled troops out of afghanistan
um
not too long ago and we began to shift
bearish but the war in ukraine
kind of
pushed this up because a lot of people
are sending aid packages to ukraine and
stuff exactly exactly park there we go
yo i definitely gotta beat you bro we
yeah so so i usually use this to time
like
you know what's going on with the
american dollar and our economy and
things like that use the russell the was
it the russell 2000 to time how the
markets are doing
um
the yield curve and and your treasury
yields to time
like other things within other markets
the bond markets all of those different
things you could utilize
this same analysis that we use to trade
we could utilize this same analysis to
be able to understand what's happening
within our economy what's happening with
the american dollar what's like it's
it's interest so it's it's analysis it's
financial analysis um and you could use
this in so many different areas to
benefit you so if the dxy is currently
shorting
then that means that anything
against the dollar
is probably longing
at this
it's pushing up
so this and this is the same candle june
13 candle on the dxy
shorting
this is for the week
and anything against the dollar
longing
gbp usd against the dollar longing
so you could utilize this particular
thing
if you're using eu gu
you know or or any type of whatever you
you know you could utilize this
to be able to have like some added
confluence or some added you know
strength to to like the trades that
you're taking now sometimes they will
both go down together
um
you have that you know then there's like
a little correction to it but oftentimes
this is it
so so yeah this is this is
you know the the us dollar against gold
you had gold b you had gold bearish look
at this
gold was bearish from here
the u.s dollar began to fall
and gold
is pushing up
with it
because the u.s dollar is falling
so gold against the us dollar
you have some
some bullish momentum
going on and that's within the last two
days that gold has been like pushing out
of the area
but this is why i say you know like i
keep talking about this this discord we
can get it up and running soon um this
is almost done by the way guys um but
this is exactly why i have my bias was
that we're pushing down into this area
and longing most people were short on
gold
and did not know where we were short too
look at these areas that i have back
here
gold tapped my line here
and it started to push up
this is the reversal where gold started
i told you the stuff i teach you can
catch these reversals
so this is over over the span of two
days
gold has pushed 44 dollars
over the span of two days
so i i can analyze for long term i could
analyze for sure too i could analyze for
a couple minutes i could analyze for for
a couple months
and that's just
the power of technical analysis
this is what i'm talking about you do
not need to follow news you do not need
to like
fundamentals are great
if you were using fundamentals for like
the longevity of a
a particular company
like let's say amc or or um
gamestop or whatever it is you know like
or or tesla or rivien or amazon or
google look at the longevity of those
companies
and when you're paying attention to the
longevity of those companies you would
use fundamentals yes
to to invest long term but you also pair
it with technical analysis
for me for the day i'm day trading i'm
not using any fundamentals at all i do
not need fundamentals for day trading
at all like it's
it's not something that i recommend
anybody use
you know yeah fundamentals are great to
spot manipulations but oftentimes
manipulations still happen within
structure
still happens within structure
they manipulate but they're not running
their stop losses
so if they're trading according to
you know whatever whatever algorithm
they're they're using if they're trading
according to that
then
you have to remember that their stop
losses are somewhere
and and with their stop losses
wherever it is that they are they're not
they're not going to run their own stop
losses exactly it's just faster news
news causes price like fundamentals
causes price to be manipulated
faster
it causes price to move to its areas
so when it gets to those areas when
price gets there faster then you see a
reaction from there to there to there to
there so when when news was happening
when i had mentioned um you know like
yesterday i mentioned some of those
levels you saw that news just sped it up
to get there
and it did not go beyond those levels
that i had
so
technical analysis is truly king
truly
look at this rejection here
from from this other area that i have up
here
even if this doesn't result in a in a
huge rejection
rejection nonetheless
look at this
34 pips down already in two candles and
still falling
look at what i said this area here
right here
you have this this buying up into the
cellar into this buy-in here
you know this is what i talk about in
terms of like
some of these appearing as
s and d's and oftentimes they're not
you know this one there's a potential
that this could be because
if you look at structure this was the s
and d responsible for breaking the high
of structure right here so that's why
you could have this reaction pushing in
here i told you anytime you want to
look for s and d's look for s and d's
that broke behind that that broke
structure
those are s and d's that have stronger
movements to it those s and d's that
broke structure
so
this one has a huge push off of it after
mitigating what is this like 90 of it
yeah after mitigating like almost 90 95
96 of it you have this huge push up
after
but then we still don't take out this
high to the left
we still didn't run that high
so
is is this
if if it goes below this s d would you
say that this s d was
was useful
you know no it's
not because
there's no run of the high
we quickly pushed up took out a high
right here
and then traded back below it
and this can be trading just to come
back into to this s and d here and still
push higher yes there's a possibility
within here let me show you guys
oh so this was here i gotta i gotta keep
i can remember to move my my lines that
i create
so they don't
trip anybody up
we had it there
um
this was valid for a short here
this was probably coming to touch this s
and d here
this s d mitigated this one
this currently is being mitigated
so if price let's say price does trade
above this area
and let's say it taps here
or even here
you know that if there's a tap here and
a rejection out of either here or here
let's say if it does go up here or here
you know that
this area here
would potentially be an area that price
just pushed past why because the area is
mitigated already
so now all this would all this would
need to do is
push down here
run this area come back up into this
area
mitigate the area and then continue down
to where
other unmitigated areas what do we have
an imbalance here we also have
a demand area down here so this could be
the next target for price
touching into this area possibly the
midway of the imbalance possibly have a
reaction somewhere at this fractal here
or overall this s and d that's here this
demand area that's down here
if
if it does get down here
you know so
these are things to just pay attention
to
when you're in certain trades
when you're taking certain trades
these are things to pay attention to so
this low here was responsible for
creating this high
and this low here
was responsible for creating this height
what do we end up getting
a run of the low but what did i say
i mentioned that often times
you have it to where you have this push
up followed by this push down and then
you have an area that price can tap into
and then go short from we just mentioned
the same thing over here
right here the same exact thing happened
so this happens on a higher time frame
could you imagine more the the more
value you get within that from the
higher time frame but this just happened
here
this happened here this happened here we
talked about another area somewhere
around here that it happened can't can
exactly remember but
same thing over and over again
over look this happened here you had
this followed by this what this wick
came down tapped into the area and took
you up
like this happens everywhere
you know and and i just want people to
to get it to to understand it to you
know like
these things are easy to see in real
time
these things are easy to to spot
and
and it's so helpful when it comes to
your trading is helpful when it comes to
like
being able to spot and learn it in real
time being able to catch a quick scout
being able to stay into trades longer it
is
extremely helpful extremely helpful if
you're having a problem spotting
imbalances
maybe you should use the the imbalance
indicator that i had mentioned
it's an indicator that's in real time
oh i don't know what
and
with these indicators that that i'm not
saying that you should you know utilize
this and only trade from this but what
i'm saying is this would help you spot
the imbalances easier
this is what i used to be able to notice
the imbalances easier when i first
didn't understand the concept of
imbalance
and now since i understand the concept
of imbalance and i know how to take
trades from imbalances or take scalps
from imbalances
i then utilize this to
to be able to facilitate that for me
you know and and this kind of helps and
now i don't need this anymore
because now i could spot imbalances and
that's just the more that you expose
yourself to the charts you're able to
spot this
you know so
this this was very helpful early on in
my journey but you want to learn how to
kick the indicators all together
you don't want to have to use indicators
at all
i am not interested in using indicators
i don't want to use indicators i want to
be able to see it in real time because
guess what let's say a billionaire buys
trading bill
and you're in a trade and you're
dependent on indicators
and
they just shut down indicators for the
day
you know how easy it is how easy it
would be to manipulate
you know retail traders
because how they understand that that
there's this dependence
on indicators for them
be extremely easy
like look i i mentioned you know
you know the the imbalance finder thing
that that i showed you guys look at this
tap into this imbalance trade away from
it
another quick scout
and now this is pushing up i i don't
know what the huge flip is but
it's it's still a quick scalp from the
area
look at this 30 pip scalp now we're
pushing don't know where we're going
don't know if it's just tapping into
this supply and leaving could be you
know but
this like catching these things quick so
this would have been two trades back to
back
if you look at it
trade down here coming from this area
that you noticed
trade from the imbalance coming down to
here
oh and and look
oh my gosh
oh my gosh and look at what we hit
we hit an impact
this this is
i'm telling you this is phenomenal
information guys
phenomenal information
look at what we hit we hit another
imbalance that was down here i said we
could potentially hit the imbalance or
we could hit the fractal or maybe the s
and d what did we tap with the long wick
away the long rejection away
we tap the imbalance
and where do we go
60 something pips up from the imbalance
this is what i want you guys to
understand
these are so
important
so so so so so
important oh my gosh
i don't say these things for
for giggles for fun or or anything like
that
these are so
important such
important areas
and and i'm i'm teaching this in real
time because i'm trying to help you guys
to understand like
like this happens over and over and over
again
there's
i don't i don't know i don't know what
more to say to like like convince people
about this to to get people to
understand how powerful this is to like
if i saw this and somebody was like
hey man you know
you
if you spent
hours learning this and if you just cut
off netflix for a week
and cut off all these different things
for a week and and in all of your all of
your leisure time
all of and i'm saying for a week i'm not
saying forever
all
[Music]
all of your leisure time
if you just devoted all of your leisure
time
to taking this all in
you know i had um uh one person um
tell me i actually want her to be a
moderator in the group too um
she told me that
she's addicted to watching it like she
she watches it while she's eating while
she's going to sleep while she's
traveling she's just watching it because
she really wants it she really wants to
get it and i really want her to get it
too i want all of you guys to get it but
i want you guys to understand
the power of
utilizing this so even if you were in a
push-up from this imbalance
you also
see that what did price do tap into the
area above the line that we had above
right here after it tapped into there
what did we get a 24 pip rejection from
that did we get the candlestick
rejection that i said i like the little
candlestick pattern where it wicks up
above
and then shorts
it's right here
right here
got the rejection
why did why did price come down here and
reject here
fractal
right here
price pushed off of the fractal
ram the high
after we run the high what do we do
since it's an area we're still shorting
out of we short back down where to
possibly this s and d here we could have
some rejection here or we could just
break through it you know the smaller
ones are usually um
you know pretty small and for a lot
anyway
but we could have a rejection from here
or we could have a push directly through
the area
but just understanding these areas
can help you
with
being able to take trades from it no
imbalance here so if it runs this low
we're not expecting it to really stop
here unless it hits another area of
interest
like this supply area somewhere within
here bam we just touched it
you know so now we're seeing the
reaction around the supply area do you
look at the higher time frame as well to
get an overall direction yeah so george
my top downs um i actually start the top
down
um you know just with a sense of
like the overall direction of price and
then we just work within that so we look
at
where price left
where price left right here
and where price stalled here
and now we know we're working
within the area of here
and here and like i mentioned from a
higher time frame
you might have like you know let let's
say you you take this area here
from a higher time frame if you're like
one of the the stream traders you know
who who trade from the higher time frame
and only like they just sit on the
higher time frame the whole time
and they trade look at this sorry it was
a little
little flash movement
look at this
so they see this here and they go oh
this is sideways ranging this is
sideways consolidating
you know so we can't trade this we got
to wait for a setup
let's either wait for it to run
above a high or run below it so they're
just sitting here spending hours
you know
just waiting for some strong movement to
happen you go oh it's not tradable we
couldn't find a trade today
you don't have to
you know like
you you don't have to do this
you just use these higher time frames
for direction overall so we went into um
we went into the daily
was it yeah we went into the daily and
we found
not just the daily but also the the four
hour i think of us
we found i'm sorry that's so
stuck in there we found different areas
that price could go to
so look now you have a wick below this
area here
a green wick below this area and then
you had a push
up this is the candlestick pattern that
i told you guys i like to see
where after it wicks below a certain
area it starts to push up and flip
bullish so price could still be flipping
bullish now and this is just from a
higher time frame perspective according
to candlesticks but we also got areas
from the left that we went to look at
and see that price could potentially tap
into so i think our first area was
was it 8 19
um
i don't think it was 8 19.
it was from the daily so it was like
8 20 something or or whatever it was um
if you go back to the beginning of the
video it it would it would show it but
it was within this area it was like 8 23
or something like that so
it came down you know missed 823 by like
a couple pips yeah there you go exactly
8 23.
i missed it by a couple pips see i i
know you know what you talk about that
that's good so it
it went down to the area
tapped into the area or near the area
and then you just started to see it flip
back up
we took we mentioned that when we get to
certain areas we like to see this
candlestick pattern where price flicks
below
the wick to the left and then trades
back up above it so now we could
essentially be targeting the area that
that we were looking to target
above which was 101
but then we could also look to target
you know as akeem says the ohlc
we could look to target either that
the the high
or we could look to target
the open
and those are potential areas that price
could touch but can price just tap
between this area yes it can
because the high and the low of the area
will give you
the midway point of this area so if we
took the high and the low of this area
one here
took the low here
let's drag it out here
look at where we're spinning some uh
resistance at right now
eight what is this zero eight six
so let's get a line into zero eight six
right here
now let's go down to the higher time
frame
of zero eight
six and let's take a look at where we
are
move this out
look at where we get our rejection from
not only 086 but we tapped into the 101
area now i'm not saying that these
rejections are going to hold here
but these are biases
that you pick up and you begin to look
at where price can go what area price
can go in so this is just higher time
frame bias
you know and and you're paying attention
to what's going on within that higher
time frame bias and you're catching
little moves from that so look we
mentioned that we can get a rejection
out of here we did get a rejection from
here
at at this particular line
right here
sizable rejection too 61 pips then look
we get another rejection out of this
area what are we at 43 pips already
from just having this area on our chart
like this
so so the higher time frames yes they
they show us you know what could
potentially be happening yes
the higher time frames show us that
the lower time frames essentially
like give you the more detailed work of
heading there but the higher time frames
gives you that bias to help you
understand that so i i do give people
trades from higher time frames too
you know i do not trades first of all
let me tell you guys that i'm not a
financial advisor
local and federal law requires
one who is in need of financial advice
to find their financial advice from
licensed financial advisors
i am not a licensed financial advisor i
cannot give out financial information
the information that i give
is only
for educational purposes
and not intended to be used
in the markets for financial advice i
need to put that disclaimer out each and
every time don't need anybody trying to
sue me because they're like oh well you
said it was shorting here and it didn't
so you know because people sue people
people sue people for anything here in
america
anything
here in america they sue people for so
look this is an imbalance here
[Laughter]
i need to be able to back myself up in
court so i leave these receipts just in
case anybody tries it
but look you gotta tap into this area
in the imbalance this is why i say the
imbalances are important like pay
attention to it they are not just
they're not only areas to hold trades
from sometimes they may turn into a long
trade depending on how
how um how much momentum comes out of it
you know if you feel comfortable staying
in but this tapped into this imbalance
so most people might be looking for it
to come down to somewhere within this
area but no we tapped into some balance
what did i say here i said we can come
to this s and d here we could either
come to this but if we blow past this we
could be coming to this one what do we
do tap into this area here
and then
we left up to where the next target here
we tap here and get rejected what's the
next target here
at this area
next target is the imbalance after the
imbalance what's the next target
here
this area here
why is this the next target
the top of here why is this the next
target
here
because everybody's probably wondering
like what how did you even find that
area
this here
stops behind here
potentially shorting
could be this little s and d if it goes
past this then it could go down to one
of the snds down here
because the imbalance already cleared
why are we shorting from here
why
why do we choose to find a short from
this area
we chose to find a short from this area
yes this this
liquidity above this area there's more
orders within like pending orders within
this area but remember what i mentioned
candlestick structure when it gets to
your area start paying attention to
candlestick structure
candlestick structure what do i mean by
that and i continue to to spell this out
for you guys so you guys understand
we get a high right here we take a low
here we put in another high and what do
we do we run the low
we even run the low with
with um we we run the low here
and then we come back into this area
here
we tap into this area again and short
from it but we return to this area a
second time
now for me i like to see body closures
below the low
that is ran so this low is ran a wick
came out of it
that's fine you know sometimes you can
get the wick but sometimes there's also
um
some sort of um
uh uh
like fake out it could potentially be
just using the wick so i like to see the
body closures sometimes the body
closures it also doesn't come back to
the area but with the body closures what
you what you have to understand is it's
given a stronger indication that price
is pulling away from that area so
you get the body closure out of the area
price trades back up into this area
this wick is here
as a a supply area
you know there's a there's a hidden
supply above
right let me
right here
there's a hidden supply up here
often times when price trades away
it'll tap into the body of the area
and leave but it also leaves behind this
hidden supply area
and sometimes when people are engaging
in shorts
down from this area
oftentimes you get a tap back into the
supply area and if anybody had their
stops behind any of these areas that
they begin to shorten
they all get ruptured
they tap into the area they all get
ruptured to tap back into there
before trading
further down i don't know why this isn't
clicking for me but before trading
further down
into like an area down there
you know so that can happen if price
comes back to your area a second time
that can happen
and on a lower time frame
on a lower time frame this ultimately
right here this little area
on like the seconds time frame this area
here
is
an equal high
and i always say that oftentimes the
equal highs result in at least a run of
the first low
which
we ran that first low here
you know and now we we do have some
stagnation within this area like i said
it could push back up to tap into this
supply area here before finally going
short or it can just go short
you know to one of these areas possibly
before going long again to possibly take
out some more highs
you know we have this area here this is
the daily high
this 156 area
this is the daily high usually when
these daily highs and lows are ran
it runs it and then you have like a huge
push down from that area
like a huge sell-off or i don't know why
i don't know you know
what the reason is behind that it could
be just
as as he mentioned the liquidity it can
be the buy stops that are that are being
activated you know they're for string
for swing traders you know
just people
not knowing like people think that just
because this highest ran it's going to
go higher and that's not necessarily the
truth
that doesn't mean that it's gonna go
higher
just because a high is taken out
sometimes a high can be taken out and it
immediately like starts trading heavily
below the law
like look this high was ran here
this was yesterday
fomc
this hype was ran
after this high was ran
and this i also ran some highs back here
this high is red let's say you were
using this this i was brand
this high is ran
and immediately look at how we tank
down below look at how we sell off
immediately after this
this time was around
so you don't look to get in just because
you see a high being ran
you look to get in
because of
structure because of what you're
understanding
maybe there's an area above that high
that price can potentially tap
and then go short from that area
so you want to pay attention to those
things as well
you know but but
i try to teach this in a way where
people
you know they're able to understand like
understand it to where they don't need
me they don't need me to come on stream
and trade every day i will not be coming
on stream to trade every day
you know like like when i'm traveling
and stuff i want to travel and enjoy the
world i want to hang out have fun with
with you know my kids have fun with my
friends have like
just enjoy life life is so short
you know and this is why i i put these
things out for free in in public you
know because
sometimes i
may just want to chill out for today i
may want to just wake up late in the
morning or whatever it is so i want to
be able to equip you guys to understand
this and not need me at all
like there's absolutely no reason
why i'm needed for any of this
and and and this is why i teach the
quality that i teach on this channel
yeah the discord is going to give a
different level of quality oh my gosh
like
it's going to be an entirely different
level
of quality
with with the um with the discord
like that is going to be out of this
world
you know let me see
just want to check check everything real
quick
uh luke the discord is going to be up
and running soon real soon
walter i see you here let me um
just i'll add you here
and if you guys know other people get
get these streams out to them get get
like my channel out to them get this
information out to them like it
it's life-changing for them brad i see
you too
keem i'm gonna answer you soon i see you
too
yeah like you know
this information is is life-changing so
look we mentioned the short here
we mentioned the possibility of coming
back up to this s and d
but then we also mentioned coming down
to this one here
so look now we we make it down to this
one
and you want to see what it does within
this area within this smd we already got
to the midpoint of it if you wanted to
take us to the midpoint the 74 pips just
from the top of that
i told you if you get in on these taps
of the lines up here
let's say it tap here
and i mentioned this yesterday if it
taps here and it starts to consolidate
down here
this is none of your business
because this is moving up and down in an
area that you're already in profiting
absolutely none of your business was
going on here now if it starts to pull
back up into this area and possibly run
this high right here then maybe it
starts to become your business because
this is you know seven eight pips away
from your entry but if your entries
already locked that break even
then you're fine you're just watching
what's going on in this trade
then you come to some of these areas and
you see okay
what did we say
we said this could be an equal high on
the the lower time frame
so if we get an equal high
we result in the run of not just one low
but the second low
so now if your
if your um
trade is down to the second low here
look at this
89 pips
and you were only risking 23.
you got there in
10 11 minutes
just because one you notice the area
two you notice the candlestick pattern
happen in the area
three if if so if you got into this
scalp on this area
you know let's say you scalp here you
hit the imbalance
you partial out 50 or 80 percent of your
order cool
price comes back up into the area oh
we're finding some resistance looks like
an equal high
you got a second opportunity to get in
and then and
and the equal high was created as a
result of the retracement back into the
area before leaving after we violated
the low on the candlestick level so now
you have a second entry here
now your second entry becomes the longer
entry
into some of these areas here
but when price gets to these areas
you're not getting out just because it
gets to these areas
what you're doing is you're looking to
see
what's gonna happen when it gets into
these areas and if the areas are already
mitigated then you don't care about them
you're looking to go further into those
areas
and you want to go into an unmitigated
area and see okay what can price do
within this area this area is is either
mitigated unmitigated whatever it is you
know what is price gonna show me are we
start are we gonna start to get some
sideways movement like this
into the area are we gonna get it to the
downside
not sure but we wait
but what are we we're
98 pips in profit from the area that we
just saw price trade away from
and this this is all consolidation so
everybody's like oh consolidation
you know you can't trade that you have
to wait until
you know you see what happens with it
you know this that's not true
consolidation is telling you a story on
the inside of there
and you need to be able to understand
what's being said of that story that
consolidation is telling you so
with here we have an area here
that price just tapped into
right here
if you wanted that to be your short and
you're out cool
we got the little candlestick pattern
that we usually see with wicks below
the area to the left and then pulls back
inside of it you want to make sure that
it pulls back inside of the range and
closes within the range of that candle
it looks better from the the one hour
let me see
so so this area
if
if you look within this area yeah this
this tap is consistent with the one hour
because if you look right here
this is where the tap is
for the hourly this is what i would have
saw from the hourly and this is what i'm
saying these these streamers that be out
there streaming and they really don't
like they're not
they're not any at any expert levels
they really don't understand um what
they're doing they're trying to to teach
what they know and trying to
help people make money or whatever it is
they say they're doing but you know you
you got to be at a certain level of
expertise to to like get into financial
markets help people and not have them
you know lose the money that they're
losing like you got to be really good at
what they what you do and and for me i'm
that's the way i am you know like
i mean i'm i'm jamaican
you know jamaicans are perfectionists
you know like they they
everything has to be speaking span
everything has to be you know it has to
be a certain way it's we're just not
i don't know maybe it's a cultural thing
maybe it's the work ethic or whatever it
is but look it taps on this line how
much drawdown do we get on this
four pips from an hourly area
and where are we
here
we've already gone what down to here
136 pips
since tapping this area
since tapping this area from the hourly
just with this this one wick alone
and what how did we gain some idea that
price would come up and tap into this
with our zones
and how we choose them
and once we're able to find out how to
choose the zones
see how did i mark that area
i took this low
to this high
but
i took it to the body
because
when price traded above this area and
came back in
that's when i noticed that price wanted
to come down remember how i mentioned
these candlestick patterns of you know
price pushing up above a high and then
trading back within it and then shorting
from that area so if you want if you
were on an hourly and you saw a price
tap into this snd
pushed up in this area came back in and
you began to short you can get in on the
next candle here look there's some
bullish bullish movement here something
is happening with price this could be
fundamentals too
but
you know you you had this this um push
up it came back in the next candle opens
you can get in on with stops behind here
and this would have been market open
and you would have been able to take it
all the way down to the area that we
mentioned price was coming to
all the way down to here
so look at how we just quickly recovered
let's go to one minute and see what that
looks like
look at look at this look at this come
on look at this this is
i just mentioned that price tapped this
line right here
this line i i said that these lines are
targets but these lines are also entries
look at this
oh my gosh like
look at this huge move up you see how i
said scalps can turn into long movements
if you just know the areas that you're
getting into
scalps can turn into long movements
look at this huge push up
out of this area within a matter of four
minutes
four minutes
after it touched this line here
like yes yes wicked literally with the
wick
i want to see price come tap into the
area but it has to come below
this low
and then trade back within the range and
then i know that it's a push up
i call that the liquidity grab candle
where it's grabbing the stops real quick
i told you within an area that is making
lows you see a huge stab and then a
trade away from it
that's exactly what happened here so
even if you got in for a quick scalp bam
look how fast that took you up
and this is what i'm talking about with
news i don't pay attention to news and
all that other stuff because it always
hits my area and then reacts off of the
news
so that's just something that that you
guys want to you know consider utilizing
and paying attention to and i want this
video to be the video that you guys go
back and watch like
go back and and and
you know
study and learn from from this
particular video there's so much
sauce that was given all in this short
period of time like so much and and i
know that if you guys utilize this like
you'll be able to to you know really
you know learn and and change your
circumstances so look i mentioned the
fractals guys i said with a fractal
sometimes you have it to where price
reacts off of the fractal the wick up
the wick down price reacts and then
takes you up so with this
you have this push down below
and it touches this fractal
cool it hits this fractal quick scalp up
what is this a 63 pip scalp within two
minutes
63 pips
just off of the touch of a fractal you
know like these these things
if if you guys get the
get the zones and understand them
because i'm literally just scalping or
creating trades from zones period that's
it this is what i also meant to mention
to you guys
remember candlestick structure we talk
about a lot on here candlestick
structure so
we make this high we come back make this
low we put in another high we run the
low
after we run the low what do we do tap
back into the area and now we're pushing
out of it
if you guys noticed this in real time
then you would have easily said okay
we
took out this high
and
we took out the low right after so price
is going to trade back into this area so
what do we get we get a trade back up
into the area too short from
where do we short from here stops behind
the zone
here
and we're looking to go to the next area
of interest and the next area of
interest is i mean we we still
what is this this oh did it did it touch
the fractal a second time so look we
touched the fractal let's say you you
took this directly to the fractal a
second time
it touched the fractal a second time
but what is it doing behind the area
that it touched
we're trading below the wick
and then
we push back up
within that area so this is what i talk
about with sometimes price returning a
second time to your area
but also having a bounce up off of the
area so we literally just
grabbed liquidity directly behind it and
then trade it back up again to this area
where are we trading to back up to this
area this possible s and d zone
right here
that could be a target from this area
heading back up to and oftentimes we do
get a reaction from the s and d zones
even if it's a small reaction we still
get reactions you know so you get a
reaction here and then there's a
possible one that's that's right up
above
you know within here but
we know that that within here if price
trades up above this from this high to
possibly up into here it's already
mitigated
this is already mitigated between this
area this area in this area here very
small areas already mitigated
so look we we have this reaction
coming out of this area and we can be
coming down to this s and d that it left
here
it left an s and d here and this is a
pretty large s and d
but we can be coming down to tap this
and because we have not came through
this or
we have not came through the low of this
neither have we put in another high
after this zone sometimes it can bounce
from zone sorry
it can bounce from
what is
can you click it please
it can bounce from zone to zone two zone
two zone
two zone two zone two zone two zone it
could do that over and over and over and
over again
over and over and over again
until it invalidates one of these zones
until it invalidates one of them
it can do that over and over and over
and over and over again
and both of the both of the zones still
be valid because they have not
disrespected any of the rules that we
had
which was
that price either has to
break
through the zone
or it has to put in a new high it has to
break through this zone or it has to put
in a new low the new low is here
at the bottom of this zone which
invalidates this zone but the new low
also invalidates this zone
but it can go from zone to zone to zone
to zone to zone to zone to zone just
like that
just like that
and i teach this stuff every single day
every day i teach this stuff i don't
charge anybody money i don't like
nothing i don't i just want people to
change their life circumstances
i want people to to be able to
you know like do the things they want to
do do the things they love to do this is
a hard world things are getting worse
you know like prices are raising
not because of any
you know president or any political
party but because of
greed
they don't have to raise these prices
it's greed it's nothing but greed
this is not a result of anybody's
monetary policy it's global inflation
this is greed man
greed
so i just want like we we are as a
result we are hurt
by this
game of greed that they're playing
we are hurt
us people
but we want to be able to navigate those
things because we still have kids that
need to eat
we still have roofs that we have to put
over our head we still have daily things
we have to take care of some people
takes they take care of their loved ones
some people take care of their families
the parents
not even having kids some people still
are responsible for other people their
siblings whoever it is
and it's very very difficult it's very
hard for them
so
why
if somebody's trying to change their
financial circumstances why would i take
advantage of
like give them garbage trades why would
i do that
why would i come on here acting like i
know what i'm talking about and and i
don't
that's unacceptable
and i don't believe in that at all so
this is why i come out to do the things
that i do you know and i hope that that
people gain some type of
you know some type of value from it i
hope that you guys actually
you know get something you guys actually
take something where you could notice in
the markets and be able to make you know
even if it's a cup of coffee man
like being able to make some money to
to even have a cup of coffee
you know like i i believe in that too
and that's why i do what i do it's not
because
you know i feel like you know people
deserve it or it's not because like you
know i want to go to the road of fame if
somebody was to take my techniques and
just like become a big power player in
the world with it they're cool whatever
you know like now you're changing more
people's lives
in a larger fashion you know like like
on a larger platform
now you're doing that
on a larger platform you're doing that
so if that's the only thing
that happens
with this type of teaching that's enough
for me
that's enough i don't need anybody's
money
i don't need the biggest house i don't
need a ferrari i can get those things if
i wanted to but i don't need that what
makes me happy what makes my heart full
is
people being able to change their lives
off of something that i was able to take
process teach them in a manner where
it could help them
to learn
something for the rest of that life this
is a skill that you could learn for the
rest of your life whether you want to
trade for prop firms whether you want to
trade for
um banks or organizations whether you
want to trade for yourself whether you
want to teach your kids trading whether
you want to teach your your families or
your churches or or other people that
you know whether you want to teach them
trading you can
you can
this is a skill
that you can teach others freedom with
and it can give you your freedom too
you know so so you see i said it could
bounce within these areas you can just
consolidate within this area yeah
very very possible
very let me go back and i think i had
this here yeah
yeah
very possible that it can bounce within
these areas
so
and it can create newer areas within
here
because look this wick right here was an
s and d that price came back up two
tapped into and got rejected from ram
the low
and then when it ran the low and came
back up it created this smd here and
then what the price do come down and tap
into it and go above
we went from this s and d here
pushed up
we opened up
came back to this s d here the newly one
that was created after it mitigated this
one and then we pulled up into the snd
above
then we tapped into the s and d above
and now we're pulling down we go below
this one and we could potentially
further go below this one because this
one already came into this
one so you just see it go from s and d
to s and d to s d to s and d to s and d
tests d over and over and over and over
and over again
like i hope you guys can see the
the richness
of like
what i'm saying in in real time like
principles and reasons as to why
this is happening
so you see i said it was going to run
this low why because we had already
mitigated this
but we tapped into this s and d above to
come down and run this low here and now
that we ran this lows another s and d in
here
and it could be in here or right above
this
you know but after running this low is
there a possibility that we could still
try to run the high yes there is
but could we continue short still yes
and you know who benefits from it most
the person that was in a short from up
here
they don't care about any of this stuff
going on down here i said when the highs
are usually ran when structural highs
are usually ran
oftentimes
you get a huge pull away
and we have that
with this structural high
we get the huge pull away
don't we don't get a body close above so
we know that we're still in murky
territories we're still in territories
of
shorting
you know and i'm talking about overall
i'm not just talking about like
like
where we are in price but overall
so look we get a break below this low
let me look on the ohlc before i
tell you guys that's a break so it's 0
30 and this is
0 30. so this is an equal low right here
within this area
change this color back to black this is
an equal low here
other times you get it equal low trade
away
whatever the objective is for price to
do it goes it goes and it does it and
then it runs it
so we have this equilo established we'll
see what price does there was a little s
d created here
price opened up tapped into it got
rejected from it took out this low
after it took out this low created an
equilo came back up tapped into the snd
created above here
then came down and ran both lows
yeah exactly exactly just like that you
know exactly
uh teachers dave
to call your callers
this is power
yes i want people to learn this like i
told you i could trade every movement of
price if i wanted to every single
movement of price i can trade if i
wanted to
because i've spent that much time
studying this so look there's a little
imbalance inside of here i don't know if
price will push up past the imbalance or
come down to the fractal that also has
the s and d inside of it
we'll see if it it has any
reaction off of it or if it just runs
through it it could very well do that
you know but you have this little snd
zone followed by this little fractal in
here also
so let's see if you chose
the fractal
that's here
if you chose
the s and d
that's
here
and then there's
this
smaller one above or below sorry down
here
followed by an imbalance right above it
imbalance right in here
yep see
tap within this area there was a gap up
here
um i don't know what that was about
but then further into the area here if
you're still in the short you're fine
it doesn't matter to you and not just
that
you have an equal high up here
so there's a possibility that this low
is ran because of this equal high
but that doesn't mean that there can't
be a reaction here first
and if there's a reaction here first it
could very well pop back up fill some of
this imbalance up here or it can come
back up into these areas to mitigate
before
going short
but these are things that that
you know you guys should just pay
attention to in in real time and even
try to look for it on your own
look at the reactions of these and try
to create a trading style around
doing this around these reactions
try to create a trading style and that
trading style will it will help you like
exceptionally it will shift your trading
to to another place i'm going to take it
to another place
you know so
this could potentially be distribution
for white golf
up here this could potentially be
distribution
um up here
so if if this
indeed is um
distribution then
you know this is coming down
um and where could it go um
maybe into this area here
could get a reaction out of this area
also as it would have just ran the low
as well um
let's see
you could get a minor reaction within
this area possibly
i'm thinking
trying to give you some give you guys
some areas before i head out of here
maybe even
somewhere around this area
possibly
and if we run
this low
down here
there's still
um this area here remember these these
are just targets if if you're shorting
you want to look at um
you know just what the reaction of price
is
if it comes to this area with this
protected low it could potentially give
you a reaction here
and that's the last area of reaction
before
it takes you down into some of these
areas
down here
some of these areas i mean i think it
could further mitigate within the 700s
um that could be a possibility i don't
know if it would get down here by the
end of the day we have two hours so
there's still
quite some movement that price can make
um but price could end up coming down to
this area and then by the time all of
that like huge
volume comes in it ends up just
springing it up to like
somewhere up into here like that's a
possibility just the same way there was
this this spring here
right here
same way you had this huge push-up let
me actually see if um
there was any news that happened
um
let me see
let me uh double check
um so i follow um this guy named uh
delta one i say it in most of my streams
um
he has most of
the news live like as it's happening um
he's releasing it i think he's on the
president's plane
um wow oil went five dollars again is
oil and gold going up so usually when
oil and gold is going up like that's a
bias that i have for something
potentially happening with the war
if gold is pushing up by itself then
there's something happening with within
our economy the u.s economy if oil is
pushing up then there's something
happening as it relates to the energy
crisis that we're in but it still
somewhat goes back to
you know like things with possible war
so um
i use those different things together to
try and give me a bias where i don't
have to look at the news i kind of have
an idea of like what could be happening
in the fundamental arena just based on
what the technicals show for those
um investigating crypto
um
some company
froze withdrawals on krypto
illama still talking about twitter
looks like the sec is just suing
well looks like it's investigating the
company
yes it is there's not much news that
little spike could have just been you
know some sort of manipulation
um which which tends to happen because
you see how it had that huge push up
took out the high
and then trade it below it
so oftentimes the those are
manipulations but this is what i was
saying i was saying that if you learn
technical analysis a lot of the times
you could learn to stay out of those
manipulations because look look at how
this pushed up huge
after touching our line
now imagine if we jumped in and tried to
short from here
he got railed
you know so
so that's something that that you guys
just like want to pay attention to
um and you see what i said you see what
i mentioned in here
like let's say that you took this area
for a bye
because it came down to this fractal
let's say you went in for a buy
brought you in you know quite a bit dr
quite a bit of drawdown but look it
brought you right back to break even
and gave you what like two pips maybe
for the commission
but even if you got it wrong
there's still a possibility for some
sort of redemption before
being able to take it in whatever next
direction it could possibly be going to
so this is oh look this is the bounce
that i have met
i didn't even notice that you see i just
be chatting and don't don't even
recognize the stuff that
so look i said it would come down to
this area and have a bounce up um this
was 43 pips that it pushed up wow that's
nice so yeah um you know uh
i'm gonna say again uh if if you guys
liked what you saw you guys appreciated
what you saw learn learn something today
please go ahead and like the video
subscribe if you're new um we do this
every day and and and potentially we
could be doing this all day when that
discord is up and running but we we do
this all the time
you know like and let me let me actually
show you guys another thing actually um
right before i i even you know segway
into that look at this
you see what i'm talking about in terms
of let's say the inverse head and
shoulders patterns that i say so look
the neckline break they would they would
say like they they always say that it's
not always um
you know like
uh
it's not always
correct like in terms of parallel
they're not always next to each other um
like creating equal highs or anything
like that but you know they would say
this
the shoulder pull back here and they
would say you can get in here or here at
the neckline break
and they tell you to do that let's say
let's say you did get in on an order
here
at the neckline break
let's say you chose this neckline break
you chose to to buy up into this
from here
i don't know why that's still doing that
but
let's say you choose to buy here at the
neckline break
you choose to buy to tell you to place
your stops
behind
the arm here first of all look at that
outrageous stop loss never ever like
ever will ever be a stop loss for me
ever
but they tell you to to go for the area
in which it came from
which is more like right here
absence of structure
you don't know what the hell is
happening here
and you should not be taking a trade
that's like this at all
like at all because
you just saw the pattern but you don't
know what the hell is even happening
here even from a higher time frame even
if you went to a higher time frame
you can't just see this pattern and be
like oh yeah that's an inverse heading
shows from a higher time frame yeah let
me jump in and trade this no
because your neckline break was here
your stops was behind the shoulder here
that's what they usually teach this is a
192 pip stop loss how disgusting and
then what they tell you target target a
one to one
that is disgusting i don't know why
people get on the internet and teach
things like this
because there's no
sorry let me stop ranting guys so so
yeah this is this is what i'm saying
absence of structure or absent of
structure
this is not something that that you want
to use like even if this did come up
above
um this high here you see we put in a
high
we put in a low
and then we broke the high
over here with this
this could potentially still come down
into
this area here but this would only
do that based on
here
so we have this high
we have this low
we have a run of the high here
now we potentially come back into either
this area or even this area
to potentially
go long if we are going long from any of
these areas
but the inverse head and shoulders if
your stops was behind the shoulder they
would have easily taken you out
at 190 something pep stop loss
because it's absent of actual structure
but i'm gonna go down my kid reminding
me that i have to make a lunch for him
so
i'll um
i'll see you guys uh tomorrow
same time same place like i said share
some of my videos and some of my
teachings with people on telegram and
other groups and
groups that have good teaching not good
teaching i mean it's amazing stuff you
guys could learn so much in such a short
period of time and become profitable
that's the goal for me guys
so um i'll see you guys soon like i said
we're shorting down to to some of these
areas you know mention that from up here
but
you guys understand the gist of it i
hope you guys learned something i hope
the quality of the video was better
today i hope that
you know like like you know you guys
understood
you know a lot of the things that i was
saying um if you guys happen not to
understand what i'm saying
if you guys don't understand what i'm
saying
reach out to me on
instagram on twitter
um i'm dave teaches on telegram if you
want to reach out to me on telegram you
can too
um
it's just dave teaches
twitter is daveteachesfx and instagram
is dave teaches if you guys have any
other questions about anything that i
may not have addressed if you guys want
to schedule some type of
zoom meeting or or just get in on some
of the little zoom sessions that i have
with other people
um i'm always willing to you know talk
to you know help you guys out anywhere
that i can
i wholeheartedly believe in helping
where i can help my whole childhood was
a childhood that was full of service to
people you know like just nothing but
service i
was washing cars of elderly people
handing out flyers working in food
pantries you know like just a bunch of
stuff it was dedicated to a lot of like
charity work and um
i could never escape that you know so
for me if you guys have any questions or
i'm not saying that you're a charity by
the way but i'm just saying that i'm
always willing to help wherever it is
that i can
um and within my limits of course you
know so i'll make sure i see you guys
tomorrow god willing
same time
same place
you guys
enjoy
great day great day
see you sean enjoy man
craig armani akeem john you know
oh ring
you like all of you guys i'll
see you guys soon
later