[Music]
let me uh
you check this audio real quick guys
just double check
the music is not so bad
you know let me keep this open
because i know i get a bit chatty so
mario what's up how's everything good
morning good morning
what's up
sometimes i wish i i came on um
at nine o'clock
um 9 30 at least so i could show you
guys like
how to to trade that at least
um
but yeah
it's my oh let me drink my coffee before
you guys start
let me drink my coffee before slim gets
in here
it was you guys night last night i
actually had a
really good sleep um
you know pretty good day
you know my kiddo
feeling sick but um
you know other than that it's it's been
an amazing day
um for us we
just the fact that i can be home
and just like hang with him
there's no priorities no obligations no
nothing it's like whatever you want to
do today kid
i i really like that bruce
yeah he's over there
now let me put this back here
so we should be coming somewhere down
into this area um
this is a fractal here followed by an
imbalance in between here
good morning i just want to say about
watching you yesterday using your
teachings i made 200 on my
account challenge in 10 minutes
that's so great i'm happy to hear that
uh walter i'm happy to hear that uh
you know i i definitely want to hear
more stories like that like that's why i
teach as open and in public as i do
hey hey little boy be quiet
he always gets loud when he hears me
start talking
but um yeah i'm happy to hear that
that's that's great man i i want people
to pass their challenges you know make
money consistently
just with the little bit of things that
we learn here today
you know like every day i come into the
market and want to make sure that it's a
killer day for somebody or it's some
information that somebody can take home
and
you know like
do something different when they're not
on the charts with me or you know it's i
just want everybody to learn this i feel
like um
i only took four months to learn this it
was really really easy for me i think
it's just the way that um
my brain processes things
and it just was really easy for me so um
you know i'm out here trying to crack
the code for others whenever i was
learning and um i was teaching some of
my friends the interesting part was if
they couldn't understand something
i would go and learn whatever it is that
they were learning just to find an
easier way for them to understand what
they were learning and this is even
while i was learning something entirely
different
so all the concepts that i have all the
stuff that i teach here
it was just
taking things and making it easier
hey hey
people don't like crying babies on the
airplane
i doubt people want to hear babies
acting up while you're trading
we're gonna do the top down soon i came
what's up how's everything what's up man
what's up i've been tied up this morning
with this little guy but
what's up how's everything i'm gonna get
back to you
i i wish you guys were um
this this is why i mean we're making a
discord we're working on it i'm gonna
stop putting pressure on on the media
guy um but
you know with with the um
with the discord i wish that um
you know like when we have it i'm going
to be putting a lot of these things in
it so you guys can see
like
exactly you know what's happening um
this morning i was um i was talking to
someone
and
i had sent this to them
uh actually no it wasn't this morning
this was last night
i sent this to them i said pay attention
to these levels
you know i had one right here where
price had already hit so that was ruled
out
the next important level i had was 873
and i said price can come down here tap
into this area and
push up
you know give us another high so price
actually kept trading higher and higher
you know from from this point um it
actually did not
come down to this area um it actually
started to go up um but if you look at
it this morning
this is where i tell you guys to pay
attention to areas and keep them for
later on
this morning
look at this 873
price comes down
taps right into it and this is market
open the 930 candle
if you had this level already it would
have been so easy just to be like oh
that hit the exact level to get in
and bam
you'd have been up like this to the next
area up here
because all of this is mitigated going
up
maybe a little imbalance here that you
might find some resistance at yeah there
was a little bit there
but then straight up to the areas up
here so from here to here just like that
and not just that
um i was talking to somebody this
morning i told them there was a
rejection up here at
30195.
um
actually i have it here yeah
look i said
i said we're gonna get a rejection of
the imbalance at 30195
and
then you know we'll have a shift down
and i said we may stop here but we also
could stop here and i said depending on
what happens here
we can get rejected from
this area here
and possibly run the low
and
you know if you look at it we got
rejected from this area here
and then we ran the lows all the way to
this area
so
from
30195 to
29873 back up to the same area
and all of that you you see that this
stuff is there with the timestamps and
everything you know like
this is why the discord is going to be
so powerful because
these are things that i'm just like
randomly thinking you know oh it's a
possibility that that could happen and
then like
boom look look
that's
that's insane i mean
i when i was a part of like other groups
they weren't doing things like this you
know like
forecasting and and
you know like there was none of that it
was just like all right we're gonna
enter trade here you know
and it's like
all right 12 pips should be good clothes
right here you know and it's like
clearly you didn't know what they were
doing but i mean you look at this this
is from this morning you know um
321 pips down
and then
300 pips back up
and that would have been in one hour
i literally told her
watch the rejection
of the imbalance at 30195
rejected from there and kept falling
yeah you had a little push up but i said
it could tap that area and continue it
did
and
you know we just kept going
you know there was this little area that
i had right here to the left a little
tiny area that i was saying price can
you know
get a little uh scalp off of look it tap
the area
look at this
tap the s and d here
pushed up tapped into the imbalance and
then left 71 pips just off of a little
tiny area that that you notice to the
back and you go from target to target as
i always say
you know so
these
it's it's rare in the market
that
these these areas
you know don't account for anything
these areas are very very important
areas
they do account for things so
you know that's just what some people
have to understand like if there's a
rejection somewhere there's a reason why
whether it's on this time frame or the
the two minute or eight minute or the
hourly or whatever it is
there's definitely
a reason why and if you find out the
reason why that rejection happened
then you begin to search more and more
for the different reasons why rejections
happen
all throughout the chart and now the
chart begins to tell you a story
you know it tells you
that it's going from s and d to
imbalance from imbalance to imbalance
from s d to s d and that's the only way
that price moves
price only moves
to s ds and imbalances that's it
nothing else yeah we get the run of
certain highs as you know manipulation
at times and then you have a huge push
down or runner below huge push up yeah
we get those
but it seems as though the the algorithm
runs to
you know um imbalances and smds alone
so you know with with supply and demand
trading
that's one half of it that's a very
powerful way to trade
the other is to incorporate sorry and
incorporate um
you know
uh the imbalances
and once you incorporate the imbalances
in it now you have like
a versatile way of trading
because you're understanding and balance
reactions you're understanding
reactions from s and d's
and coupling those two together
with how price moves where price goes to
you know
that is it would change your trading
style forever so you don't even have to
do like the little candlestick thing
that i look for in there or you know
like the bullish flip or like you don't
have to do any of that if you don't want
to
just learn order flow learn learn the
way price moves
and then just watch for
you know rejections in those areas
dave are you going to travel this
weekend no no i'm actually going to be
home um
a little one is sick you know so
gotta um
you know make sure he's good before i i
go anywhere so yeah i'm gonna be stuck
home this weekend but it's it's father's
day weekend as well so you know it's not
really stuck i guess i don't know for me
father's day is every day you know like
my kids always tell me
you know i love you or
you know you're the best dad ever and
and these are just like they spend a lot
of time with me you would think that the
parent they were the most is the parent
they
you know have such
anger towards but i mean
they they just really enjoy themselves
and and i'm grateful for that you know
so when i hear little things like oh
you're the best dad ever
you know it's like yeah i know you know
because i try to be you know and and i
try to make every day
you know father's day you know or every
day thanksgiving or everything christmas
you know like
we don't get caught up in the the
holiday things i mean if people do
that's fine we'll celebrate with others
that's okay um but
you know other than that like
you know every day's father's day
father's day for me it's just
pretty sucky that that he's sick so this
could be coming down to this area here
let's uh see what it's going to do
to there
yeah let's see what it does here
sorry wait where did i put this
i'm tripping i'm so sorry guys
the last low
the last
candle
down
if it's large enough
it should send it that way
because if you look if you look at this
um
this here was already mitigated
look at this
let's take it to this high here
you see how this tucked above
like that tucked above that high
and then it dipped back into the area
tapped into the center of this area and
then traded out of it
so this was already mitigated so it's a
possibility that this continues down
uh
hey dave good morning what's up sean
how's everything good morning good
morning
my um uh
media guy uh he suggested that i change
the camera angle because he was saying
that uh
the other one looked a bit weird i don't
i don't think so you know like
i kind of like the one a little better i
had like my my sexy side on it and now
i gotta look like i'm cross-eyed over
here
so yeah i hope you guys are fine with
the uh the angle change on that
um so this
filled this imbalance here
let's check and see if it does anything
here
because it may just be an imbalance fill
to
continue sometimes that can happen but
this candlestick pattern
you know let's see let's see if it runs
this high
because there's an area down here that i
could still tap
into before continuing up
i didn't do the uh
the top down yet guys um and wait a
couple more minutes
um
just so people don't miss it those top
down to everything man oh my gosh like
that
they really give you some some great
direction for the day
um i think yesterday
what did i
what did i say yesterday there was some
levels that i gave i just don't remember
what they were
um oh it was on the other chart why am i
on this one
oh that's my personal chart that's why
yeah yesterday here we go
look at this
this was from the top down this exact
area
you see the top on this
from six seven we marked out a couple of
these areas where we can get some
you know reactions from but a possible
reversal to head back up
and if you look we got one right here
right on this line
at 767. i don't think i don't remember
if this was from the hourly or or the 15
minute it might have been the 15 minute
not too short no no it might have been
the hourly um but yeah look at this
perfect tap on the line drawdown where
and and look at
look at the height that it goes
look at that
474 pips
just from the touch of this area
this is what i was saying about these
how strong these areas are from the
higher time frames and when you get
touches to those areas there might be
like a little dip below it
but then there's like a huge push coming
out of that area and then i also
mentioned um
on stream another thing i said that um
i said that price was probably going to
dip back into here to run the lows
and i said that it would have to come
above i think it was two nine eight nine
eight i had mentioned on stream you guys
can go back to receipts of that
but it was two two nine eight nine eight
i was saying that if it broke that area
then you know that price is flipping
bullish
and that's after it dips in here if it
dips below this and then comes up to
break this area here
the ar
this is this is where white golf comes
in
because this this whole thing is
wyckoff's accumulation
and then it pushed up after wyckoff
teaches you what happens in
consolidation
so i'm a firm firm believer in in white
golf i mean look it
usually you know gives us this
accumulation and it usually brings us
back up
to the high in which it came from and if
you look to the left
we hit that
bam
and then reject it from there too so
imagine finding the cell i mean the by
up to the cell
you know just paying attention to these
little things and i'm seeing this stuff
mind you from the one minute time frame
but as i said time is fractal time
frames do not matter you could see the
higher time frames on whatever time
frame you're on i could be on the
seconds chart and still see the higher
time frame
you know once you expose yourself to
charting in that way like it doesn't
matter what time frame you're on you're
still seeing all of the same things
you know so this this essentially here
is wyckoff and i think um john had
mentioned it um
when when it first came down he said
looks like wyckoff is happening he
actually started learning white golf
with me um
you know but there's usually the i said
if we dip below this low over here we
could tap into one of these areas and if
we push up and break
the 898 level
then we're gonna flip bullish
so we pushed up we broke it this is the
spring in wyckoff this is the retest of
the spring
so we had where the spring was tapping
and then we also had the retest of it
too
so we had both of these areas
that we could use
and
and the reason why i say both is because
look this is an imbalance in here
price came and tapped into the imbalance
and left
not even the the supply or i mean not
even a demand zone below not even an s d
below
probably tapped on the top of it maybe
yeah the top of it
but if you were waiting for it to come
to the 50 of it it left without you
you had a
imbalance here
with an s and d zone
right below it
which makes this whole area a likely
target
so we flipped up usually after the
spring
you usually break the ar
right here
and if you guys go
if learning if you guys aren't familiar
with white golf and you go and learn it
you you'd understand what i'm saying but
the ar
usually after the spring is made
this is the spring
down into here we dip below a previous
low
after the spring is made we usually have
a push up like that
and that breaks the
ar to the left
so we came back in to test
within the area
and then we were out of here
so there's an entry here
there was an entry here
there were other entries along the way
you know dipping back into imbalances or
you know dipping back into certain s and
d zones you know all the way up all of
this going up all the way up
unmitigated areas that price is coming
back to touch into
and once it taps into those areas you
see these three candles here these like
three down movements this one this one
and this one you see that stab in the
middle
you see how it's always present
well not always but most times this has
a stab in the middle
this
stab in the middle
like if you if you pay attention to
to price and the way these things move
like this here
stab in the middle or on a larger scale
since this is wike off this whole thing
is wipe off
wykoff ends with a stab down and then
starts to make its way up and just like
it ends with a stab down is the same way
that it ends with a stab up
and that's why people tend to think they
see
you know or not think they see they they
call it inverse head and shoulders
you know or head and shoulders pattern
when they're not understanding that it's
wipe off happening in there
so they see the youtad created
and then price comes down and gives you
that
you know um
that uh what was the show of weakness or
sign of weakness
and then it pushes back up to test the
utad
but
they're not seeing that they're seeing
that
sorry they're seeing that it pushes back
up
and for them they believe like i think
this is this is how i explained it
yesterday
look at this they see this as a inverse
head and shoulders
sorry
here
and then they get in at the neckline
break here
but what happened with this neckline
break
tapped you in and then took you out
immediately
you see that
you got tapped in at the neckline break
whether you chose this as the neckline
break or whether you chose this as the
neckline break
you would have got tapped in and then
taken out immediately
with the spring
and that's why i tell people all the
time
do not i mean i get that that it might
be easier for you in the beginning to
learn these things but do not trade
these
if they're absent of structure do not
trade them just because you see them i
told you it's it's almost like a
like a 30 percent
you know win rate on those
there's no way
so if you look
now if you look here
sorry
if you look here here's another one
down
into this
back up
up into this
and then we come down into this area
here but look we come back up you get
tapped into you thinking this is a
neckline or maybe this is a neckline and
then what happens we get pulled back
below
the shoulder that they tell you to place
your stop loss behind
so price takes you out
and then rips up in the direction that
you expected it to go into
why because you traded this absent of
structure
so i continue to you know try to talk to
people about these these retail patterns
because yes it's easy to see i see it
all the time
but do not use it while it's absence of
structure
because if it's absent of structure
that's like a 30 percent
win rate
win rate really really does matter the
30 win rate
rr matters too of course
you know but
like if you get your win rate up
your rr moves with it
andrew what's up how's everything good
seeing you man glad to have you let me
finish you just remind me to drink my
coffee because you get me
going you get me talking
let me see what was the other chart that
we had
so it didn't hit the imbalance
here
there's another small imbalance within
[Music]
so the imbalance above here as well as
an imbalance here
but we're coming down to so we're within
this area we could be coming to this
area
[Music]
again here
let me just take this whole area
there's also a minor imbalance within
here
right on this line so let's see how
price
uh reacts to it
i'm thinking if it's an imbalance i
should use um
green lines
and if it's um
s and d zone i should use a different
color
look at this pattern now let's see if we
get a flip above here
let me see so see we hit this fractal
got rejected
actually let me let me actually do the
top down um for you guys uh
let me not get beside myself
because i could just read probably
straight up like just on the chat let me
all right
oh let me go to the other chart
yeah so this is a chart that we do our
top downs on
sometimes i don't be wanting to erase
certain things
because all of the
important information on it
so
let's see
uh
let's delete this
now you ready you guys already know
where i'm going to start or hopefully
you guys do we always start at just as
akeem said
the open high low close of the candle
the previous day candle
so look at this
this was pushing down
when the candle opened up there was an
imbalance that was left between
this area here and up here
so price went back up to tag the
imbalance so
that's why i had a i believe the other
day you guys saw me place a green line
on the left side of the previous candle
and to the right side i extended it so
you could see that when it fails the
imbalance oftentimes it just continues
to sell off
so these are things to like these these
little things
like things to do when you're doing your
little um
not your little but when you're doing
your top downs um
you know just consider that
um consider these imbalance fills that
that price often does
let me see the price tap this imbalance
here
nope
so this is an area that price could
still have a fake pump up to
tap and then reject so we think mark is
going bullish tapped into this area and
then just could titties down
or if if this is flipping bullish and
tap into this area dip back into this
area and then go up
so we're going for this low here
i know some of you guys are like stop
talking and do the top down
slim what's up look at you reminding me
that i'm forgetting my coffee you see
andrew you see what slim does to me
so yeah this this is coming down to here
it should run this low
um
often times when we get the run of the
low we get a huge spike up
um after so just be mindful of that
let me just look for some other areas
that's here so if it runs that low
there's a possibility that it runs this
load too
are you guys fine with this music it
just you flip to something entirely
different i'm fine with it i just want
to make sure that you guys like
so yeah we have these two oh i have 653
on the other chart too so that's good
consistency you see you guys consistency
i'm not giving you one strategy today
and another tomorrow
so it's friday um friday could
definitely
you know like give us a push down here
because friday's usually like the
sell-off day um so we can definitely do
that armani what's up good morning good
morning
uh he's shannon what's up how's
everything
morning morning
he works for the caffeine industry and
he wants you to become addicted watch
out
yes i know please don't make me an
espresso i feel like i'm
having a overdose or something like that
please don't i'm trying to kick the
habit of coffee too really really trying
to kick the habit badly but
it's difficult look look see
so we run we run the low
there was like a little pump up that it
started to make just now when i saw it
but now it looks like it's a
continuation i'm saying that this is the
next area that we could potentially
target but let me look to the left
to see oh we don't have anything here
jeez
yikes
yeah so i think i think we're we're
running we might be running down to that
low let me
let me just double check um
more of this area
uh
let's see the one hour
um
where's price currently at 724 oh yeah
no no i think we're running this low
guys yeah so
yeah i think that's that's where we're
headed
let me just look behind it then
because there could be something back
here
that
um
let me see
let me see if it hit this area already
oh yeah it did right here yep took it
out
i'm telling you these areas are so bomb
like
geez
so it could have a little tiny bounce
here
um since this wasn't entirely mitigated
and it could have a touch
uh
here
by the way guys i'm not wearing the same
shirt i have a bunch of champion shirts
so need to get that out there
good morning good morning derek how's
everything good morning
so look these these two areas are where
price can possibly top and you know give
some movement up or or just continue
down um
that's after it ends up running the low
of this so it has this this area between
here
from six five three to six two one
and then ultimately we can capture the
low as well right here
all right let's go back and look at
where price is
so look
we got that tap
on the run of our low
we came further down into it
and now we have
you know slight of
a slight push back up um i told you
after every structural low is ran you
usually get like a a huge tuck back up
in that direction i don't know why i
don't know what the reason is but this
could actually be signs of like a
reversal right now happening on a lower
time frame
right here
because you had price come and go below
it
and then price trade it back up into it
and then price trade it lower
so after price trades lower and then it
goes up and it runs like i know that's
ugly right there but it it runs the high
then you have a dip back into the area
and then
it leaves like that and this is a very
ugly drawing i'm not an artist at all so
you just listen to the explanation i
know it might hurt your eyes
so
so we tap into this
um there's nothing i mean this this is a
strange place
you know oh sorry
this is a strange place where where
prices now because
um
you know we haven't been down to these
levels since um
the whole gamestop run
um you guys remember that right
we haven't been to these levels since
then let me see if i can go back a
little further
and meet an area back here
sometimes with the replay tool it might
get you past some of the data that that
you don't see when you scroll back you
can do it at least two times i think
um
all right yes so we're here
oh look i'm looking for right here oh
geez i already did it twice let me see
if i can do it another time
ah there we go yes yes
so the replay tool can get you further
back than just like the data that you
have it's just that if you flip to a
different time frame right now like a
lower time frame is going to take it all
away
so it's best to um
use it like that
the the replay tool
let's see so we put in
we put in this low here
and then
we have
this too
so let's see now we have these areas
here
and these are areas to the left where we
could potentially
i mean i know this looks striped up and
crazy um
but there's a method to my madness uh so
i'll go back and and show you guys
so where are we
all right so we're still rummaging
around that area let me go on this time
frame okay this is one minute
all right so you see how i said um
that we could have
um that dip below
and then that push up
and then the dip back into the area like
the little drawing that i was doing
that's exactly what happened
um based on what i was seeing from the
the higher time frame and this is what i
say you know with the higher time frame
you guys can see the higher and lower
time frame across every time frame
they're all doing the same thing at the
same time it's just being able to spot
that so look there's this little s and d
here it could just come crashing through
it you know
because this is still pretty early so
they could still be engaging in
sell-offs and guys i realized um
something super neat
um
you know just an observation don't quote
me on it
but
i realized that
spreads are higher
when hedge funds are selling off
so usually if you're trading a
particular pair
and
you're you're getting higher than usual
spreads
often times it seems as though
those are the times when hedge funds are
um you know in the market and and
creating a lot of activity so um that's
just something
neat to to understand
um you know whenever you're trading i'm
not saying every time you see it you
know like jump in the cell or whatever
it is but
you know it seems like um
most of the activity that's happening
with hedge funds and corporations um
when they're usually selling on buying
in droves the spreads get a little bit
higher hey what's up what's up erin
what's up what's up how's everything
good seeing you back man happy to see
you
so you see how we tapped into this smd
right here guys
i told you that we could have like on
my little ugly drawing that i had
mentioned i said we dip below the area
we come back up
and then
we come back into the area and it would
probably run maybe a high somewhere
within here but we come back into the
area and then we push out of it do we
push out of it back to the s and d here
maybe but we could also push up above to
some of these areas that don't have
mitigation like this one this one here
uh
this tapped into this area but not as
much so it can be like another thing
here that you know you might get a
slight rejection from and even possibly
here
so this area this area this area this
here you could possibly get a rejection
but these rejections are what forms the
trend
so when you see
price going up and then it starts to
retrace
we're looking at the areas that are
starting the retracements
so we're trading from
beginning of the retracement to the end
of it
and then from the end of that all the
way to the continuation
that's what all of this movement is it's
just creating the trend so everything
that it hits
every area that we mark out that it hits
it's hitting that area to tuck back and
create the lower low
then we know that since it already got
mitigated when price is coming back up
we know prices going through the area
so that's something that that i want you
guys to um
you know think about when we're trading
like super powerful information um
a lot of times people don't know when
it's going to pull back they don't know
why it's pulling back they just throwing
their fib up and hoping that it comes to
the 61.8 and it's absent of like actual
rules so that's a little um gem for you
guys a little nugget there so this was
already mitigated here
i believe that this should push up above
this high because
when price
looked like when price dipped below here
it came back up to mitigate the area and
then
left
so let's see what it does here
uh maybe this can come back to this
fractal here or even this imbalance when
within here you can come and tap it and
then
continue higher i mean and there's this
little s and d right within here so we
can break through that tap into this
fractal or
into
this area down here
and if you guys have any charts you want
me to look at like anything you're in
long term anything from the higher time
frame
any market
you know if you can draw it on a rock
and send it by picture i could help you
trade it you know so just let me know
i don't mind um going back to oh i did
have something in oil
i believe
yeah look at this look at this this is
amazing look at this
so
so i saw price pushing back up to this
area
and i was like um
i was saying to myself
you know maybe we'll get a tap up into
this smd here
and then if we get a tap away
we could potentially come down
to this s and d here because i told you
price moved from s and d to s and d and
balance to imbalance or s d to imbalance
and balance to s and d things like that
so i said okay there's another slight
imbalance in here
maybe price can move up to this one
because there's an imbalance here but
then there's also an imbalance directly
behind it too
so price made an imbalance in both you
know both places you know of of price so
it tapped up into this and i said maybe
we get a rejection here and probably
find a rejection out of the area
you know and i i left it at that i just
left these lines here i was like you
know okay it could work out that way
now come back and look at the chart and
we're sinking to hell directly from the
area that
that i have mentioned
look at this 394 pips
just because it is tap here like when
when you when you learn how to uh nasdaq
btc ripple okay when you learn how to um
you know like re-price you can get in on
little opportunities that can turn into
longer ones
you know like you you don't really have
to like
utilize i'm going from here to here
sometimes there's price gives you no
shift no change in it
so when price gives you no change in it
then you continue with that and you just
manage your risk by moving your
your um your stops up
you know so let me go to knives that
should be falling with everything else
same way
um
maybe a tap into here
but if it falls below this i expect the
same stuff that's going on with the us30
oh naz has some area down here us-30
doesn't look at that let me see if s p
500 has oh s p does
that's strange then
[Music]
i don't know why all of this is moving i
don't
know all right right here
trading b is always giving me some
some issues uh
just double check make sure nothing's
open oh spotify is
is is every like you guys see me fine
i'm not like glitching or anything like
that can you guys hear me
let me properly
let me just double check this guys
all right
yeah usually um the quality gets a
little more choppier
um
when um
i'm on this
let me see so
yeah th this has no area back here so
that's interesting that um
if there's no area back here in the us
30 it's interesting to see oh that's
what it is
um tech stocks are probably doing well
it's doing a little better than the
stocks on okay not now i see what it is
so let's see we got a double bounce in
this area
we just took out this low here
and then we may end up
trading there's an imbalance here so
watch this
could get a reaction at that but there's
also this little snd
mini snd in the middle that can be
responsible for this
couldn't come and close this imbalance
here
and then
continue up if it wanted to
[Music]
yeah
so smd here as well that it's
sort of
leaving behind but it could mitigate it
[Music]
um so
what what um what time frame do you
yeah sound video just fine okay um what
time frame do you usually trade nas from
maybe i should just give you the top
down on that that might be a little
better oh this is a nice area finazz
right here
this little spot here
it's a nice little spot watch that area
you could have um
a little push out of it
and this is from the hourly so
if it does come down to this area you
might have a little movement around this
line
and then
like going back to the top to attack the
upside
but with the upside it could also just
be coming to here
yeah it could also be coming up to here
so you could have a
retracement up tap into this area and
then
continuation down or you could have a
tap right here back up to this area or
the low could be ran
and then it comes up into this area and
then
then continues down because it looked
like um looks like it might continue to
sell off
um today
um
hour one
after that
oh okay
um
so yeah this this is a little uh
one hour scenario um i just gave you
price tap this imbalance already here it
looks like
no it did not
so there's an imbalance here
um it's another imbalance directly above
another imbalance directly above another
ballast directly wow this is
a lot a lot of imbalance here geez
you see there was this larger imbalance
here that price came up and tapped into
and then continued shorting um so let me
actually look at the four hour
all right so we tapped into this smd
here on the four hour
right here
um
we also are back in this area here
now that this is
yeah we also typed here but i don't
really see this being an important area
being this mitigated
right after it was created
um we go down to 15
look at what's happening here
so it looks like the 15 we are touching
this area so yeah we could be um
possibly trying to head back up
let me just take this here
send that across
take this area here move that out
yeah so we did get a tap into this area
we could have
you know like sort of slight push up
um from this area so this you might see
a double bottom
on the um
the uh lower time frame
you know
which
this slightly looks let me see the ohlc
on this uh
zero nine three six seven
[Music]
zero nine three eleven
so this is slightly lower than this
um
which could make the case for it
heading back up
could have a rejection at this
fractal here
if it does come up comes back down into
the area so
let's say it goes like this
up to that
comes back into this area
taps maybe into whatever imbalance that
might have been left behind so we still
have five minutes to finish forming this
candle this candle could eventually be a
red candle down here so if that's the
case then this doesn't apply but um
could tap up into there quickly reject
the way tap back into wherever the start
of this s and d would be
um
could tap back into that and then
this s and d
to the imbalance up here or to the s and
d further above
that could be your target if this
happens so mind you tap up into here
projection away from here and then push
up unless something is happening on a
lower time frame we're showing that
it'll be a stronger push um within that
area so that's just what i have for nas
in the the interim
um daily it's the same daily as um
us 30.
um possibly running this low here
right here
you know i was wondering if i um
should do like a sunday zoom
you could possibly run this low here so
just pay attention to this sometimes you
can run the low and then have a huge
push
um
to the other direction and you see how
it came up and filled the imbalance here
this is why you pay attention to the
higher time frames just to get a little
idea of what price could be doing from a
higher time frame standpoint
and you're looking at what
you know what's being laid out on the
lower time frame
um
okay so i did 15
and i did hour for nas four hour um it's
probably like the oh we did four hour
already that's right we came here so we
said we tapped into this area
you know pushed back up um this candle
still has two hours on it to go so this
candle could be down here and before you
know it you know like
it'll be up into up into this thing here
or it can be well below this down here
so you can have the rejection to the run
of this low
which the run of this low is likely
today you know so just you know consider
that
um
but yeah you this candle could
end up closing any any way you want so
we just got to look at the lower time
frames to kind of get an idea of
um
what what could potential like how this
candle could potentially close because
this is this has two hours left on it
um
and uh you mentioned uh
bitcoin
uh bitcoin on what time frame
yeah so i i was um on sunday i think it
was a sunday it might have been a sunday
i don't know um
i was talking to a friend about shorting
this um i think it was in a 15-minute
time frame i tell them it's best to look
at bitcoin in the 15-minute time frame
because um
because it's so volatile there's so many
wicks and drags everywhere and it's hard
to like mark up uh zones you know so
it's better to look at zones from the 15
minute time frame because
it's just overall easier to read price
on that for bitcoin
um
so i told them the shorting from here i
said we get to run up the low we get a
tap back into the area and then it
leaves so i said
you don't want to get out of this area
or this area unless you see some type of
bullish you know shift in price
and
look at where it ended up going
from
28 000
the low of this is 20.
so 8 000 ago i mentioned bitcoin was
shorting
and it was just to like some of these
humble areas i didn't think it was gonna
run the low of 25 000 anything like that
but if you don't see any change in
behavior
you continue to take this thing down
there's no no structural highs being ran
for you to want to get out
and that's you know
intermediary structure or major
structure
so
this whole thing this whole ride down is
something that you know if he stayed in
he could have caught but this was
i don't even you know what i i wasn't
even
yeah i wasn't even here in new york when
i mentioned this to him
i wasn't even home i think i was
traveling when i saw this
so it's just like those little things
you know like
but yeah the bitcoin is um
oh four hour down okay
yeah because i tend to like just come on
weekends and and
still shopping my skills sort of
using that
um
so
see we have an imbalance here that price
already reacted to we have another
imbalance here
um
we could come into somewhere within this
area and react
um back up
yeah like somewhere within this area
yeah so it's it's somewhere between
i would say more so it's somewhere
between 19 and and 17.
um
but for right now um
i would just have this as
a mark of where price could touch
and this is the imbalance let me see if
it actually hit it already
yeah look at that imbalance tap right
here
this is what i'm saying zone is own and
balance and balance balance to zone zone
and balance you know all the same thing
on every market everywhere all the same
thing you just learn this and it becomes
like so much easier for you
so um
there could be a double bottom here um
this
tap into this area
you see imbalance to zone
to potentially
zone in a smaller time frame maybe
somewhere around here
um and then push up above the area
um that it traded out of that could
potentially happen those things
you know often happen so
you have this low put in your price
trade above it
and then price comes back down into it
so this could just be mitigating it from
a lower time frame
let me see so you get another
bounce in here
um
this could be wyckoff happening
you know s-c-a-r-s-t
sign of strength
uh
um
this could potentially still run some of
these lows here
but if it doesn't then
um you should see some movement back up
into this area potentially
this s and d here
maybe back up into this area at 21 and
then could fall out of 21 and end up
running all the lows here at 20
and then after
coming from
20 you could have a huge push up that
runs this area
21 760.
you could dip below here end up running
21 760. if it runs 21 760 and it pushes
up
then that means that
you know we're looking to
come back to at least some of these
areas maybe up here within the 25 region
or up here within
the 27 region that's only if this
continues to
you know play out the way it is but it
looks like it's wyckoff's accumulation
happening here
um can you check eth ethereum theorem
should be the same thing
um
i think it's a four hour
just take a look at where price is right
now
prices here within this area price could
have a little pump from here
this is um
s d zone edits in
could have a slight pump up from here
but if it falls below here
this area seems mitigated already
um
so does this area here
but there could be a
a slight
tap
here um
yeah there could be a slight tap here
so if it ends up running
this
if it ends up running the low of um
1040 it can go to 966.
um
and if it goes below
you can end up
tapping into this imbalance here
at 862 and that could be
like a very strong imbalance to
um send it back up
i don't even know why i put that there i
was trying to get the line
yeah it could be um
strong imbalance to uh send it back up
so we already hit the first area you see
how we reacted to it bam
remember that little pattern that i told
you guys about um
this little thing here
so just be mindful again like i said
this could be
you know just digging within this area
to
you know continue up
you know so just pay attention to that
same thing with bitcoin
um and i imagine all the other cryptos
are kind of moving the same way
so um oh and you mentioned xrp right
uh
um
so xrp got rejected out of this smd here
object did i oh no i'm sorry wrong one
huh
rejected out of this smd here i don't
think i put enough coffee in my
coffee oh man
slim gonna make me some coffee now
so let's see it tapped into this fractal
here
we got rejected from
this smd here
now we're coming back into this one that
we just left
so this could be coming into this area
here
um
somewhere around 31
could be shorting down to 31 and
potentially having
a push-up from this direction but if it
doesn't and it runs this low it's more
than likely gonna run the rest of the
lows too
down to 29.
so that's um
what what xrp can do
let me go back and
[Music]
and uh take a look at us 30 see what we
got going on here
[Music]
really good nazar
you see what i'm saying guys
you see like this
i literally just mentioned this to you
guys
talk about how we could essentially come
up
come back into the area and then go
along now we didn't tap into this we
just bowled through it but
from a lower time frame i think we were
on the 15 when i had mentioned it the
same thing happens on every single time
frame
so
we had this push up
rejected from the imbalance
down here found support on the snd
came back up above the area that we got
rejected from came back into the area to
whatever s and d
over here or or imbalance might have
sent this price up and then
we shot up to come to some of these
areas here
over and over and over and over and over
and over again over and over and over
again it happens
so many times so many different ways
like
like wow this is
it's beautiful
you know like i love
i love the charts i
like oh my gosh
this is
this is amazing
remember what i said pay attention to
that little thing that that like the
little stab in the middle that i tell
you guys about like
very very important in the area like
this very very very
important
very important
like once you spot those things it makes
it easier in terms of like the decisions
that you would make to do things
very
very important
like there you go guys
yeah so so this is this is what's
currently happening with the us-30 um
remember there's an smd here this smd
was responsible for breaking structure
to the downside so that's what makes
this important and you get a little
rejection from here but remember we have
this imbalance up above as well as a
larger s and d
above that another imbalance in between
it another like
damn all of these imbalances
what time was this
oh this is where they had pushed price
up and sent it back down
yeah like this this is
very important to pay attention to the
zones the the like everything very very
important to pay attention to
let's see did i
what did i have for this
this is from a higher time frame
trying to figure out where this gold
so i have no idea where this is from but
i know that if i was on this time frame
it would be just like this
bam and balance tap
push up from there
and it's just i mean
i didn't create these concepts and rules
i've heard of it and i just spent time
watching it
and i just found ways to make it easier
you know like i always say that um
my uh
this could be from
[Music]
is this
maybe this is an hour
uh yes that was the hourly imbalance
that's why i had that a little higher um
but usually if i'm day trading
the highest that i'll look at for the
day is
it's it's usually the the 15. um i'll go
to the hourly if i don't have any
clarity on the 15 but the 15 is is great
for day trading you really just got to
find zones on the 15 and just use the
zones on the 15 to
take certain trades from
or that could be your your like
current bias for
you know where prices
see look like we mentioned
we said that we can push up
come back into the area we tap into this
s and d that it's leaving behind
remember i said pay attention to the smd
that we're leaving behind
it can tap back into this area
and then
go long from here
and what do we do we wait log for a bit
like this it's i'm trying to get you
guys to understand how how powerful
these um
like seeing these little things are um
and it'll help you with scalping and
help you with any long trades you need
to take and you could utilize this stuff
using like a penny lot size if you're
not comfortable if you want to like
learn someone else's system learn a
little differently learn how to
implement this into your own type of
trading you could still forward test and
you could forward test with a penny lot
it's pennies you know like
why not just forward test with pennies
and it helps you to to understand the
market a little better
it helps you to to notice a little more
um
stability at least
[Music]
within a live market because everybody's
a genius in hindsight everybody
and that's why you barely have people
coming out here to to do this stuff live
on youtube the hiding behind zooms and
and all these different things because
some days it's a hit and other days it's
not you know and and or most days it's
not you know
so um
some of them be called little 10 pip
trades
you know
i mean that that was a confidence factor
for me so i used to just take 10 pips
and get out so i'd be like that
take that little bit and i'm out
and then i'm like no but this is going
100 pips after it hit here i'm
discounting you know or selling myself
short
and then that's when
you know i started to become more
comfortable started understanding zone
zone and balanced imbalance you know all
those different things and i'm that kind
of help to
um
you know sort of make my training take
off
and just
essentially made it different than
than anybody else's trading that i know
i'm not saying that there are other
people who who are not profitable
there's a lot of people who are
profitable
um with their own trading styles even if
i don't necessarily agree with them
they're still profitable from it
you know so it's just really finding
something that works for you
i don't know that for me precision is
like the only thing that i would ever
consider
like you know working for me
i get that other people get more
accurate even down to like
the one second time frame but
you know i'm comfortable here i mean if
you could learn this technique and trade
on the 15 second
great
on the 15 second you guys can
learn this from the the one minute you
can trade this on any time frame so if
you go to the 15 second and you see
these things happening faster oh my gosh
you'd be great
hey duraj what's up how's everything how
are you from india
great peace and love from jamaica
yeah man
yeah
my friend john he swear he's he's uh
jamaican i don't know why he he just
he swears he
he whenever i talk to him
he's always like saying all of the words
he knows in one sentence
yeah yeah
i didn't have the nerve to tell me that
he really don't trust jamaicans right
yeah right
he was just kidding by the way
yeah so we we dropped below this low i
want to see if it's going to come back
and tap into this area here um it could
be there's a little imbalance in between
here
you know like somewhere between here
um
want to see if it's going to tap up into
maybe some of these areas and then
you know continue short
let's see are we going to run the high
and then come back below it
sometimes this is where um
using candlestick structure can
you know mess you up because um
you see you have this area up you get
the slow you get the high
and you get a run of the low
and then you come up usually you come up
into this area here
but if you see
price came all the way up to
the neck
of this area here
and that's where it can get kind of
scary
um
you know for
not necessarily knowing whether price is
going to short from the area or not
sometimes it can go just a wick above it
and that wick above it guess where it
could be tapping
right here
so you can get a wick above it and it's
going above this area
that you have usually with candlestick
structure but this is happening within
the area of your imbalance with an area
also that's directly above it
so you have to account for
just what's
like slightly above this area
and this could be the candle that pulls
above this high
grabs the high
pushes up to here that gives it the
little
stab like look
and then
trades away like that's a possibility
like sometimes those things happen you
know
so you just want to
be open to that like when you're
utilizing the candlestick structure in
in certain areas you want to be open to
like just just a little
shift or change in price
and understand that
you might have the right idea here
when you're looking for that
but just in the wrong area
you know so that could happen
there's still other areas up here guys
um
you know just in case this does run
there there's this whole area within
here
[Music]
this whole area here that's a bit
stronger
um
you know than than some of these areas i
told you this s d does matter um
here
no sorry it was this one
yeah but this this smd it comes from a
larger area um
so there's more volume in this area
so this way you got to tap into it right
here at the bottom of it then you got a
quick rejection away
and then
price pushes up this is what i'm saying
when it when it comes up into these s
and d's and it gets these like reactions
from just the tip of it just the bottom
of it
oftentimes i see that it rejects away
and then it goes up and trades through
but it can still trade through it
and then if there's a wick above it
what what can often happen is
that you'll see um the wick goes above
it but the body closes inside and still
makes its way back down
and usually that's like
you know up from an area like this like
this candle here
you see so if you put a um
if you take this
right here
you see how the wick ended up going
above the area
and then price traded down
like at times you i was explaining this
yesterday at times you
you you could have that um
even the dax 30 is doing the same thing
yeah all of them all of them tend to
move with
the the uh the s p 500 so look the us 30
you know obviously we just saw that s p
500 is doing that
nas is doing the same thing
you know this is japan's exchange doing
the same thing
china's exchange is just a little bit
rogue it's a little bit different than
ours
the movements are different maybe it's
just
the fact that
they essentially control the world sorta
you know because they're a major
exporting country um
so they move a little differently than
us
slightly differently um than we do but
yeah all of them they move in in the
same fashion
same exact stuff happening
on every chart i don't know why i was
still looking at nas i thought i was
looking at the us 30 just now
i thought this was the us 30 but
but this is what i'm saying like you
know
pay attention to like before you're
shorting pay attention to certain areas
that are still possibly directly above
it
because
those areas that are directly above
you know like you can get caught up in
trying to short from this area because
you you notice them
candlestick structure
but then candlestick structure absent of
a particular area
is
is where you get jammed up it needs to
be in in an area that's highly likely to
short from
uh any idea why they move like because
um the the us dollar is what dominates
um the rest of the world you know like i
i mentioned yesterday all the debts
everything that um
[Music]
you know like is is tied up into any
debt of another country or paid from one
country to the next most of most
business around the world is dealt with
in the us dollar
so
whatever is happening with the us dollar
is also going to affect other countries
because
the world is dollar dominated
you know so
that's why all of the exchanges tend to
move with it but even um
even at night like or in the asian
session
when the u.s studies closed we tend to
follow the asian exchanges too
you know we tend to follow japan and and
hong kong's exchange also throughout the
asian session
so it's good to
you know potentially look at that as
some sort of um confluence as well
you see look this is this is what i was
talking about like
let's say you you ended up shorting from
here
and
you got caught in a short
pulled you back up
you know and now you're in drawdown up
here
there's always that opportunity to come
back
out of drawdown and potentially into
profit
you know if
you understood what was happening within
this era there wouldn't be a panic for
you
you know yeah it could just push right
out of this area and go straight up you
know like if news happened or something
like that of course it could do that
you know but
you also have to understand that that
there are certain areas that you might
have just gotten a little early i find
it to where sometimes i get in early too
i think i have a trade um
was it
was it gj i think it was
yeah so look at here
[Music]
i drew this let me um
take this out
and i said we were shorting from here
and we went up took the high and then
shorted
back into the area that i thought we
were shorting to
then we went all the way up here
and guess what price pulled all the way
back to come to the area that i said we
were shorting from so even if we missed
it here
this was still an important area for
later on
and i don't know if this was news or
something happened um
with this i don't know what the hell
this was but
we pushed back into the area and then
look at the massive movement up
after just touching the area so so let's
say you know you you took a trade here
you would have immediately
been pulled up into
100 pips
flash like that bam
as soon as you tapped into that order a
hundred pips immediately because news
happened
and i told you guys
news does not
matter at all
it does not
matter
at all like
if if you're good with technical
analysis if you're efficient with it
you can catch the technicals and be like
oh some news happened somewhere what was
that
you know but this this is look this is
one candle
this is a one minute candle like this
from from an area that i said price was
going to
bam tapped into it
and gone
look at this
and it wasn't this line that that i had
mentioned um pressures coming to was the
imbalance that was in here
bam tapped in and you up 100 pips
immediately because news happened and
you were in a safe spot
you were in a spot that you knew stop
losses were back here
because this is where they began to buy
in
why
to shift price above
they bought in here and they are
responsible
for moving structure
so they move structure from the lowest
point of here
this is where they begin to shift
structure from down here
so this becomes a protected low
and if they were to make their way back
down to anywhere
it would be
down to
their protected stop loss
and look right back up
so guess where their new protected stop
losses
here
because this is where they began to
shift structure to the upside
but if you look
structure was shifted here and we put in
another low right here
so if we put in this low
and did we did we get another high
slightly
a little
a little um
smidge above that don't really like that
um
but then if you look we
we shifted down below
we shifted down below it and we went
back up to the smd that was responsible
for the break of structure
this s d is what sent price down
to break the structure
so we head back up to that we tap into
that
and then
we leave down
but this is why understanding s and d's
and and what their purpose
you know is
this is
you know why you consider this because
these are also
this is a high
this is a low
this is a high back in
this is a high
this is a low
so if you see that this is the way the
trend let me actually zoom in so you
guys can see a little better
if you see that this is the way the
trend is going
with these highs and lows
these become protected highs protected
highs protected highs protected highs
and prices not going to shift up above
once this crew once this one here
this high
created this new low
you can expect price to come up to
this area here
and then give you a reaction back down
yeah it could come to the the middle of
the area as well
you know that that's a possibility too
but oftentimes it mitigates like this is
the last high and low it mitigates the
area entirely sometimes
with the s and d or maybe the fractal or
or the imbalance there was an imbalance
play here that rejected it out um there
could have been like a fractal somewhere
up into here but it taps into that area
and then it continues so when you pay
attention to to structure
and
you know
how structure moves and and what are
protected highs and what are not
then you end up staying out of certain
trades like you might have seen price
going up here and
people might have thought okay yeah
we're gonna long and just take out this
high
take out this high and go to this order
block up here or this you know ict order
block or this um you know supply area
whatever it is and then no we get
stumped here
because this is a protected high
according to where structure has gone
down up down up down according to where
structure is going this is a protected
high
so we can come be between this area and
this area we have this entire range to
just play around and create liquidity
all of that you create liquidity with
the equal lows
you give it equal highs
you run it
tap into the area then run the equal
lows
people thinking that
you know this is somewhere to
to um
uh buy from
gives you a little fake boost up
thinking that this is an area to buy
from and then runs it
so you know you you just gotta
consider that make sure you have
structure involved first
and after you deal with structure now
you look for the other things this is
why i don't you know come on and teach
people oh take take the seventy percent
of this take the sixty percent of this
look get in right here and then get out
here you know like i want you to see it
for yourself so when you begin to see it
for yourself it becomes a lot easier for
you to trade on your own
on your own
you know you may not always have the
time to to come on stream i may not
always come on stream i may be traveling
you know but
these principles
they will help you
you know they'll
shift your perspective you know
change the way that you do trade
so this happens everywhere
everywhere the little you know s and d
rejections the imbalance fills you know
like all of this happens everywhere
and i you know want you guys to to
understand that
you know and this is why i teach what i
teach this is the this is why i teach
the way i teach i can trade any time of
the day if i wanted to if if six o'clock
sunday came i could start trading from
six o'clock sunday
i don't i don't have to wait
you're like oh spreads are high even if
the spreads are high
go to the higher time frame now
because the higher time frame is going
to give you more pips
and that would certainly clear the
spread if you're right about your
directional bias in that case
you know so
it's just you know some gems that you
guys uh
might want to consider
um
yeah
i feel like i'd be i'd be ranting to you
guys
they're like oh shut up and find a trade
already
so as we mentioned with this area this
is
this is a pattern that you particularly
particularly see in price that
facilitates a shift up and only because
this oftentimes is wipe off on a lower
time frame
so this is why i tell you guys to to
learn and study why golf because it'll
help you grasp my concepts way faster
way faster
because you're like it gives you an eye
now for it but you have to first learn
what everything is
you gotta first learn what everything
means
and when you learn that
then you're able to participate in the
market with that so i see this low put
in we have this high
then we well first of all we had this
low put in with this one candle
if you were to just take the high and
the low of this one candle this was
responsible for running a low
and taking out a high
so you know that price is going to if
price runs this high it's going to dip
back into the area before leaving
this is your first entry
fine this mitigates this area
you don't get in
because you know this area is mitigated
you didn't see it happen
you have another opportunity when price
trades higher to come back into this
area
take a trade from here
then it goes
so it continues to go and again you look
you see where these rejections are
happening where the trend is building
these rejections are just building the
trend
so
you have
price come into
now this area is making lower lows i
mean higher high higher highs higher
lows
higher low here
we break up above to this area but what
do we do
we tap back into this area before
trading higher
and this is why i said when these wicks
come out of the area that you're looking
to trade from that's okay
this is just called absorption
this is what i tell you guys study
along with white golf
study absorption
study displacement
and
there was another one that i had
mentioned
imbalances look at how could i forget
that
study absorption study displacement
study balances there's a little
imbalance in between here
not sure if price would just tap into
this area and go let's have intense
imbalance and then leave
probably tap back up into this area and
then short maybe from it not too sure
um but it is a possibility
so there are times where price doesn't
tap into the 50 of the imbalance
sometimes you tap a little higher
sometimes it'll just leave that's a
possibility too
yeah inefficiencies and efficiencies
that's exactly it
so study those three things
along with wyckoff oh my gosh your
trading would go to like the next level
those three things will wipe off
next
level and i get it it's going to take
some time to learn those things it will
i mean it took some time for me
you know to to catch on some of it was
difficult i felt like wyckoff was just
like
burning my my eyes and brain cells like
oh my gosh it was
gruesome
but
you know again i was able to
learn a little something from it and
build on top of it i don't expect people
to trade the same way i do yeah there
might be people that have the desire to
you know trade the same exact way that i
do um but
you can take this trading and turn this
into like some next level stuff you know
i can act like i'm the best trader now
and later on you could stomp me out
after learning you know
like all of the people all of the groups
that i joined
i watched how fast i progressed
above them like like a lot faster than
they did and it was simply because um
you know like they
they topped out at learning they learned
one particular
trading style
and they kept at it with that
nothing else they they didn't feel a
need to to learn anything else watch
this um smd up here they didn't feel a
need to learn anything else
and they're fine with trading with their
style as their system they're going to
do it over and over again
all of this stuff that i teach you guys
are from so many different trading
styles that i've seen and been exposed
to but i'm like yeah that's cool but
that could be better you know and then i
find a way to make it better there's
this guy on youtube called
joshua wiseman
he makes all of the um
all of the fast foods actually let me
let me show you guys
yeah
just give you guys a look at this
um
yeah right here look at his first guy
here
so he makes all of the different um
fast foods
um but he has a
section called butt better so he he
shows how to make you know good food for
for cheap as well but he makes a bunch
of things you know like um
the obviously you see snickers here you
know girl scout cookies he's making like
he's making different types of food um
and he's showing you what
it could cost in a restaurant versus
what he he does with four dollars
you know like and it's healthier options
but this guy he makes everything and he
has a section called but better
so he takes whatever it is that he's
he's learned
you know from from these fast food
chains and he makes it
in a better fashion
you know or or healthier ingredients or
even the taste is better
so um
you know like that that's something this
could be coming to feel this imbalance
here
or tap further into the s d zone but
yeah he he has this section called but
better and
the food is really
really a lot better than
than i've ever seen it anywhere you know
um yeah so this could have been the tap
here
um
here maybe
yeah this could have been the tab here
to send it up to one of these smds here
or here
but this was also
coming up the imbalance as well
yeah that that's kind of what i want to
do i want to like
watch other people's styles and
techniques and then make it better you
know like it it doesn't have to be
complicated it just has to have
structure involved and that's why i tell
people i don't trade with indicators i
don't like and i try to get people to
ditch it too because like i said if
trade and view went down one day
and you had access to no indicators and
you're in a trade you're stuck
you know like that's all it takes is for
a billionaire to buy trading view and
glitch the indicators one day or a
couple of days you know oh our servers
are down sorry you know
and everybody's caught out there
so you know you guys just want to make
sure you um
[Music]
you know you you insulate yourself in
that ways by learning the skill without
having to
be guided by
you know like this could be feeling this
imbalance possibly or coming back down
to the snd down here
um
you know just just learning
you know learning it and and not needing
anything
you know to see it or to do it you're
far ahead of so many people within the
industry
far ahead there's only a couple people
that i know don't use indicators at all
um
and i'm not saying that they're the best
traders in the world you know but
they've gotten their system in a way
where
they don't need to use it because they
just read price now do they reprice the
same way i do no
but
it's it's sufficient
you know
like it it makes them profitable
like um uh raja banks
you know wix don't lie he uses the wicks
in a way where
you know like he was able to
take his account from 50 000 to 2
million in one year
that's remarkable that's impressive
um that and
that happens people can do that
um it's very very possible
um
but
you got to have the skill to do it
your skill has to meet
you know like whatever it is that that
so this line was for the imbalance guys
by the way this this line is not here
for anything other than the imbalance
yeah um yeah so you know
he he makes a ton of money you know like
utilizing wicks
and
and that's amazing that's cool that's
his trading style he has the same
discipline does it every day
um regardless of
whatever his personality might be to
some people um
he teaches these things and and other
people learn from him you know there's
other um traitors other streamers who
utilizes his techniques while streaming
i mean i think he's a little upset that
they don't really give him credit but
you know there's other streamers that
utilize that
and sorry guys i was just pulling
something out of my head so
unprofessional right
i don't care opted out of society a long
time ago
so
yeah you know watch this in balance here
guys it could feel the imbalance or
possibly um
tap into the s and d or you can just
leave it in balance there and continue
to trade away
yes exactly raja he he'd be tearing some
of those people up i'm like oh yikes you
know he's
and him and him his little uh
war with daniel savage i don't know what
that's about but they
they gotta hug it out or something i
don't
he sounds like he hates that man
so yeah you know like
like you have some of these streamers
who like
they they do great things with their
trading um they're very profitable with
their trades then you have other
streamers who don't take trades at all
like i didn't i didn't find a trade
today didn't find a setup whatever it is
and it's like
what yeah
the amount of pears and stuff that you
can trade in general even if it was
exotics
i would go to mexico new zealand right
now if or somebody give me an exotic
pair i can go on that
and just trade an exotic pill like
something that people don't trade
something super high spreads maybe or
whatever it is like i could i could do
that
you know whatever it is anything it
doesn't matter it's the same stuff over
and over in every single market you see
what i said we can probably try to fill
the imbalance but if not we just have a
continuation down
so there's a continuation down
um
we want to make sure we're not going to
tap into this
and then head back up
to let me see
yeah here just want to make sure we're
not
doing this and we should be coming below
this
hopefully actually wait
yeah so see when when these zones start
to get cleared and there's no reaction
from them then it gives me some sort of
confidence that we're continuing down
but you see this
had a reaction to the middle of the zone
that's why i kept
you know trailing it from here to here
to here and you just begin to watch this
and see what happens within this area
you know when we when we tap into
certain zones
usually we want to see some
consolidation going sideways
to kind of give us an idea that
we could potentially push off of this
area but even with this zone look we're
establishing
equal lows
here
which we could potentially come back up
into this and balance then run or come
back up into this s well this imbalance
s and d imbalance s and d
and s and d here so you see
all of this here you know
this is unmitigated this whole area
is is unmitigated within here maybe even
on a higher timeframe you might see that
it's unmitigated from there too
um
but yeah this you know we we just begin
to look at what what happens around this
area
and when we
you know kind of get an idea of what's
happening around here we know that if we
were shorting from up here we could
possibly get out of a short because it
might take us back here
but
what this can honestly do is come back
up to this area and tap a second time
too and have a second rejection from
this area
because we didn't consolidate in this
area we came and tapped into this area
and left immediately
so there could also be
a tap back into the area at a later time
maybe it can like go down to this
imbalance here or somewhere within an
area here head back up within this area
and then
you know push further away um but that's
why we just watch price and we just look
at what price does
and and
we just move off of that we just make
decisions based on that remember um uh
armani i told you about the the stab
that's here
remember i said watch how it happens on
the upside too you see that i tell you
look like head and shoulders patterns
almost you know that the people are
you know hypothesizing but oftentimes
it's just wipe off
just distribution happening oftentimes
so accumulation distribution you can
come down here accumulate again it can
distribute up here it can accumulate
again down here like when you're paying
attention to these things it helps you
to be able to
scalp a little more but for me you know
i pretty much
you know
utilize these things in passing just
like i'm aware of something
but i'm not actually
like using it to trade
you know
i'm i'm just more so using it to
um you know like look this here
this could be the
the ar
ar here selling climax here secondary
test here sign of weakness
then we could have the ut
we could have the utah here
we could have a test of the utad or we
could have a push back up and test the
utad
before continuing down to these areas
that could be a possibility
you know and
that's just understanding
you know wyckoff
now
the way that i trade again i don't use
that you know i use more like a more
powerful
way of trading a more simplistic i i
would say
way of trading
um
so i don't
you know it was it was born out of white
golf
so this is why i continue to say that
like this is why golf i am using white
golf but i'm not using it the way
people use i'm not using the way people
teach it
it's it's like an entirely different way
so look this is the low here
right here
this is the low
and this is the high so we're in between
these two areas
right here
so this is a protected low
this is
a high that they
they just put in
so
with
if you look at this with um there's
there's different types of structure
here
this top here
up here
down here
down
up
and then what do we get a run of it
after we get a run of it what do we get
a tap up into the area
but this tap may not be sufficient it
may come further into this area like
through here
you know so so we get this tap we trade
back down
we didn't run this high i mean this low
sorry or this high
because these
according to like the structure that is
creating
these this is the important low and this
is the important high everything else
is lunch meat
everything else in here between this and
this
all lunch meat
all you got is new people coming into
the market and just jumping in trying to
take trades you know
people that don't know what they're
doing
trading within these areas and not
really understanding
you know what they mean
not really understanding
you know that
these areas are specifically put in
by
the ones who control the market
and if they're ran then it gives you an
indication of
what could potentially happen
after they ran
you know so
yeah
and you want body closures below
because wix can
can fake you out
and you see
you see what i said here
[Music]
i said we can come right back up into
this imbalance
potentially reject the way and continue
down
look at that right back up into the
imbalance
reject it away continue down
it's it's like
it's so repetitive it happens over and
over and over again like you know i i
don't know
i don't know if
i if if i saw something that was short i
would jump on it you know
like i would try to expose myself to it
so
much
that
you know like i
i just want to learn it i just want to
know it
you know and that's what i would
essentially be looking to
to utilize am i trading
you know whether it's using certain
zones for scalping so with
with fractals
sometimes i use fractals for scalping
sometimes fractals can end up being a
more long-term thing so look
this touches the line on a fractal
you get a reaction up 19 pips
reaction just off the touch of it bam
and once that happens
jump out with 19 pips i told you guys
all i need is 24
pips for the week 24.
do you see how easy it is to catch
24 each and every trade
[Music]
each and every trade
this like i don't know like
12 13 14 opportunities per stream what
do we stream for like an hour and a half
two hours
that many opportunities
so i want you guys to understand hold on
let me
because i'm i'm serious
i need you guys to know that i'm serious
i want you guys to understand
that you
now
learning this if anything ever happens
to me
learning this
will radically change your life forever
save these videos download them i don't
know if youtube might remove them later
on fbi can come from you who knows you
know
but save these things
it's free information that's out here
this may be turned into a course later
and you know all these videos may be
gone
save it
because it will enrich your life you
could learn this trading style and open
your own business
meaning passive income whether it's
signal service whether it's mentorship
you know like all these it becomes a
skill that that's in high demand
and
people can learn it from you
so please bunker down on this and it
will change your life
forever
let me get my
ugly face out of the camera
it'll change your life forever man
forever
volume is low yeah yeah volume is
definitely low um
it could be fridays
friday's usually a thing but i mean even
even with low volume like
price still goes i tell people this all
the time price still goes where it's
going you know whether this volume or
not
um the volume just speeds it up you know
to get there
you know so look at look at this um
look at this imbalance here
come on i feel like i feel like a broken
record when
whenever it is that i'm talking
you know because it's just the same
thing that happens over and over again
look at that my weekly salary
in one candle
oh my mic was low damn
oh my god
i did not know that i did not know that
i gotta do that take all over again
this could change your lives guys
can change your lives forever
like forever that's that's what i want
you guys to understand change your lives
forever
look at another imbalance fill and
balance feel here and balance feel here
like
even if it did not come up here
always look for a reaction at the first
imbalance that's something that i
learned from ict
always look for that um when is the
discord going to be up bro
john is really working very very hard on
this there's actually some um components
actually that um
he
he had mentioned um
like there's certain things that you
have to pay for to um
like
you know
certain features to to monitor or keep
track of or use certain bots to verify
because it gets really really spammy in
discords um so he was just going over
like
weighing
that weighing the um
the pros and cons with that and what
those monthly expenses would look like
um because i believe the the features
are like they're monthly so um
if there was a yearly one we could have
just
purchased it right out but um
you know he's he's just trying to figure
out um
what features would better suit
most of the people uh joining and how we
can keep track of certain things collect
certain data spread
um
you know the channels out um we're just
you know working on some creative uh
avenues to be able to um
you know take this into
um so once it gets up and running i'm
you know you guys i'll let you guys know
quickly i think that um i believe that
it's it's monday coming that that he's
gonna have it up and running we're gonna
be working on it over the weekend um but
it should certainly be
uh monday coming because i i really hate
the fact like when i'm sitting here
trading sometimes at night or i'm just
watching the charts i really hate the
fact that i can't share with you guys
you know at least you know you guys who
come and support all the time i really
really do hate the fact that i can't
share with you guys stuff that i'm still
seeing after the fact you know many
times i'm tempted to just like
go back on stream
and
and look at something on stream to to
you know show you guys
you know or or i'm like you know what
let me just
let me just put a quick video up maybe
and they could catch it then but
why not try to create it to where it's
in real time
because that would probably better serve
you guys
you know if i was to create something in
real time that you know i'm sending
stuff along and you guys can just use it
as ideas
you know so that's where the discord
becomes very impactful but um he's
working on it um it should be up and
running by monday um i'm gonna you know
get on it over the weekend with him put
all the the last few things in place and
um you know we we can just we'll just go
from there but um
worst case scenario if if he doesn't
have it up by monday worst case which i
think he will he's you know great at
what he does um worst case scenario i'll
create a um
group on
telegram and i'll just start to send
stuff through there
until the discord is is created because
i i realize like the power of the
discord and also why it's needed watch
this snd up here guys um i realize the
the power of the discord and and why
it's needed and how it could be more
helpful
than
you know just straight listening to
hours of me chat you know so
um i certainly want to um
you know be able to connect with you
guys more and give you guys trades that
you know
you may not i may not be up for to see
it play out but
you know i know it's going there you
know and there's a possibility of it
going there so look we we hit this snd
here got a rejection from it
um there's another one below here
um and there's also one down here
this one
didn't get tapped into yet oh no it did
yeah this did get tapped into
so you see how it puts in the low and
then immediately runs it this this here
this here as well
you see how we put in the low and we run
the high and then we come back and tap
into the area and then go up to the s
and d and then away from the s and d now
we could be running this or we should be
running this because it was already
mitigated you know like this this is
what i'm talking about like you you
could see this all the time
every single day
everywhere
you see this so look this came up
tapped into the s and d
went into the imbalance
came back to the snd that was created
again went up to the smd above left the
s and d came below ran the lows run the
low could come back up into the s d
trade away from the snd come back down
to run the low again or come back into
an snd below only to make its way back
up and possibly take the high and
further mitigate this s d
those are things that price does over
and over and over and over again i get
that it sounds like the explanation
sounded like a lot i understand that but
this happens everywhere on everything
everywhere
so
those things tend to happen and and
that's what i want people to
like really learn and and understand
like the birthplace of these concepts
and and why
you know these things happen and how
you're able to take advantage of it look
at this this is an imbalance i told you
that that sometimes imbalances can be
used as scalps so look we got a
rejection from this
snd zone here this
picked fractal
a rejection from it
then we had an imbalance
that was tapped into here
price taps into the imbalance
pushes up
what does that give us
23 pips
after just tapping the imbalance
you're out
most of the time you get more than 20
pips from from somebody's trading so if
20 pips would would it was the marker
for here pace
you're out as soon as you get in
in and out just like that
over trade close it i'm done
20 pips i'm out
just like that that easy
like you you just gotta pay attention to
these important areas and and i'm i'm
more than sure that
you know
the the fractals you could use the same
way look at this the tap on the fractal
bam right here what do we do push up
come on 20 pips again come on
like really
and and this this could be oh wow look
you you had gotten a rejection from
there back into this area 42 pip
rejection tap into this area go back up
to the s d 49 pips go from the s and d
and tap from the sd and come down to the
the um
first to the fractal
73 pips from from sorry the imbalance
73 pips from the imbalance you tap into
the imbalance come up 25 pips
from the imbalance
pushing up you get a fractal
20 pips from the fractal
like
that is astonishing
i don't know anybody that's trading this
way i don't know anybody that's doing
this that's astonishing
that this is the way that price moves
and and
of people
percent of people
are oblivious to this like
you could go and show them and they will
still choose to hold on to the
indicators they will still choose to
hold on to
to all the different techniques that
that that they've used they will still
hold on to those things
still
so look
this looks like
a head and shoulders
that would have worked out if you use
the neckline break and and you took it
this would have looked like an inverse
head and shoulders
that if you use the neckline break
it would have took you
there but just the simple fact that
these happen sometimes and other times
it doesn't
is an indication that that's not what
you want to rely on
could you imagine if you went to work
hey
cut it out
he hears me get excited and then he
starts yelling
could could you imagine if you went to
work
and
50 percent of the time
they paid you
could you imagine that
coming into the charts
i'm here teaching two hours now
and
some days i get paid some days i don't
what is that
there's no way
i would never go and work for somebody
and get paid half of the time why would
i come into here and do this
why would i do that
there's no way
no
no way possible i i can't
i would never be a part of something
like that
see look at this i said i like to see
the double bottom around our entry i use
double bottoms entirely different than
than other people use it because double
bottoms only have certain purposes
whether it's to go to
a um
an s d
that's above or whether it's to go to um
an imbalance sorter
so there's this s and d right here at
this line of 842 but then there's also
this one above here
at um
a61 but you see how easy it is to
take the first entry
and scalp it up what was that the 20 pip
entry and then came around and gave us a
pattern where we knew that we could
potentially look so it it
it came up popped up it came back down
took out the low but then ran the high
immediately after so we're looking for
it to come back within this particular
area here
it comes back within this area and it
taps and and takes us up it takes us
long to wear snd to snd fractal to snd
fractal to
imbalance and balance to fractal
zones that's it
zones
look at this 60 pips up already from the
second entry the first was 20.
the first was 20.
60 pips up after
like this is i'm trying to teach you
guys like
life-changing information
because i know yo like something could
happen with my health
tomorrow anything i could be taken out
this stuff needs to be here for for
people to
you know learn for people to understand
people to change their circumstances i
believe that there's still great people
in the world
and and i've been shown that you know
from
from like so many people that i've met
over the last year or so
there are still great people in this
world
like i don't care what anybody says i
don't care what has happened i don't
care what anybody has done to you i
don't care what our governments are
doing there are still some great people
in the world and
those great people need to be equipped
to continue
to do great things for others
they need to be able to do that so
so
they could continue to pass on that
humanity not just through
through um
you know like being good and saying good
words but good in actions also
we have such an issue with with
you know homeless kids and
kids
you know in poverty and like america
sends so much money to places and
we have kids in poverty
in new york we have a hundred thousand
homeless kids that attend the public
schools a hundred thousand
yet we have
billions of dollars in new york
our our um uh budgets
overall for the entire city
is and that's just the city not even the
state but the city it's like 80 billion
dollars 90 billion dollars
that's our budget to work with in
certain things
where is most of our money going
to areas that create profit for
for the
government so you're gonna put a lot of
funding into policing you're gonna put a
lot of funding into development you can
put a lot of funding into subsidies so
you can get larger companies to come
into new york and create jobs that
creates tax revenue for them to do crazy
things without taxes in the first place
you know like
all of that happens
and it's wild
and we got
a hundred thousand homeless kids
here going to school and they're
homeless a hundred thousand
remind you i could drive around in new
york i could drive around to each
borough and i can tap each borough and
probably
i don't know get there in like
hour and a half like a circle in new
york
i want to have maybe two hours depending
on if there's traffic and stuff like
that too but i could circle new york
within that time
and how is it that it's a hundred
thousand homeless kids
within that radius
and we do nothing about it
it's despicable
you know so i know there's good people
in the world and and i want let me turn
this back on guys
and i want um
i want people to
you know
be able to
to kind of
do the things that our governments
aren't willing to do do the things that
some of our churches are doing and some
of our churches are not doing
i want to be able to
like create
you know that type of wealth and
compassion and care i know when it comes
to money there's a lot of like
heartlessness going on like
you know wall street would eat me up
if
they knew i was teaching this and it's
such quality and and it's all going out
there for free wall street would tear me
to pieces
so
just with that alone like you know i
want you guys to to understand that
i'm doing this knowing that i'm going
against the grain one
but two
it's because the way i was raised
they they're trying to turn the markets
24 hours they're trying to make it 24
hours seven days a week
that just means that there's more money
for them to take from us if they were to
turn it that way
so why not get ahead of that
you know and and that's kind of where i
am
getting ahead of that
because i'm showing you stuff that's
happening in real time
i told you i said
if we tap into this area
we can
you know get a quick scout but we may be
able to come up and tap into maybe this
s d or this one above
what do we do tap this smd here
i told you sometimes it will just tap
the bottom of it and then reject the way
and oftentimes if it rejects away after
top and the bottom a lot of the times if
you don't get any rejection out of here
then it's going to take the high of this
probably up into the next smd
and then if that does happen guess what
that looks like
tap here
neckline break
right here
short
just like that
that's how they get us each and every
time just like that nothing different
each and every time they get us like
that
it's like oh yeah take it back up there
it can go up there i'm not saying that
it can't but i'm saying that they
understand our psychology like the way
that we think and it looks like that and
then they end up railing against us
you know and that's just this
it's not something that that i want
anybody to experience
it's not something i want to happen to
anyone
you know
so
that's why i'm i'm here and that's why i
do this and and it's
just solely because of that i get that i
go off into tangents and i ran a lot and
all that other stuff you know great you
know
but um it's for the greater good
you know it's it's definitely for the
greater good
um
might be an imbalance fill here or could
leave it behind and just continue up and
then the next thing comes in taps in and
then
takes it up or it just runs too we'll
see what happens there but this
oftentimes what happens it tries to make
its way back to feel the imbalance and
then
and the imbalance is usually
um
like when it quickly fills sometimes
it's with the next candle that's open
the following candle opens you could
potentially
have some move back up and then
attack back into the imbalance and then
price trades away from it you know like
that could happen too
but yeah that like
these are these are things that
that happen within the market and and
i'm trying to
get people to understand that and get
away from these garbage traders like
i know somebody told me not to name drop
traders and stuff like that so i haven't
been doing it to stay out of beef
you know but you know
it's it's it's so sickening to to see
this stuff like i said when i first
started trading this one guy was like oh
i have these
you know we have this free telegram this
free group you know you guys can join
and
you know like just
learn from other traders and just foster
a great environment you know like he was
saying all these different things and um
and i'm like oh great wow that's amazing
you're like let me join the group he
sounds so like
plausible with some of the stuff that he
was saying watch this snd up here guys
because um
with this smd uh
this is the one that actually broke
structure
um here but intermediary structure so
just watch this
um but yeah he was like um
it's like yeah and look this is this is
also what i'm saying too
um
this stab
that i keep telling you guys about i
don't know why i keep calling it stab
but
this right here
that stab
and then
other areas created to take us back up
but a lot of the times
like i mentioned we may just be going to
structural areas yeah we could run the
high too if if they're ready to run the
high i don't control the market the
banks do so whatever it is that they're
ready to do they do but this is what i'm
saying some of these patterns
they work out sometimes
not all the time because look
you would have um
you'd have taken a short from here or
this neckline break look
this here
taking a short to this neckline breaking
you trying to take it down here
stops above here
here's here's where your neckline break
is
stops above here
you're coming down trying to get this
140 pip trade or whatever it is maybe
tack the lows maybe hit the s d whatever
it is didn't come down and do any of
that so now
there's a possibility that if this does
come up
and it comes to
tap this area here
guess what
this guy is out he put his stop right
behind the shoulder
would come up
pierce the shoulder
and then this guy is out and what kind
of stop loss is this like there's no way
you know
sorry about my ranting guys um
do you pay attention to s and d flip
zones
um i i don't
i don't really know what what that is um
maybe if you could like recommend a
youtube video i'd probably just look
over real quick
and um pay attention to that but i
really don't know what um the flip zones
are now i do know candle flipping um
it was this trader uh lens i saw her
doing it official lens she's a retail
trader um on youtube she has the most
heart out of all the retail traders that
are on youtube i will say um
she does she kind of uses the same
technique as um raja banks i think she
was a student of his but um
you know she's doing this thing now
where it's like you know
candle flipping essentially
you know it's
it's it's it's like what fractals do
you know like this
so price opens up here and goes down
but if price begins to flip
back up above this high
what she would do is
she would put a limit here
and get tapped in
with the momentum
of
the the candle flipping bullish
and she would place her stops directly
behind that area
and take it
you know wherever
she believes it's going so sometimes
she'll take it to the next rejection
area something like that or when she
sees um
price flipping back the other way then
she's like iron amount or she has like a
a 30 or 50 pip for whatever on us 30 or
or whatever it is i i actually started
watching her um when i first started you
know you you start watching those people
that you think are good and then you go
back and i'm not saying she's that way
i'm just saying that i started watching
her um at first
when i first started learning the ropes
but she she does um retail teaching i
just don't trade retail so i no longer
you know really patronize her channel
but
um yeah it's
that was candle flipping that she
explained um i don't know if it's if
that's the same thing that that you have
mentioned
um
with the flip of the zones i'm not too
sure but look at this
imbalance
oh right up
like this is
incredible stuff
you know we have this little snd zone
here that we mapped out right here you
see we got the middle of the snd zone
and i said sometimes price doesn't touch
the middle of the s d zone this is why
you consider to have
this here
[Music]
so if it taps the bottom of it
cool that's still an a rejection entry
for you to take it
to another direction
so you get rejected out of here
and this rejection
facilitates this pullback
and this pullback could potentially
find support on this area this imbalance
and then continue or it could continue
to go down
to
within this area that's a possibility
too
but this is why when when you when
you're aware of how
these areas function
you could utilize them as little
scalping techniques just take fractals
and imbalances
play the fractals and the imbalances
on on um
you know on back testing
and see the reactions some will have
reactions some won't
but then it would start to familiarize
you with like
a reaction that's happening in these
areas just with the fractals and the
imbalances alone
and it'll start to give you a level of
comfortability on how to implement that
into your own system if you need to um
demand turn supply
splinters into an
internet show
yeah yeah so that's that's kind of um
you know the the smd
um flip that that
that other trader uh lens was doing so
you're um
you're right uh
that's um
it's it's pretty neat it's a pretty neat
trick for a quick scalp or something
like that but
i mean
i guess for me the risk involved is
is
the reason why i don't like retail
trading there's a lot of risk involved
the stop losses are
to heaven or hell and you know it's just
not something that
that i
would really recommend
um for anybody to pattern trading
you know like i remember when i first
started trading i was trying to use all
of that stuff i'm like okay look this
this is what i used to do
let me show you
uh where is it trend lines
uh these used to be my friend you see
the favorite was there on the trend line
right there
this used to be mia so i would go just
like this
and i would go like this
and i'd be like
you know price is trading in a channel
and if it
pops out of the channel
then
maybe i would like squeeze it here a
little bit against
the um
just to get like a tighter
[Music]
move to it so i would go just like this
price
price breaks out of the channel
you know tap the above channel or or
wedge or whatever pattern you call it
you know price breaks out of it
get it on a retest
and go
and what you do is
on the retest
your entry is here
your stops
is
behind
the the last touch
and you're targeting
i think
i think you're supposed to target like
whatever
length the break was or something like
that like the the measurement of
something that that's i forgot how
exactly they teach it
um but it was like 113 pips
so then you target 113 pips
and it's like
oh yeah you know like it hit
like wow that thing actually works and i
could have took it longer you're like
that's what you're thinking in your head
you know but for me
i'm looking at this and i'm like
there's no way that i'm gonna risk
76 pips
on this one trade like
no way
this is like
30 trades in the asian session you know
or like this absolutely not
you know but at first i'm like oh yeah
so so sometimes when this hit it hits
but when it doesn't
miserable
like absolutely miserable
you know and it was like
30 40
of
of the time it hits
you know not always you don't know how
to really like draw it you don't know
like if an area is too tight or not you
don't know if that was the rejection
from it like so i would also do this
here
take the trend lines here
sorry let me fix this
yeah i would also do that there
and be like oh that's a falling wedge
so if price pops out of the wedge
you getting an entry here
here
you place your stops
behind the wedge
and
you're targeting
like whatever oh the the back of it
that's right
you're targeting
whatever
the size of the
the back of the wedges
that's how much you're targeting going
up
so
that's 125 pips
you'd be targeting
125 pips
like that
and although this can hit yes there's a
possibility that it does
this
and the rules behind this had nothing to
do with structure
so you could find that you end up
getting stopped out most times because
you don't understand what's going on
with structure and you're just drawing
these everywhere
you know and these are the things that
you know like mamba fx and all these
different traders this is the stuff that
they they teach people
you know and
they're teaching people based on these
patterns based on the the patterns that
they know
you know remember i said price can
return back to an area a second time and
possibly get rejected if it gets
rejected then it ends up running the
lows if it pushes
you know above the area then it ends up
um
you know continuing higher to
a possible unmitigated area above
um
but yeah this is the stuff that they
teach
um newer traders and it's like yeah
watch me flip this account from from ten
dollars to to thirty thousand
and they're doing little things like
this and it's like
so where's the structure you know like
where is
where's the zones where's where is the
why
you know behind you taking this trade
where is the why
and look it's oh it hit a it hit a
one to two point nine two point nineteen
and then go yeah if you guys want more
trades like this
follow me on instagram and so and so
join my signal service is the best
signal service in the world is so they
take little 30 trades like this best
signal service in the world we be
calling out bangers
join i'm telling you if if you want
go to my link
join and you could also get a discount
on the prop firm
funding for this don't you want to be
able to
take that hundred dollars that you have
in that small account
and be able to get a hundred thousand
from that
you could shortcut it so everything
becomes into like marketing and and just
like all of these different things that
they have
you know running off of
this one trade that they caught back
testing
and you didn't even forward test it they
caught it back testing
and they'll photoshop numbers to show
the videos and then when you listen to
people who are actually in their groups
it's like nah they barely be calling
profitable trades
you know so it's like little things like
that
and and all of this risk for just one
trade like nah bro not happening with me
because you see how this was
you know this did indeed push back up up
there
this
the zone is here
right here
that's where it's at and this is the
second entry
the first entry is here
and the stop is behind here 15 pips
if you were to take the second entry
the second entry is here
stops behind here 17 pips
why would i have 50 something
pips on a trade like this
because i'm utilizing whatever lines
that it showed me and it did whatever no
this this not how anybody should be
trading that's not the way i trade and
that's that's not the way i expect
anybody to trade because like i said
still absence of structure
absent of structure
you did not give any indication as to
why
price was moving back in that direction
oh i saw all of this sell and sell and
selling followed by this buying buying
buying so there's a lot of buying
pressure and i took my fibs and i went
and and you know just mapped it out and
it
let me let me show you guys
it hit the 61.8
and then we ride from there
saw a little resistance coming out of
here so i got out and took my order out
and
you know let the chat know close the oil
here manually
in a mouth this is what they do all the
time
it's like
what do you guys eat like
you didn't even give reasons for why you
took the tray from from that direction
you didn't like nothing
and then look the potential 125 pips
trade
only went 123 or 120
and then
it's tanking again and then what it
comes back and take you out any stop
loss if if price is actually going here
[Music]
and we're just believing all of that
stuff that they're teaching
and all of it is wrong
we just end up being liquidity
because we're using pieces of these
things and not understanding that
structure and supply and demand is the
only thing that the market moves on
structure and supply and demand the only
thing
fractals are smds from a lower time
frame
you can just see it on this time frame
but it's from a lower time frame look at
look at what frac look at what fractals
are let me show you guys
let me show you guys what oh and this
this is a good um
picture i this is what i used to fall
asleep with in my hand this
this is why golf
buying climax ar
sound of weakness in phase b ut
utah
test of the u-tad and then you get the
the movement down
it's a couple areas that it leaves for
you to join
and then it has the mark down and it
marks down all the way into
accumulation
so you see the preliminary support you
see selling climax ar
secondary test
then we break the ar
then we come down to break
both the secondary tests and the selling
climax then we push back up
as if we're going higher
and then
we come down
we come down and run the low
and after we run the low we come up we
test
the spring
we run all the lows actually not just
this low but this low too well this
already liquidated and then this
liquidated that low remember what i said
to you guys i said that
oftentimes you see it to where the lows
get manipulated before trading higher
or the highs get manipulated before
trading lower
so
white golf won't look like this every
time this is a nice presentation of it
but there's two different schematics it
could look different it could look ugly
it could look sideways
it doesn't always look like a straight
through consolidation like this
so we could look sideways
and then when you look within here you
see what double bottom
tap here we go up
tap here
they say get in at the neckline break of
the double bottom which is right here at
the top of this
takes you in
runs your stop loss behind
the double bottom
takes you back up
okay yeah we're making a um
inverse head and shoulders
you know you you getting on the neckline
break
takes you up some
runs your stop-loss behind either the
shoulder or the head runs it
and then
takes you up oh but i thought it was
going up it hit my stop loss and then
went
oh but i thought it was going up and hit
my stop loss and then went they know
that this is our psychology this is our
behavior
and
the market just plays on that
it's like the little guy with the cup he
play he puts certain things under the
cup and he's like
mixing it around you know and you swore
it was that one you saw it under that
he opens it up
give me a dollar you wrong
that's what they do with the movement of
the market
this is essentially human behavior
because look when we get up here and
we're getting ready to run this high
right here
we get up here what are we doing we're
jumping in to try and get in with the
continuation of it
nope
we push back
random low
ain't that wild
then it looks like oh it's just a larger
double double bottom with a um
uh
with one leg shorter than the next
so let me get in on a neckline break
this breaks this is the neckline break
across here
you get in whoop take you back that way
oh this is the inverse head and shoulder
i mean this is the head and shoulders
forming
let me get in on the neckline break this
takes me in down on the neckline break
right here
takes me into the neckline break
up here
this is what i'm saying you can't trade
these these things without understanding
structure
because you see how it's just made to
fake you out all this is exactly how the
market moves
in in consolidation before a huge
breakout
and this is
what traders are getting involved in
this is what they're using to to trade
with but back to a fractal i was
mentioned i have mentioned that um look
this is a fractal
this right here
this low
this high
and the price trades away from it
so you see that
we take this wick to this wick
place a square over it whatever it is
mind you there's this square down here
from a lower time frame fractal
but when you open up the fractal
on a lower time frame look at what it is
[Music]
you see that
this is what it is
all it is is a zone with
smds in it
which ones are more likely
could be the tap within this area
could be the one up in this area here
this wick this wick we know it's not
this because this is already mitigated
could be this entire candle here
could react anywhere within this area
but that's why we get
[Music]
the
touch
oftentimes of the fractal
and sometimes it's the s and d that's
above here
but there are s ds inside of the
fractals as well
and that's
why i talk about fractals the way i do
because
they are smds on a lower time frame
and it just becomes easier for you to
spot a smaller smd so when you see when
price quickly turns around from a
particular area and you're trying to
figure out wait what the hell why did it
why did it hit that area
look we went below this s and d
to where
down within this one
down within this one right here
what's the next
buy or sell
um it's whichever one you choose
um but you got to learn the concepts
first
whichever buy and sell you want to
choose you can choose on your on your
metatrader on your phone
i'm not going to tell you where to buy
yourself but i'm going to teach you
concepts of
how to get in on one
you know so this validus this area is
still valid because we haven't put in
another low yet this low
so you could have multiple rejections
coming from this area
because we haven't taken out the low
neither have we traded through this area
so this zone still becomes valid
still remains valid
and then just right above this area
right here
[Music]
you have this fractal
this fractal right above
so remember how i mentioned that
sometimes you can go through an area and
wick out of the area and then
trade below it
sometimes it's because there's a small
area just up above it
that
you'd often get that tap into before
leaving
so that's something that you you guys
want to you know pay attention to when
you're trading from a specific area
understand that even if it's pushing
through the area
there could be a tap up above it
tap into that area and then trade back
underneath
the area you were trading from
so that's why i'm not a firm believer in
in placing limits right here
and then
putting your stops behind here
because a lot of the times
you might be right
about where it's going
but
there may just be an area just above
that it
you know up and wicks you out at
you know whenever it gets to here
it can go and tap this area and then
begin to fall
and that can kind of look like the
little stab that happens in that area or
whatever it is like there's there's
different things that it could be
but those are the explanations for why
that happened so again you could have
this order here look limit order
i mean you might be risking 10 pips so
you might be like you know yeah whatever
is 10 pips
you know
but if this happens to go through the
area while you're limiting in
then
you get stopped out
because there just might be an area just
above that price is going to and then it
pushes out of the area so remember the
different types of projections that i
told you about i mentioned it could
reject here
at the touch of the zone
it could reject from the middle of the
zone and if you look this is 23 pips in
profit already and then it could flag
through the top of the zone to tap into
an area above and then close back within
the zone
and that could also be your rejection as
well
a little minor imbalance within here
um that price could react off of here
i can just continue down to this s and d
here
you know this
smd right here
but this is exactly what i'm talking
about when you understand these things
then
it gives you the ability to react with
them
so it's like okay
tapped here long wick rejected away cool
i'm looking to jump in on this and
possibly take it wherever it might be
going
and that could happen just that fast
like that just that fast this is 58 pips
already 60 pips just that fast
it happens like that
yeah and this could potentially come
into this area or run the low
i think it could run the low if it
doesn't get rejected out of this area
look at that
and this is just me
telling telling you guys a trade that
that i'm explaining
you know and even the explanations
you know
hit in real time
so
you know i want you guys to to
understand that and and know that like
this
this can happen let me um check some of
my uh stuff here
uh
[Music]
uh derek i got you here um
okay former military thank you for your
service brother
let me
add you here
yeah thank you for your service i'm i'm
happy that uh
you're in forex um
it's this is gonna take off this is
this is a very very new
thing that i'm teaching um some of the
concepts are
um
still out there but they're not taught
the way that i teach it this is supply
and demand on crack on steroids
um you see i said i could tap into this
because
this whole thing wasn't mitigated look
at how we got the tap and we immediately
jet it back up to this
i told you these are targets to take
profit and entries
so now you understand like
you know look at this tap back into
there let's say you got out of your
short there and got into a long from
there
right here
back up into
this area or running the highs
back up into like the the middle of this
area here
stops behind the zone only a 19 pip stop
because that's what you would have
mentally you tap there
and then look
out of this area showing where to
possibly
hear you know maybe
stops behind there
yo
this is like so crazy and
and you can do this each and every time
look at that
66 pips 63 pips back up
and maybe this is going to the middle of
this area who knows or this can come
further down to this area who knows you
know
but look at that three trades
right in front of you guys
nobody can't talk to me about like the
the lack of um
transparency or or anything like that
like
we we just watched
this happen
we just watched this happen like
literally right in front of us
so if people were to measure
any type of
you know like like
whether it's it's
you know oh you don't know what you're
doing you know you know what you're
talking about you know there's all of
that look this is back up into the area
by the way
back up into the area
and stops will be behind the zone
at these stops 19 pips 14 pips 10 pips
9 pips look at this and this could be
running a high maybe
bam
that's what i'm saying like
i can adjust very
fast
to a market like this
very very very fast if i wanted to just
trade all of this we run the high we
potentially have a rejection from there
back down to maybe here
you know or maybe just to the middle of
this area and then
we go
but these things like
i don't know anybody that
that uh
hey dave can i get a screenshot of the
top down impossible
just real quick okay yeah yeah let me um
go out did i did i do the top down on
here
oh yeah but i didn't mark these areas
so um
our top down was
you know potentially
um reacting from these areas but this
was the first area that we had
right here let me go to the hourly it
might show a little better
yeah this was the daily low that we were
running
so i said after we run the daily low we
usually get a huge pump up
um
and where did it pump back to
you know this area here
and i think i had mentioned that this
area was the area that um it was going
to come to but i think i mentioned that
on nas
um
but yeah
it was this um we have some other areas
down here these are just areas where
price can tap and reverse again these
these are not areas to um
hit to scalp
let me open this up a little more these
are not areas to that it hits and you
could scalp on because these are from
higher time frames so
the wicks
could travel through this it could
travel through this whole thing here tap
into this and push back up
and you just see a wick on a higher time
frame
but you might have
taken the tap of this and ended up in
drawdown all the way to here
you don't want that
so yeah the these were just um uh higher
time frame areas
that we selected and we said that
there's their um possible reversal
points and this is a daily low let me
actually make this
red this is a low
a daily low
so if this low is ran we could expect a
huge pump up after this low is ran
but again this is a low so
it would essentially be a pump up to
retrace and potentially continue back
down below it
so um that's just uh
something that you want to be mindful of
but i'm explaining it that way
then you also have
this high here
watch for the possibility of
the run of this high
but
really and truly the run of this high
would give me some indication that
we could possibly
try to attack
this high up here
right here
yeah
that we could possibly let me move this
here i don't remember why this was oh
this was
um the uh thing
the
the little um
imbalance feel that's what that line was
but yeah if we if we run this high
there's a possibility that we could be
looking to
get up to this one
up here
so these are just targets that are above
um here
here
and this is what i'm usually doing after
stream
um
you know oftentimes uh
place these here
and look at how price reacts to some of
these
so here within these areas here
yes because all of this the reason why i
have this and then this
is because
all of this here these candles here are
mitigated
this one here didn't get a lot of
mitigation to it
um
let me actually see
yeah this one didn't get a lot of
mitigation to it so
if you do get a rejection from here
from this line 144 it is valid
um
it could be momentary as well
but it is still um
valid to potentially have a rejection
there because um this entire thing
wasn't mitigated i said i'd like to see
it mitigated anywhere between like 50 to
so yeah
um if if you want to take a a picture of
this or a screenshot of this you can
um
i just wish that see this is where the
discord becomes important because i
could do the top down send it right into
the discord
and then
later on just work with the rest of the
day and people would just be able to get
it from the discord
yeah let me just see how nas worked out
um
yeah
you see the same way still gave me the
rejection at 12 11.
pulled back into the area
and then
continued up
let me go down to the 15.
oh my gosh i hope this youtube oh no it
didn't
if it goes to the the next uh song
oftentimes it's like a song that's
copyrighted already
um
and then they end up taking on your
stream i know sucks right
so look we had a push above into this
area and a tap
up here
then we got a rejection from this area
back down
so this was essentially facilitating
that push up above the line and then the
rejection off of it
and then we
got
a push back up to it but remember what i
was saying
you see what i was saying we're here
with this with this head and shoulders
pattern
and why it's important not to
you know
try to trade these patterns absent of
structure because if you look right here
the neckline break you're shorting from
the neckline break essentially what
they're telling you and they tell you to
take it down to
you know some zone down within here
let's say you took it down to the zone
until you place your stops directly
behind
the shoulder
look at this
out
47 pips out
because of
using a pattern absent of what structure
is actually doing
so that's why you you don't want to use
that
that's great i'm glad you got the shot
sean
yeah that's why you don't
you don't want to use that and if you
look here
um let me actually go to the us30 chart
if you look here
see look i told you exactly what i said
this is why i said you know like when
you understand order flow like it
changes
everything for you so look we tapped up
into the area a second time
right
here but i mean this is this is like
four or five taps really
one two three four
five
we tapped up into this area a second
time
and i said usually when we run the highs
we usually short
but this is running the highs with wicks
no body closures above
so what do we have that we always talk
about
equal highs
equal highs usually resort and result
resort result in
the run of the low
and we either run
the first low responsible right here
for one of the highs
and possibly the second
responsible for the other high
which we got the run here
but then we also have
equal highs
over here
here here
here would be included these would be
included
so what's happening in this area
we're getting multiple rejections out of
this area
but even though we're getting multiple
rejections out of this area
we still have not ran the low
so that makes this area still a valid
area
because we have not ran the low
this area still becomes valid i said
this when we were right here look how
many tops we got into this
we got one here we got another one here
we got another one here we got another
one here
five
tops and we rejected away from it each
time
because this zone is still valid
as long as price did not trade up above
and close or
give us another low
so this is what i was saying sometimes
people see
they see this consolidation here
but often times you just have it to
where it's jumping from zone to zone to
zone because look this right here
this right here
is
an s d on a higher time frame
this right here
on a higher time frame this is the s d
this is the demand so it's going from
supply to demand to supply to demand to
supply to demand to supply to demand
back and forth between this whole thing
just ricocheting through this whole
thing so this demand stays valid this
supply stays valid and we just bounce
between it until it gives us a direction
and and this happens
quite a lot this happens often
so this is why i come on here to teach
this because
you guys are going to see this whether
you like it or not
now
you guys are going to go on the charts
and you guys are going to see this
happen over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over and i've never never again
to where you can't unsee it it's gonna
happen over and over again
you see how i said sometimes it can push
through
these imbalances
you can push through them
what do we have as as you know areas
above the imbalance where we could
potentially say it could tap
look at here
move this out so you could see
what did we just tap
whether we just tap that to cause this
this rejection
this supply yes
that's valid
if
if someone is thinking the supply
supply is valid
but
more accurately
we tapped the supply and we came in
we had about seven people draw down real
fast and then out of it
[Music]
you know we're here 15 pips
but forget
this
and look at
[Music]
this fractal sorry this fractal tab
look at this
we tap this fractal
and then went down
what did the fractal give us 21 pips and
counting
this could be going for the imbalance
that's in here i'm not too sure
or continue to push further into the
area as well
there is this
area here
but it's still overshadowed by this
whole area here but look look at this
look at this
look at what i'm saying and we're seeing
it happen live we're seeing this happen
live
supply demand supply demand supply
demand supply demand supply
you see the zones are still valid
man
i love charting guys i love it
i love charting
i love it because
it's
it's simple
it's predictable
and for me that's that's how i am i'm
very simple like very very simple
yeah like
it doesn't take a lot for me
and i've found a trading style that
suits my personality
there's this gut this other guy that
that trades on here um
i was gonna go get his video but let me
not
stop being problematic
um
he says that you should look at um
let me actually see if i could find it
um
what was it
ig market
is it
so he he goes here
and
i don't know where exactly
it is
um
it's like somewhere within one of these
things
he goes to this
uh
yeah i don't know where exactly it is
but he goes here and he goes to
here
um
msnbc what is it um
dao
so he goes here
just like this
and he goes
uh
pop-ups he goes just like this and he
goes look at the amount of them they're
red and they're blue
and i mean red and green
and it gives you an idea of what you
should be doing today
whether you should buy or sell
and he goes just like this
he he'll
click on like something like this
and he'll look at the whole number 29
000 and he'll go okay it's
it's plus
you know 5.48
so this is letting us know it's bullish
we should buy
he does that now this has dax on it this
is shanghai this has the japan exchange
this is
um hong kong
some of our exchanges the london
exchange
you know german it has all of that there
but this is useless
for us when it comes to charting
this is useless
because
when we had that
and the market opened initially that
would have been in the green
when the market had that push-up
and people would have saw that and
thought okay our biases to buy
and immediately after the market opened
up
not even half an hour later
sell-off
within less than an hour
and what are people going to say
with this
oh what happened you you said to look at
that and and look at this and then you
know what you'll be doing for the day
but
it failed
what's the explanation behind that do
you know i heard this guy tell
the person
that they were wrong
you were wrong you didn't follow my
system i told you when it hit this and
that and i told you when it does this
you gotta follow my system
that's that's what he literally said to
me
you follow my system
you didn't follow it correctly
what
first of all the system is flawed that
should have never been something that
anyone should should have been agreeing
to to follow
anyone
so now these two zones are invalidated
this one here
i mean maybe further into this could
still be validated like the middle area
of this let me just place this here just
in case it comes down
maybe that
could still be valid but
the touch of it is about imbalance as
well as this zone isn't valid because it
was traded through
and and what does that what does that do
for the
the um
head and shoulders pattern guy
with his stops 126 pips right behind the
shoulder
and he's targeting
these areas these zones down here
he's his stop is 126 pips his target is
92.
and then you
ring it over
and all they're seeing all they're
seeing around their entry is this
they get in oh we were in some profit
now we're in drawdown now in profit now
we're going to draw it out now we're in
profit now we enjoy that now we're
profit that we're enjoying that that
we're profit now we're out
so
this could have took the equal highs
that were created
tapped up into an area
and then come down and run the equilos
that it created also
but this is the creation of liquidity
this back and forth movement
between two zones
back and forth movement
between a higher time frame zone
and a one minute time frame zone
rips up
runs everybody's stops that are back
here
rips up
comes up maybe establishes equal highs
or runs it
and then sometimes has the propensity to
run it and then come down and run all of
this you got trend line liquidity here
you got equal lows here
and then we ran the equal lows here
along with the trend line liquidity here
we ran all of that going up to the very
t of it
and there's a possibility that we could
still take this high
and just start to melt down
run these lows run these lows
back into the area that we may be
actually buying from
we tap into this area
and then to be continue
for sunday into monday
and that could be the trajectory of the
rest of the day
that could be what would happen for the
rest of the day so we just did the top
down right
and the top down we have mentioned
i believe we mentioned that this was an
area i don't want to lie about it
but i do remember that we mentioned that
they could potentially be looking to
take some of these highs
let me go back and check if this is the
area because i don't want to
say that i'm lying yes this was an area
i said if we came up
we could run this first
and after we run this we want to watch
and see what could potentially happen
because we could run this and have a
fall back down but we could also come to
this
here
this area as well
and if we run this high there could
potentially be a rejection here so these
are all targets but these are all areas
to pay attention to because when price
takes them
when it
cuts above that area
then
there's a possibility that
it
falls
activating the buy stop cell stops in
those areas
so this is why when i do the top down i
tell people like hey pay attention to
this stuff like
this stuff is is is wild it's like the
way that it actually happens there's
nothing else that should ever be taught
in finance other than this
in terms of trading
there's nothing else that should be
taught
other than this
so let me remove this so nobody's
mistaken by it
um
this would have been a loss for
the head and shoulders pattern guy
whether he put his stop-loss here or
whether you put his loss behind here
that would have been a major loss for
that guy
but we get into optimal areas what's
this area imbalance from the left side
you guys want to learn about zones and
all that other stuff take them they're
here take them baby
i'll see you when it gets there and i
hope you're faster than me
just like that
craig what's up how's everything man
good seeing you
craig he he's
this guy is his bull running through
through the charts like
like he's he's learning it at just
a different rate than than most people
that
that i've seen and taught
like let me let me show you guys this
um
i told him i was gonna mention it on
stream
um
but let me show you guys
he's he's been doing pretty good
and and this is coming from like no
knowledge of forex at all like
none
to
starting to learn and try to utilize my
techniques that i'm i'm teaching him
you know this is this is um a
demo by the way i know some of y'all be
hating on demo but that's where you
learn that's where i started learning
from demo and then i was able to but
look at this
you see this
this us dollar is that that
so if he had 500 in his account
just learning and yeah some people might
look at this and be like oh it's over
leveraging lot size too high blah blah
blah
sometimes accurate techniques do not
use the same rules for
for um
you know just lot size and things like
that if you can get the perfect touch of
certain areas and you're just scalping
on those areas or scalps turn into long
longer moves you know like look at this
this is this is remarkable like somebody
taking the basic stuff of what i'm
telling them
with no knowledge of charting no
knowledge of none of that
to basic
things that i'm teaching them
i give people a beginner track to go
through
i tell them to
you know learn um the one hour video
with adam kuh it's a good explanation
for the basics or the foundation of
forex
and then i bring them into beginner
charting videos
that smart money source has a playlist
for those beginner videos
and then after that
try to get them into understanding
supply and demand
then get them to understand and wipe off
and then
get them to understand my zones
and
then the the more you're hungry for it
the more you want to learn the faster
you accelerate in learning and look look
at this
this is 500 and he almost 100 his
account
just utilizing what i'm teaching
entirely different from what people
teach you but entirely doable
that's why i said i could take 600 to 20
000 in one week if i wanted to
entirely
doable
entirely doable
this is somebody just just trading just
learning
they continue to apply these same
principles and techniques
and
it will take their trading
to to a different direction
take the trade to a whole different
level
so look you get the rejection from here
you get the rejection at this line
here
we get rejected we come down look at
that
30 pips down off of just
a little tap in a rejection
but we would have got out a little
earlier because what we would have got
out the fractal
yeah there was a fractal directly above
it but it just made that fractal
well look
27 pips one minute
tap into a fractal then you know the tap
into the fractal can also be the
rejection to take you up past the high
where do we go to the next line that we
have established 71 pips from the
fractal to the next line
where do we tap
from the next line here
back into this area
maybe on the fractal maybe possibly
within the imbalance that's here
yeah i think this is imbalance
but usually this little short movement
like up here and then it stops here and
pushes down usually gives me a short
from there
but look at this
i know sorry i was doing the imbalance
here
and here
look at that tapped into the imbalance
tapped into the imbalance pushed you up
to here 28 pips
what did i say about this movement up
and then back down
i said that for some reason
whenever price retraces back up to this
area it rejects out of it whether it's
the top side or the bottom side and a
lot of it has to do with
um
you know like big like he mentioned it
could be
an order block within here ict order
block within here
you know and if there's an ict autoblock
width in here that could be responsible
for this rejection but that's on a lower
time frame
that's not even on this time frame
that's on a lower time frame
but according to candlestick structure
this also makes it
you know possible as well
to be
a rejection because look we get this
high we take this low then we trade back
above this high
and then we run the low so after we run
the low what are we looking for a
retracement within this area and then a
short from it to the next area
and where's where's the next area that
we're shorting to the s d that's down
here
[Music]
and i get this is this is you know
probably coming in fast and coming in
hot for you guys you know who who may be
new or who may not really understand
all of the different concepts together
that i'm teaching in one i i get that it
it could be difficult but you guys are
literally watching me show you price
movement and why everything is happening
the way it's happening
there's a reason for everything the
reason for everywhere that price start
stops on the chart there's a reason for
all of it
everywhere
there's a reason for it
so
i continue to try and teach you guys
this and help you guys understand this
because
this is
the only
way to trade the only way
to trade once you start trading this way
you will never go back to whatever way
you were trading before
once you learn this there's there's like
there's no going back
because all of this looks like lines but
all of them
exactly had a touch and gave you
something
all of them gave a reason for why it was
tapping there why it was rejecting there
all of it
it all like just worked out that way it
told that story to you
you know so
um
i definitely want you guys to
to really like learn this
and really take this in
because it's it is a lot of teaching it
is like
our videos three hour videos this is
three hours now you know i'm thankful
for whoever sat through and listened to
what i had to say but this is three
hours
i don't take this lightly
you know like i do this as long as i do
it because
i know how much it's badly needed within
this industry
and
you know just
what good is it if i enjoy myself in in
greece
[Music]
and
people don't even have peace
i'm not a rapper though you know but
what good is it you know
like look we just placed this line here
we just placed this line here
just placed it
and we're already down
29 pips almost 30 pips
after just the top of that line we like
to see this little candlestick structure
that we talk about with
the um
the wick trades above
that and then comes back into the body
of it we love to see that because that
gives us an indication that we're in a
right trade
even if even if it's for a scalp this
can continue to push up and go
but even if this is for a scalp let me
see where can this go if it does come up
above
it already hit yeah it already came
there if it does come above already tap
i went below tapped right into this area
and then yeah so
i'm
i i'm glad that you guys are staying
yeah exactly all right i'm not a rapper
though
you know i'm happy you guys stayed i'm
i'm very appreciative of it um i hope
you guys were learning things throughout
this um
you know i have this stuff here for you
guys to come back and just listen
through comb through on the weekends i
would spend the weekends just learning
eight ten hours nobody's spending
weekends like that everybody's trying to
go out and have fun enjoy themselves and
we have a recession possibly a global
recession
looming
next year
a possible global recession
and i'm teaching you guys principles to
pull money out of the market now grab it
down run
pull it out of the market and do what
you have to do
to to sustain yourself to sustain your
family
i'm i'm showing you guys these things
live you guys are seeing this happen
over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over
again over and over again
we're watching this
look at this this came all the way down
45 pips
i use a 10 lot size this is a 100 lot on
my broker that 45 pips would have been 4
500.
and if i use the 40 lot size
come on man
let me get out of your ear like that
somebody probably got the headphones in
like ill stop doing that
but
i i showcase this all the time for you
guys
um and
you know i'm here follow me on instagram
follow me on twitter follow me on
uh you can add me on telegram if you
want a little more personal conversation
it's easier to to reply to that
yeah
yeah ikea you my brother you probably
really my cousin you from jamaica it
could be you know
but yeah this this is this is it guys i
want you guys to get out there and make
money like using these principles i want
you guys to
to learn this stuff and
and like yeah like it'll change your
life like forever
these simple things
you see i'm not clicking on into all
these different pages and saying oh you
gotta look at this and then we get the
fundamentals from here and then we take
the numbers from there and then then if
we pass this resort oh there's some
strong resistance here this like people
get all animated to make it seem like
they know what they're talking about
they don't know what the hell are they
talking about
at all
they don't i've seen it
at all they don't know about it yeah i'm
telling you the way we think it got to
be
it got to be familiar bro i got it
but look i said
you know potentially equal highs on a on
a higher time frame
so if we didn't get the rejection here
that brought us down here 80 pips
then we had the opportunity to get the
rejection here
because we saw that one of our lows were
ran according to candlestick structure
and then price traded back up into here
and then took us down here
72 pips let's say we didn't get that we
talked about tapping here
we get down into here
60 pips
cool
why are we stopping there
why are we considering that as a tp
ah you guessed it right you guessed it
right
um
yeah you guessed it right
come on look at this imbalance
imbalance
like this is yo this is sauce
to create a new generation of advanced
traders
to be able to shift and change this
industry give
quality back to this industry
so you get a tap down there
then you got to tap from here
to possibly head back up
where into somebody's smds maybe that
they still have no mitigation and maybe
this one here
i don't know maybe this one i don't know
but i gave you your start
here
and that's why we don't have take
profits really we just look at what
price does in certain areas if you want
to use these zones just take profits
cool
you know you can
but we also know that that
we use these as
zones to trade from we use these as
entries we use these as targets we use
these as you know possible reversal
points not just imbalances smds too we
talk about the different smds the
candles the one with the wicks the
you know the fractals s and d's too all
of that all of that is here i'm giving
you guys everything that i know
everything
that i
know
because i want you guys to be profitable
i want you guys to be profitable
i want you guys to to learn at the same
rate that i'm learning and and i want to
see you guys when i go to you know
jamaica when i go to
to greece when i go to thailand i go to
aruba we can even plan trips there
ourselves you know we all meet up
together
because this is quality information this
isn't stuff that's not true i i expect
to garner an audience or garner like or
foster a group of just like people who
love quality and people who enjoy that
nobody's going to come in here and
really get oh what you taught it caused
me to lose because okay if you lost then
you can still make it back still
opportunity to make it back
if you lost then
you know but i i know that this is is
such quality such quality in terms of
learning look at this imbalance tapped
up 50 pips up just off of the imbalance
where did we tap the middle of the s d
that i said was here we came back down
again come on
crazy
information these last two days
that i've taught i went over three hours
these last two days thursdays and
fridays are always the best
day in the market for me
people talk about oh friday's no volume
get out of here with that yeah there's
no volume but price still is going to do
what it does
so look watch you may have a rejection
from this area here um
could be a
sizable rejection maybe not not too sure
you know like
this is a possibility
um
because this actually was the s d that
shifted price above this but then we
also have this area still here
so with this area still being here this
is the most recent high remember what i
said to you guys i said between the last
low and high
price can do whatever it wants in
between these areas
so
this is the major structural high and
low but you got to know how to trade
intermediary structure you got to know
how to trade minor structure
you know and those things
help you with look at this candlestick
pattern i told you about
sauce man so even if this comes back and
goes down sauce
sauce this is that jerk sauce come on
the jerk sauce
mmm
sauce
yeah traveling that would be dope meet
up with dave the ea teacher
yeah gems exactly all of it
i'm showing it all in real time
because i want people to learn that way
all in real time i'm showing this to
people
because i know that there's a bunch of
garbage information out there and i want
you guys to understand the right way
so this is taken somebody asked me how
does the retail trader win
and i saw on jon stewart he actually has
a set a segment called the problem and
he talks about the finance industry and
how rigged and corrupt it is and he asks
how can retail traders win
the truth is
retail traders can win if they study
technical analysis that's it that's the
only thing i have to offer
maybe maybe money you know like if they
had access to more capital the way some
of these places do
but
technical analysis maybe
that's how retail traders can win
period there's no
other way for retail traders to win than
with technical analysis
no i do not believe in any other way
the guys in gamestop amc great work that
they did exposed in the industry but
that was a losing battle
that was a a
a
you know pump in the market to stick it
to the big guys but it was still a
losing battle they went in knowing they
were going to lose
so yeah they shifted the system did what
the system did to us but there are ways
to read and look at the footprints
that's within that
so i you know with me i teach these
things like these are my last
days to teach like these this is my last
teaching i don't know what the hell
could happen to me anything gonna happen
to me and i say that all the time not
not feeling like oh you know something
happened to me i'm losing my mind i'm
gonna get the last secrets out you guys
must notice if i died
the federal government killed me you
know like i'm not
but but i teach with the quality
you know just so
you guys could take this and make
something of of yourselves and and and
who you teach this to
and who learns from this with you
you know that that's why i
i teach the things that i do that's why
i teach
the way that i do because i want you
guys to
to get that to to understand that and
and to pass it home pay it forward i
used to watch little movies like that
moment a movie pay it forward you guys
haven't watched a great movie
that's
my beliefs you know and i'm sorry that
they may not align with other people um
but that's my beliefs
and it's just
like i worked hard for this you know
like i abnormal amount of hours
paid less
no one paid me
abnormal so this might have been this
little s and d zone down here
right here you see i said most times you
got to pay attention to at least 50 or
more this probably went like 61 or so
yeah
yeah it's about 61 percent or so
but you see what i say paying attention
to these s and d's yeah there's a full
body smd here but the wick sometimes are
the hidden zones
and if you got a tap on the hidden zone
that hit an snd
tapped right here
pushed up look at that gave you 23 pips
just off of that
and if you took the regular snd
just with this alone
[Music]
you got to tap in here and i believe
this had pushed up to here
29 pips
and just off of
the two choices within the same zone
two choices within the same zone
we end up running this high
and running this high made us do what
tap further into this smd up here
maybe it was
this here
if this hits i'm out
i'm out i'm out
i gotta get out of here i gotta
this is why you i said you could
literally trade everything like you
could
you might encourage some losses a little
drawdown whatever it is but this is way
too accurate for you to fail this is
fail proof
this is what this is
the problem is 90 of people won't spend
time going through these three hour
videos to learn this and that's why i
teach the way i do
i want you to get through these three
hour videos
because sometimes all it takes is
patience watching the market
like to watch the market this long we
this was this was three and a half hours
you guys didn't seem to take a break and
walk away watching the market this long
is what taught me this being able to sit
for a video this
long
is what taught me this
so i'm not telling you guys to do things
that i haven't done myself
but this is what taught me this
i was able to sit here for hours and pay
attention to this
pay attention to what's happening for
hours
and if you guys can do that too it will
change your life forever it's the
discipline factor it's the discipline
the money is in the information
but the information can only be
extracted through one access to it and
two
discipline
kamali i love your enthusiasm but you
gotta learn
how to
work this thing you gotta learn how to
learn this
[Music]
look at this it tapped into what this
fractal
pushed up back into this area
might close the imbalance may not but
may continue up to either further
mitigate this area
or to possibly tap into what our special
area remember what we talked about
we talked about this area
where a lot of the times you have a
rejection coming out of this
push-up push down straight away
a lot of times you could have a
rejection within this area
there's still not not enough mitigation
within this but this could be an equal
high
only being created to run the low that's
a possibility
but you wait and you see what happens
within these areas yeah this is an equal
high or this could be an equal high
but why not learn to trade from the
zones first
why not learn to trade from
fractal from an imbalance
from the s and d why not trade from
those those are those are more optimal
than trying to see if this is going to
create an equal high
or if it's going to make an equal low
these things are more optimal zones
and when you factor in imbalance and
when you factor in displacement and when
you factor in y golf and when you factor
in supply and demand areas when you
factor all of this together you get this
you get this
so as i mentioned we could
end up running the high here
but then we could also come back and run
the low
there's a possibility of that too
and on a higher time frame that would
make this consistent with an equal low i
mean an equal high
that ends up
taking us back down then we could find
an equal low somewhere down here and end
up running the high
and that could be
the flow of it
but you just have to know
what
what the order flow is first before
engaging into the market
learn
order flow
first
once you learn order flow it helps you
look at this i have mentioned that this
wasn't mitigated as much
this still could be further mitigated
what did we do we got a tap right on
here
within this area to further mitigate and
what we started pushing down
to where maybe this imbalance who knows
maybe it just rips through that area or
maybe it just pushes back up to the
actual snd that's above we don't know
that but what we do know is
that
price has these rules that it follows
look this is getting rejected from a
mini imbalance that's within here tapped
up got a quick rejection away from it
from
right in between these two candles tiny
imbalance in there tap there quickly
reject it away now you have another
push-up where possibly to this s and d
and mind you we have one hidden right up
above
most people don't don't look at these
one hidden up above will price get
there's a possibility price guess
there's a possibility price doesn't
but
hidden s d zones
why not trade from the zones
why try to chase why try to you know
jump in when it's going to or coming
from when zones are more optimal they
have faster reactions
so if you jump in you can be in drawdown
a little bit you can be you know sitting
around that area because you jumped in
price is waiting
to go wherever it's going
but you jumped in
and you can jump in and you see that you
get some profit or you could jump in and
price can just sit around that area the
entire time
but with these areas price quickly
rejects away from them quickly
there's another i told you guys s and d
zone
oftentimes which you have is a tap at
the bottom of it
mark these things out on your chart when
you see them
look at this tap
from the zone
i told you you get a tap from the
beginning of it you might get a
mitigation in the middle of it
or you might get a push through
depending on the zone above
and if you just utilize these principles
y'all like
your life is changing forever i promise
that
that if you take these and apply them to
your own trading in whatever market you
trade in whatever market it doesn't
matter what what is this uh um
let's see let's find amazon maybe
whatever market you're in whatever
market you're trading in whatever market
you're in tap we go return to the entry
a second time then we leave so we get a
scalp on the first one bam here we come
up we get another entry here we see the
bullish flip it makes the flip takes us
back into this zone with our stops
directly behind here and then what do we
do we end up in a longer trade
because we
got the i told you consolidation is only
telling you a story of what's happening
with price
that have been here exactly immediately
like that this is this is amazon by the
way
this is amazon
amazon
we can do it within here too these
little things here like it doesn't
matter w wherever we are that that's
amazon on the stock exchange for for new
york
and go to amazon on on other other
things
other things
look at this
tap my line
bam
tapped in for short
everything it doesn't this is amazon on
another exchange this ain't even
new york's exchange
anything anywhere no matter what it is
no matter how it moves no matter if it's
manipulated or not
anything
so
i i want you guys to
i want you guys to allow me
to finish drinking my coffee when i come
into the charts okay
i love you
i'm kidding i want you guys to to
like look at this
see how it moves
look at what you can do with price look
at this i mentioned this this morning
that i just randomly saw this if
somebody actually traded oil
and been like where where would you get
in like obviously you know where to get
in you know on the top of the line
but this was the first opportunity to
get in here
with a 26 pip stop
and look at how look at how far down
this bad boy went
look at this
this is outrageous
just on the one minute
with this kind of stop
and if
if you were in earlier
we mentioned the top of
this zone here right behind
this wick here
and you're just taking it to see okay
where it's going i told you once you get
tapped in and price moves away and it
starts to consolidate that none of your
bit this is none of your business down
here
where this is consolidating none of your
business at all
because you already got in on the tap
and if it tapped and took you away and
did not quickly trade back and started
consolidating it could be moving away
from that trade so look at this
if you just held on to this trade this
is a 1 to 24
[Music]
and this one here is a 1 to 83
oh sorry 81 1 to 81.
people think that this stuff is fake
like you you can't really call this this
type of thing no you can
it matters about where you start what
your rules are and and where we're going
now i didn't know price was going all
the way down here but price still didn't
give me any indication within here that
we were flipping bullish maybe right
here i would have thought that we were
flipping bullish but look this i know
there's an imbalance in here that i got
rejected from let me go down and see
let me prove myself wrong real quick
because i am wrong
sometimes right here
you see price almost touches the 50 of
the imbalance but i told you guys before
sometimes it would just
come into the area almost touching and
leave out of it it doesn't always hit
the 50 and go
but
another imbalance play in here
right here
here
to here another imbalanced play here
rejected away price pushers up run these
highs i'm all the way up here if i'm in
why do i care about what's happening
here maybe if it came like halfway to
where i'm at
but then i'm continuing short once i see
that there's a breakdown and it goes
short
so you could manage
while you're in a trade and take it at a
distance you didn't know it was coming
here you didn't like
you have any indication oh i know it's
going to you didn't know it was going
there
i didn't know what was going there
but we found an opportunity and we
watched price we just looked at what
price was doing even if it's your full
tp that went to some of those areas or
is your runners that went to some of
those areas
it doesn't matter what it is
we didn't have any idea of of that
actually happening but
but
but what did we do
look at this come on
[Music]
i'm done i'm not streaming for the next
three weeks i'm done
this video was more than enough
for people to come and sit and learn so
much from watching this
over and over and over again
look at this
imbalance fill
or
tap into the smd
the beginning of it
what do we do go back up where do we go
back up to remember i mentioned a little
lovely spot here that we could
potentially be going to to tap into
lovely spot bam right there
look at this
from s d
to s d
68 pips
you get a tap here
already 25 pips in profit
watch it as an imbalance here so it
could
you know
make a u-turn from there there's also a
fractal here and an s and d within here
so that makes this area a likely area to
kind of have a rejection out of with all
of this stuff going on and it can just
be a quick rejection
a quick scout coming out of this area
here
because of
all of these things going on within it
and the possibility of all of this and
let's say price just continued to go
down
let's say price just just shifted down
and broke the low within here
there's also a possibility that if if
you were buying up into here that price
would shift back up into this area get
you out at break even before going
but this i mean
is is here for you guys you know like
these these last two days is more than
enough for you guys to be able to become
profitable if you study these last two
videos over the last two days
it's more than enough
for you guys
to become profitable
more
than enough
and look at this
s
back to snd
come on like
so we went we went what was this uh uh
68 pips up
just for a turnaround
of
86 pips down
crazy
but
that's all of my time guys if you liked
what you saw so consider subscribing
like the video
you know uh
you know reach out to me on instagram
add me on instagram twitter
um you know let me know you know how i'm
doing let me know if you guys like the
stuff i'm teaching you know thanks joyce
thanks a lot um you know
just like let me know if you want me to
analyze something for you guys um
you know just to be able to teach you
guys in real time even after the charts
um
you know again we talked about the equal
highs running the low yeah we got that
just now you know we got the tap there
left out of there there's a little
imbalance within here so be careful of
that um we just tapped into this small s
and d zone that's down here the hidden
one so we got a little reaction off of
that like this there's always reasons
why price reacts the way it does
you know this can try to continue to
come up and feel the imbalance but if it
leaves it behind i could feel it later
after tapping into an area below you
know like this
just i see this so many times that that
like i said if you woke me up at 9 00 am
no sorry no name if you woke me up at
3 a.m eastern standard time it's like
where is price now or else i'm gonna
shoot you i'll tell you exactly where
price is
because i've spent so much time in the
market to know what
the movements are even through the night
you know so
you're welcome guys um
i look forward to having you guys back
you know on monday
i might consider on sunday start doing
like weekly outlooks from the higher
time frames i don't know i'll see but um
i was
glad to be able to do this with you guys
i'm always happy to to do this with you
guys i'm always grateful that you guys
come and listen to me i told you my own
kids don't listen to me so i'm happy
about that um
and uh
i just want us to to become profitable
together you know
so hopefully when we get this group
started we could definitely um
uh analyze can you analyze btc
oh i i do everything you want me to
analyze a rock i will
i do everything what time frame do you
want me to analyze bitcoin on
because we have we actually went through
an analysis during this video um for a
bitcoin actually
i think um
is this still here let me just double
check and see
yeah we we had this bounce here from
across the way
something about oh the imbalance that
was here so it bounced off of the
imbalance but then we also talked about
the s and d that's down here too
and this s d was responsible for
the structural break above so that's why
we kind of signal that out
um
so that's here
somewhere within here
um
you know we talked about this hitting
the imbalance it already did here oh
what am i doing
hitting the imbalance here
and um after the imbalance we had a huge
push up
into um this area up here i don't
remember if this was a daily or a four
hour
um
smd zone yeah it was a four hour s d
zone right here
you see a perfect tap got a rejection
away
um
so this could be coming down
tap into the area again
to try and make its way back up
um
if it doesn't then it ends up just
falling down to this area you possibly
have another tap within this area but
you do have a you do have quite a bit of
imbalance um within this area here
so um price could try to make a reach
back up into this area
before continuing short
um so i had this marked out a lot a very
very long time ago um this area here
um
look
so i this was a long time ago that i i
drew this like months back you know
but i talked about bitcoin coming down
to 11 000 possibly and
um even possibly a little lower but i
had this area because this area is
responsible for the highs being ran
um there's also this slight area here
too which is in the 13 14 000 range but
um i drew this months ago like a bunch
of months ago i can't even remember when
did i write the date or anything this is
off the monthly chart actually
yeah
yeah so i drew this months ago you see
snd down here
months ago
and i said that um
monthly demand i expect bitcoin to
rebalance in this area for new highs
and um we've
[Music]
we were like
up here maybe
we started going bearish up here
but look
equal highs
ran the first low
we just want to be careful of this area
not to have to possibly run the next low
at
you know pandemic levels 3 000.
so um yeah this this was my analysis on
it you know
and
it's it's been it's been delivering
you know since i've i've
been that way since i i haven't
you know really mentioned anything
different i did think that we were gonna
make it make it up to some of these
areas but um this is where fundamentals
come in you had um
celsius and all these other companies
doing certain things um certain shady
practices that caused the sell-off in
price
bitcoin is still um useful crypto is
useful in general it's just that it
needs some regulation and and
structuring to it and
you know once we get that then
it's it's essentially going to be the
future regardless of what people want to
think now um it may not be bitcoin but
it could definitely be crypto um it
certainly is crypto ethereum has a space
in it uh xrp has a space in corporate
and corporate always drives a lot of
money so you want to you know look out
for that and
you know speak with your financial
advisor about owning some of it and by
the way this is a great segue into this
is not financial advice nothing i teach
on this channel is financial advice it's
just strictly teaching you about
um
the education of market analysis that's
it whatever decisions you make is the
risk that you choose to take
and that's on you but there's no
financial advice here the discord won't
be any financial advice not now not ever
we will never be offering financial
advice to anyone unless we become
financial advisors
uh
the lady name that is on you
100 bill
oh wow i didn't know that i had no idea
that the lady's name that was on the 100
bills on ripple she's on the board of
ripple i didn't know that but ripple
i've been saying that it's the future
like i've been saying that since the
conception of it since it's like at 14
cents or five cents or whatever i've
been screaming about ripple since long
ago
taking pictures yeah
no but for us that's it you know like
that
this is the analysis that i have on on
bitcoin um like i said if we get a
double bottom within this area then we
could potentially push back up to fill
some of the imbalances that's within
this area in a higher time frame um
but i still have it short and and
overall you know i have a short
rebalancing in that area at least so um
yeah that's it for today guys like i
said hit me up on instagram you guys
could add me i'm always willing to talk
sometimes i get back to you sometimes it
takes a little time to kids and stuff
like that sometimes i'm tired i'm
exhausted you're watching tv i have a
life too
you know so
yeah um
just hit me up with any type of analysis
that you need or any conversation any
feedback whatever it is if you guys need
any videos on how to learn a particular
concept or videos that i trust i told
you i trust pips of persia and smart
money source that's it ict is cool too
it's just that he goes on a little rant
kind of like me but he takes a little
longer to get his stuff across meanwhile
i'm just like
you know so
um i would recommend him too but you
know again he
look into his fair value gaps that's
pretty good too listen to his fair value
gaps video that's teaching about
imbalances but different people have
different names for it because they're
marketing themselves obviously but um
yeah um those two guys is who i
recommend
great videos on all of those concepts
that i talk about and
yeah yeah so you guys can reach out to
me if you want you know hit me up don't
forget to subscribe you know turn a
notification bell so if i do come on
stream maybe back testing over the
weekend or whatever it is you guys will
be notified by it um but thank you guys
for your support um i appreciate you
guys staying here for almost four hours
and
i hope that this information will change
your life
so um
i'll see you guys um
on monday
same time
same place
enjoy guys later