you know what got me into trading I
don't think I shared this with you guys
what got me into like not not trading
but
like finding
something else
is that I was always
the Uber Facts guy at work
so I worked in a cubicle
there was
five other women in the cubicle one as
my supervisor and four others as you my
co-workers colleagues uh whatever you
call the people on the same level as you
and um
I would always come in in the morning
and and you know they over there sharing
their disinformation on different facts
and stuff like that and and I would come
in
and I'd be like yeah I'd hear it and I'd
give the actual factual
idea of what was what was going on you
know the stories they were sharing is
like all right listen
part of that is true but the other part
is wildly exaggerated let's this this is
the way it works this is how it happens
and you know what my supervisor looked
at me one day this was two days before I
left she looked at me and she said
she said can you can you tell me what's
going on with uh uh it was just some
random you know event in the news at the
time I think it was that Predator R
Kelly uh we were she was talking about
she wanted to know what went on with
Gayle King and all that so you know I I
um
I uh
just off rip told her the whole story of
it how how it all worked out what the
charges were with you know like all of
what the defenses could be would you
know like all that stuff who's involved
and it just just you know
analyze the whole situation and broke it
down to you know she looked at me and
she said
boy I think you missed your calling
because you ain't supposed to be here
that's what she said she was a
African-American lady boy I think you
missed your calling because you ain't
supposed to be here
and she just laughed at me right back to
work
and I sat there in the seat for the rest
of the day and I'm like
she's right
what am I doing here
if I know that my brain is what and I
always used to say this even before I
even got into trading and my brain was
worth millions of dollars
if I know that my brain is worth
millions of dollars
what am I doing here
settling in this place
and this is why my job history I only
you do about three four years and I'm
out you know it should have been less
than that I'll tell you that much but
I always said that my brain was worth
millions of dollars everywhere I went
people were always like yo you the
smartest dude I know or you know all of
this all of this Jazz maybe they're just
buttering me up because
I did
stuff for everybody you know but
um
you know she said that and I was like
she's absolutely correct
what am I doing here I
I know that my brain is worth more I
kept thinking to myself you know what
I'm gonna walk across the street to the
World Trade Center because I work in
downtown Manhattan I was like maybe I'll
just go to one of these Office Buildings
see who got these high-paying jobs and
tell them Hey listen
I may not know whatever the work entails
now but give me a week
matter of fact give me two weeks
and if I don't learn the job to the T
in two weeks you can fire me that used
to be on my my uh uh cover letter
anytime I sent a cover letter I'll just
talked about being a fast learner
adapting to environments quickly and I
said you can fire me if I don't
learn the job within two weeks
you can fire me that's how confident I
am in my ability to learn it that that's
what that was in my cover letter
um to most of your jobs I applied for
now most of the jobs I applied for of
course is word of mouth so obviously not
really
really good you need a resume or cover
letter for stuff like that well you you
know somebody and you get in like that
you know
a different story you know you skip the
line you know
but
she said that to me and it really made
me think you know not too long after she
lost the worker yeah her best work at
that you know but
but um
yeah I had to take pride in myself and
and my ability what I could do yes
when I live I didn't have no backup
option or anything like that but
for me I knew that
I was wasting away in that position
and it was becoming so irritable
to where even when I went home I wasn't
a pleasant person because I became so
uncomfortable
with the the salary was fine it was uh
uh 70 80 000 a year you know like for
for you know that stage in my life it
was fine
you know but
I was uncomfortable
there was no more room to grow every
single job I've ever gotten I knew my
work the next person's work the
supervisors work and the person above
them
so when my supervisor is coming to me to
look over something
them telling me that that I'm wrong in
something no we're not even gonna waste
time because this is this is what it is
and this is where it's found and if you
go into this book it's going to show it
here and this is how it's dealt with on
the managerial level and because I I'm
reading everything
reading it all I used to just read
policies in past time you know like just
just at lunch everybody
clacking and talking I'm reading the
policies of the workplace I'm reading
you know the the the procedure how the
procedures are carried out for the
different job functions that I had I'm
reading this stuff I'm reading what the
lawyers are supposed to know in order to
protect the business
you're like that that was the work ethic
that I had so um uh whether I was you
know cop without I was um an
investigator uh uh for the city you know
all the different job functions I had I
was reading it you can't pull me over
and tell me what the vehicle traffic law
is and uh you know uh you know skewed
way because I'm gonna tell you exactly
what it is I'm gonna tell you where the
subsection is found I'm gonna tell you
the exceptions to the law I'm gonna tell
you all of that
oh look at that
let me tell you what qualifies as a
misdemeanor what doesn't what's a felony
what doesn't what class it falls under
I'm gonna tell you all that why because
I didn't spend my my Leisure Time
clocking with with soap with a uh uh
co-workers
I was
actually trying to absorb as much
information as I can
so I always insulated myself with every
single problem that I faced
rarely heard a mum out of me like you
know you you
couldn't
you didn't have anything to review or
check over or anything because it was
all done
by the time it got to your desk
but then I realized that
no matter
how you know good of a worker I am I'm
still a worker
and at any point where they start
passing down budget cuts guess who's
first
guess who's first
when they were
um
they were planning on furloughing a
bunch of city workers during the
pandemic
the first portion of the pandemic I I
was outside working
investigation still needed to happen I
I dealt with child deaths
deaths d-e-a-t-h-s
having small kids and going around
to
observe environments of kids who have
died at the hands of their caretakers
so that was another thing that was
making me uncomfortable
having
my kids who I'm taking care of and then
showing up to the loss of other people's
children you know like it's it's not
gonna go too far into that you know
don't want it to be you know
sad moment or anything but that that was
that was the paperwork I was filing
that's the stuff that I was going over
that's the the environment that I was
going in you know I'll tell you one
story the story of this woman that had a
kid she didn't tell anybody where the
kid was she gave birth to the kid at
home
and then went to the hospital to go get
taken care of for recovery and they were
like hey this is consistent with signs
of you just going into labor where's the
kid she wouldn't tell anybody where the
kid was we go to her house
I opened up the the
the the uh little the little cabinets
underneath the sink
and there's a dead newborn on top of
the the uh cleaning supplies and all
that other stuff
newborn died of starvation in there
you went to the hospital to take care of
yourself
and left the kid underneath the
when the stone many other services the
the
you could at least gave the kid up you
know something you know but
that's the type of stuff that I used to
I used to doing on so um
we all see I'm so direct with certain
things play no games or certain things
you know just just
it's because the the work that I've
dealt with
it wasn't time to be theoretical
it was exact it was facts that's it
nothing else
that's it
so um uh
it was it was a lot a lot to deal with
you know so that was part of being
frustration at home and stuff too
um
you know but when she said that to me it
really made me think and it made me
reconsider what what or maybe even think
about what I was worth
you know
where I placed
worth Within Myself and um
uh on the other side of that
you know here's where I am like I said
during the pandemic they were
furloughing people they wouldn't pay
them
um for they still had to work still had
the requirement to work with they'd be
fired but also was not getting paid
so they were getting ready to come down
and and cut a lot of the newer people
who came in I was only about like three
years in but they were getting ready to
cut staff
and
the second portion of that year
I had to think every day about
whether my job was going to be cut or
not
because I was one of the newer
uh
employees there I came in with a newer
class
and our class was looking to get cut
um you know so that that wasn't a great
feeling
2020 was a
year was just just insane that the last
day of the year I got hurt at work
last 2020 that was December 31st 2020.
the last day of the year we we had to
and we lose we lost Betty White you know
all these different people that that got
taken away from us and in those years
you know it was it was just just an
insane thing
um
to to deal with but I said that I'd
never ever
put the Power
of my kids being able to eat in somebody
else's hand
I will never ever do this so when people
ask about psychology for trading here's
the psychology
you have no time to waste
every second that you give
to things that do not enhance or benefit
your life you're taking away
from the time you have
to get this
and you're digging yourself deeper
and deeper
into the hole you currently are in now
but you think nothing of it because it's
not that deep once you become
uncomfortable
to the point where you can't even sleep
at night
imagine having to study under that type
of atmosphere under that type of mental
capacity
so don't wait
don't wait until it gets to that place
because I promise you it'll be ten times
harder to grasp this
I don't know who that's for that's a
wake-up call for somebody I don't know
who that's for that's what shadow
somebody in the chat
needs to hear that
oh somebody in the chat and he said I
ain't a rapper though I ain't a rabbit
of somebody in the chat
needs to hear that
and get yourself together all right
that's my trait of psychology there you
already got the strategy that wins every
day
it's here we show it we you already got
it
all right
amen
um
you see what I'm saying guys how I'm
expecting it to come about these eyes
here
um
if it does
a drop I would expect it to
Rebound in here and then
trade back above here but I'm expecting
these these highs to be taken out
why particularly because we have this
low here
this here
traded down to this low and back up to
the high that brought this here
so this is considered a weak High
this is the high that put in this low
and what we'd end up doing is taking out
the both of them
um
uh
can you rethink your opinion on your
opinion on one-on-one mentorship so what
what I'm considering doing uh for August
at least when I get back
is that um I'm probably gonna do a boot
camp where I teach everything straight
through
you know like from from Zero to Hero
from intro to Market structure
from uh Video One
uh video two
three four five and now six that
happened yesterday
I'm gonna teach you straight through
and um
cream cream made that mix uh Josh cream
that's with a k
um I'm gonna teach all of that straight
through it's gonna go through like a two
or three day span
and um
one of the days is going to be a full
Market Day
a full Market Day
so
um that that market day is it's probably
going to be a New York session more than
likely but um
I'm going to show you
every single entry that you can possibly
take
take whether it's a quick Scout whether
it's something you hold on to or there's
something you add to as well you'll hear
that some of you add to as well multiple
pairs not just uh futures
you know those would be Forex added in
there I don't know if you want a little
bit of crypto whatever it is but all the
different entries that you can take that
meets the criteria of what's in the
playlist
um
you know I'm I'm gonna go through that
so I don't know whether it's going to be
a Friday that I do it or whether it's a
Monday that I do it but um it's going to
be a three day span and the first
portion is going to start with you know
obviously the the Necessities the basic
structure and end with candlestick
structure
then the following day is going to begin
again with candlestick structure but
then incorporate zones and then
um the third day is just gonna be
literally every single entry you can
take with
you know
um with everything that's taught so I'm
going to do that sometime and um uh
uh
what did I say uh uh August due to
sometime in August give me a three-day
boot camp
but outside of that
um
you know I I don't want to get into
one-on-one mentoring because with
one-on-one mentoring people don't have
the same work ethic off-screen that they
say they do on screen
so
to be a mentor to you I need to be
involved in your entire day I need to
know what your routine is I need to know
where your mindset is and you know what
level of understanding you have I talk
about for one-on-one I need to know that
I was trying to Mentor some of my
siblings until I saw that some of their
daily routines were entirely the
opposite of
what it took to become profitable
you know they're they're uh daily
routines had a lot to do with
knowing who was doing what watching
videos on Instagram you know uh uh
watching the latest movie
chatting it up with friends and and you
know sitting around drinking and all
these different things
rather than
wanting to focus in on it exactly what I
was teaching
exactly what I told him to go back and
do I'll tell you to go watch the video
and I'll say something about a video and
see what your response is
tell me where it's at in the video
oh yeah I said this in video three tell
me where it's at
tell me what video this was in
and and I'll start the sentence
and figure out if you if you know
exactly where it's going
yeah you remember that what video was
that
oh oh okay
now you stop giving me the responses
that's just yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah when I hear people doing that I
know that they don't know what the hell
they're talking about
me to death
but if I told you show me it on the
chart you don't know what is that
can't do that that's a waste of time
I'm literally trading the time from from
my family time to to reset my mental
health to give to you
and
you
are taking that time for granted so it's
it's very very difficult for me to
commit to mentoring someone one-on-one
knowing that people are not ready to
give up the lifestyle that that they
currently have
give up the nothingness that they're
they're doing now
the
nothingness that they're doing now their
Pleasures their comforts
you want to be a mechanic why are you
not watching all the all the videos on
Mechanic hacks
well you're not watching all the videos
about about
cars you ain't never worked on yet
or how to solve you know whatever it is
quick tips on on this and that while
you're not watching videos about that
huh
would you want would you want to be
mechanic
you want somebody to trust you trust you
touching that call
you want somebody trust you touching
that car
and
you that's your work ethic oh
okay okay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
that's what I mean yeah yeah yeah right
out the door you ain't never gonna see
me again
whatever it takes
whatever
it
takes
so so I I can't commit to doing that
knowing that people are not ready to do
whatever
it
takes
because I know that I'm willing
to do whatever is necessary to make sure
you get this but there needs to be a
reciprocity there
you understand it needs to be a
you know and that was just an experience
that I had with my siblings
and and I was teaching for a whole year
I was doing 16 18 hours in the Discord
I was teaching all the way into 1am and
would get back up at six and start
streaming
and then back into teaching throughout
the whole day after after the market
closed now I'm checking in with
everybody seeing how they're doing
showing them certain things in Asia
teaching from Sydney Market open all the
way into London
and guess what they were focused on
boy when I get my funding account I'm
gonna go I'm a I'm going after the world
economic forum
thank you
but you complain about the price of eggs
but you're going after work economical
form
so so I had to scale back
scale back yes work ethic is not
something you you could teach people yes
it has to be inside yes innate
Kobe said
if
he did if most of his competitors are
doing two workouts a day but he was able
to do four
and he was able to split it up between
certain times and still be able to get
family time in and all that other stuff
he said before you know it you will be a
light years ahead
you will be light years ahead
of your competitors
light years
ahead of them
just do that for a whole summer even
like years ahead
y'all don't ever see them coming into my
no trade days what is a no trade what
does that
a no trick
wasn't no trade day for me
I'm I must have went blind and something
happened to my fingers that's a no trade
day no no
trade what a
how many hours is in a day
no trade what
you draw down for days draw down for
draw up away
draw Down For What because someone said
Turn Down for What Jordan for what
what is this that you speak of
let me I know I get people offended when
I when I talk about my work ethic and
and what what I see and what I'm willing
to do and
you know the
the capacity that I operated yeah I know
people get offended by that you know so
I I just need people to
um
understand that you can put that time in
and learn that for yourself for free
you need to pay for any Services you
need to pay for any mentorship you need
you need to pay for anything
matters about
you know your willpower
the effort that you put in
you know because whatever it is you're
good at how long did it take you to get
good at it probably wasn't it wasn't 15
minutes
I know it wasn't 15 minutes
so you want to go to if you want to get
good at something that's supposed to
take care of you for the rest of your
life
it's not going to be 15 minutes
I promise you it's not gonna be 15
minutes
you didn't learn that in 15 minutes but
you want to learn this in 15 minutes
you learned that in a five minute video
but you wanna learn this in a five
minute video
man oh man
I don't even think it took you five
minutes to walk
you took your first steps and then what
fail
you took more stuff and fail you took
more steps get and failed over the
course how many how long
oh
but you want to learn
something life-changing in 15 minutes
okay
got you
heard you
so um
now I'm putting some music behind it
because I feel like that needed to be
said to a lot of the crowd this here and
anybody that's going to come back and
listen to this video
I wanted to get that out the way
um somebody asked hi Dave actually they
accidentally two different accounts but
the same question but
hi Dave I have a question regarding
funded accounts so you risk two percent
of the trailing threshold fifty dollars
of drawdown is 2500 I don't know how
much you should risk and I'd never tell
you how much you should risk because
risk in this market is inevitable and
whatever you risk you can lose the
entire thing
and in order to
receive any advice on risk that means
that you need to receive financial
advice correct and on this channel this
channel is only
for educational and entertainment
purposes only
nothing that you hear
on this channel is financial advice
nothing that you hear on this channel
will ever be Financial advice this is
just my personal perspective on the
market that's right every day by the way
and you need to
seek out a financial advisor
if you're looking for financial advice
on what to risk
in these markets
let me see do that miss anything
because you are not going to sue me
he said to do this and then and then I
did it and and then I lost everything
y'all know younger two people for that
right anybody give you a signal
and and they don't go the way it's
supposed to go and you lose money you
can sue them back part y'all know that
you can sue them back for it
shoot them for the money that they they
made you lose
because they gave you that the direction
now when I'm trading my
funders accounts
I am risking
a percentage
of the drawdown that I'm allowed
so if I have a 100K account and I'm
allowed 2500 or maybe it's maybe it's
like four thousands
drawdown
or eight or ten I don't know what a lot
of these other companies have but um if
I'm allowed four percent
and I'm risking
one percent per trade on a 100K account
that means that I'm risking a thousand
dollars per trade
so that means I only have four trades
and I have to be right on at least one
of them and at least make that one
percent or
you know higher
so um
I wouldn't be risking the balance of the
account I would be risking the
drawdown that I'm allowed so if I'm
allowed only 4 000 in drawdown
then I'd be risking a percentage of
whatever I'm allowed and draw down
not
what I'm allowed for the size of the
account
now for me personally
I'm risking a lot more than y'all are
because
in a lot of these areas that I'm trading
from
you see that there's an exact tap and we
shift away you get the tap and we added
it
So within a couple points over then a
couple Pips or or whatever it is
um certainly
you know expecting a quick top in there
and then we out of there
and if I lose on that then then I lose
that and I wait for the next thing so
I certainly
um
have different metrics into what I'm
willing to risk based on what experience
I have
but for for you
um you see a lot of financial advisor
and they'll let you know
um what percentage is okay for you to
risk in the markets but whatever it is
that you do risk make sure your risk is
always behind
a zone that you're trading from that's
what I teach in the playlist it has not
changed it's not ever going to change I
will never ever change what I say
whatever if you watch my playlist if you
join mentorship whatever it is I think
zekeg you you have joined a mentorship
previously
um you've been around for quite some
time as well
the question that you ask is like a
Elementary question um like a first
grade question in terms of
what it is that you're risking I've been
saying that for a almost a year yeah and
some change and I'll never stop saying
that you're risking
whatever whatever it is that you are
risking it's behind the zone that you're
trading from that's it it's nothing else
if price trades below that zone it
invalidated your trade and and you're
out
but whatever it is you're risking so if
the Zone if you're getting it at the 50
of the zone and you're risking the other
50 portion of the Zone guess what
whatever you have in your account
followed by whatever amount of Trades
you want to be able to take to survive
in this game goes behind that account
and nothing else
if it goes below that that uh structure
you're out
your trade is out your trade is gone
whether you lose whether you were right
about the direction but you were wrong
about the entry you're out
I follow the same things too I'll close
the trade as soon as it goes below the
zone and invalidated my trade I got into
a poor entry I need to find a better
entry next time that's the way that I
trade that's the only way that I would
encourage somebody to trade you don't
hold on and hope that it comes back
no
so whatever it is that that you're able
to risk you need to understand that it
needs to be behind the zone
that you are trading from
needs to be behind the zone that you are
trading from
so I'll never tell you you know what
amount you should risk what you know
never confirm or deny anything like that
I'm just saying that that's that's what
I've taught if you ever watch my
playlist if you ever
you know studied under me you know that
I've been preaching that same thing for
God knows how long and I'm gonna
continue to preach that same thing
because that's how you remain profitable
I told you guys yesterday
in order to continue playing at the
arcade in the pizza shop that I was
playing those video games at one I
needed to know how to play the game
I'm gonna be wasting my Quarters on on
you know already fighting fighting with
my sister about stealing it off my dress
up but you know I'm not wasting my
quarters
so I'm gonna know I need to know how to
play the game first
but in the event that I lose I need to
be able to play the game again right
so if you have that
in the Forefront of your mind
then your wrist needs to be calculated
with the amount of times
that you want to be able to play the
game if you want to play the game once
over leverage and blow your account
you want to be able to play the game
multiple times
then
basic elementary math is required that's
it basic elementary elementary
math is required
that's it
I lost a lot of money when I first
started options trading too I lost
eighteen thousand dollars when I first
started options trading I wasn't even
like I didn't know what a chart looked
like I didn't know what candlesticksburg
nothing I was just trading based on the
Greeks and
I lost a lot of money I ain't going back
to suit him I was foolish for even
following that eighteen thousand dollars
later I was foolish
I was foolish this man was foolish for
following that yeah
so I don't blame them that's my tuition
you know shame that's my intuition you
know
it happens to the best of us
you know but uh
make sure that now trail with better
risk better understand it
I know
that um
that has helped me to
live to live again
if it does make it make sense
very foolish
yeah happy to see you streaming again
today hope you're having a good day so
hey Tara what's up yes I'm I'm having a
beautiful day
mentality exactly yes mentality
yes
yeah do that is either you have it or
you don't that's it exactly I can't
teach that that's what I keep telling
people I can't give you psychology maybe
you need to go speak to a therapist or
whatever it is maybe you need to look
within go to that mirror and be like for
me I used to get up and I used to be
like you are somebody I used to look
into the mirror like you you are
somebody you are great
you do have purpose
you are going to be successful you will
make it in life you are not a a
you you are not your past you're not
your past decisions
you made these decisions in error and
out of ignorance and even if it wasn't
ignorance even if you knew the
consequences of it you made these
decisions but you are not your decisions
you you suffer in the consequences of it
now yes
because you reap what you sow exactly
but you are not your decisions
you you are better than what you've done
there's there's this hope
as long as the breath is in your body
this hope
you know that that's what I had to tell
myself
no matter what you did no matter nobody
can't hold your past decisions over your
head the shame and guilt that comes from
it I was married less than less days
than Kim Kardashian
I might have Beats world record if
that's the case
but you are not the the poor decisions
you made that doesn't Define your life
doesn't Define your future you're better
than that you can come out of this
you're gonna rise out of them ashes
that's what I tell myself in the mirror
speak that to myself every single day
just because you're having a bad day
doesn't mean you have a bad life
you you ate today
yeah
you woke up you can't put an alarm clock
in a graveyard and watch them get up
if they do then boy we at the end of the
world we in the last days but you can't
you can't put an alarm clock in the crib
the Breath You Take now somebody's
taking the last one
well you taking this one that you take
it for granted
it's been taking the last one
you still here you will not die before
fulfilling your purpose you're not
allowed to die until you reach your
destination until you reach your purpose
until you reach the place
that God called you to go to
you're not even allowed to die
that's what I tell myself every day in
the mirror just to just to work myself
out up out of that funk just to get
myself out of whatever it is that I was
feeling
and it doesn't mean that that I felt
better that day
or I felt better the next day maybe I
didn't even feel better the next week
but guess what baby
guess what
look away man now
look at how things changed
and every every new level you get to yes
there's a new Devil at that new level
ain't a rapper though there's a new
level
the new Devil at that new level
yes
going to deal with issues at that new
level too
it means throwing a child each time you
you deal with those issues
you understand what I'm saying
I know some of y'all understand I know
some of y'all feel it
maybe they should be the trading
psychology video I don't know maybe I
should put this in the playlist be like
this is the greatest psychology you want
to you asked for it you asked for the
training psychology here we go
you ask for it here it is
maybe maybe that should be it
but there's only thing I have to offer I
don't I can't tell you
you know what cold showers to do for you
I can't tell you to
you know go go to some grass go with
people out there touching grass and
still coming back and losing in the
market that don't help
you know I can just tell you how to stop
yeah what what you should do when it
comes to How You observe the market yeah
I tell you where to place your enemy
because I told you
no Financial advice on this channel but
but let me tell you what worked for me
and maybe some of those things that work
for me could indeed work for you too
that's all I have
when it comes to the psychological
aspect
of
these markets here
you follow your rules you follow
whatever it is that you
you need to do day in and day out to to
maintain profitability whatever rules
you need to to enter into a trade to
exit in a trade I told people
whatever it is that you get paid per
hour
at your old job at the job you had now
at the job you want to you know maybe
another job you want to get to because
people be like I I want to work one day
a week and make five thousand dollars
for one day a week
you you
don't even know how to boil water and
you talking about you want to make five
thousand
nonetheless nonetheless let's let's
bring it back in now let's bring it back
in y'all stop laughing I'm not even
looking at the chat right now because I
don't even want to see what you're
saying that but you know you
whatever did you make an hour
if you made it in a couple of minutes
consider that
where you where you place your stop
you're taking out be grateful that it
was more than what you made in an hour
just within a couple minutes you're
gonna find a couple more entries
you you're gonna be able to to work your
way through it creatively
but the first step when it comes to
Trading
I always tell people it's Capital
preservation
Capital preservation
most of the entries that I give you guys
well I don't give you guys entries most
of the entries that I'm teaching with
they instantly go into profit and allow
you to be able to
to uh manage quickly
within that they allow you to be able to
manage quickly
and
the rest is on you
because you're going to be overtaken by
greed
or you're gonna be overtaken by fear
at both of those things could cause you
to lose
even if you know where the market is
going
so
that's that's my trading psychology for
for me
and if
the shoe fit
Leicester stitch up
you know like the
laces usually stitched together
you shoot fit baby
lace that stitch up
Dave I'm getting better love that crypto
monster I know a couple months back
you've been commenting on these videos
all the time talking about I'm I'm
watching it Dave I'm getting it I'm
learning it
brother kudos to you you keep at it keep
at it you're gonna get it I think
yesterday sticks NYC came on here and
said he'd been watching video one over
and over and over and over and something
happened for him it finally broke it
finally shifted for other people that
are here that are learning the concepts
that I'm teaching what I want you guys
to understand is consider this a bag of
popcorn right
consider this a bag of popcorn
Charles already popped
got a couple other people in here
already popped other people is is they
they getting there
they're getting this heating up
and and they about the sticks he said it
popped ready for him bird it popped
ready for him we all in the same bag
we all apply in the same kind of
pressure
but just because one pop doesn't mean
the the
everything else is just going pop all at
the same time no we you know let the
heat get to you apply the pressure
you know you use the playlist that's a
little butter to accelerate it you know
and and when your time comes
you gonna pop too baby you
when your time comes
you can pop as well
be happy be grateful that somebody else
got it use that as a testament to say
hey if if they got it then I can too
use that as a testament for yourself as
well
but understand that we all in this
together
and we all gone
at the end of the day when we open up
that badge
it's
to be delicious
delicious
so yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you know I I learned only on this
I learned only on this I don't look at
anything else other than this if I say I
want to successfully trade the one
minute I want to learn on the one minute
in order to successfully trade it
all right
I maybe sometimes use the higher time
frame you know when there's no price
action to the left to show me what's
going on but
you know so yeah earlier today
I sent to my group that we were in a
daily Zone
I asked them to refine it
and pro charge was the only one that
that
sent something so I was like you know
what
maybe they're asleep or maybe they don't
want to learn so you know we're just
gonna come out here and Stream So
he came out here and even if you're
wrong it's fine I saw Gianni post
something in the group amazing amazing
you know like even whether it works out
or not post
post because
you are trying to get over
you're trying to get over your need to
be correct
you're trying to get over that you don't
need to be correct for every single
trade that you take but every single
trade that you post there is room there
is opportunity to grow there is
opportunity to learn and I'ma be there
imma be there and I'm taking my little
magnifying glass
you you post something I'm gonna look
I'm gonna look over it
and I'm gonna say
where is this entry from
and I'ma look at you
you're gonna look at me
and I'm gonna look at you
and you're gonna look at me
and I'ma look at you again
look at me again
and we're gonna both
collectively figure out what's going on
here
and where we can improve
people in the group they're short when
we long while you shorten if we long
you're in a group that long while we're
short while you long enough to be short
and and I'm gonna have that exchange
with you
because this is about growth you need to
be able to do this yourself
you need to be able to do this yourself
I can open up the signal group and it
could be a an amazing signal group
and if I die what happens you know what
happens
if something happened to me what
happened well what's gonna happen to you
you need to be able to get this for
yourself you need to be able to see this
for yourself you need to be able to open
up a chart
and immediate immediately
know what's going on look look at look
at how I said 132 look at what's
happening around 132 135 sorry
just
refuse to me you just get on up again
it's confusing there's gonna be days
where you know beyond the Beyond The
Shadow
but the price is going to play with you
is going to play in your face
you can play and play in your face
and you got to be able to to hold fast
today you gotta be able to
hold on to to what you've learned I'm
telling them post your entries in the
Discord
post your entries in the Discord I want
to see you trigger on it I want to see
you press the button oh yeah I'm not
really feeling well today because
yeah I you know I'ma just take the day
off
but everything else you just posting oh
yes don't go there and then go there and
you'll see go there and then and it's
gonna go okay now Trade It
refuse to press a button on it yeah no
I'm I'm not too you know I I don't
really know if yeah
because
yeah I it's it's not really
you know
I'ma just yeah I took a couple setups on
the demo and and then and then you know
I really couldn't really
all right
okay
you walk out of the same zone I'm
knocked out you didn't press the button
on it
you get no credibility for that
I don't none whatsoever
you probably have one of them that's
here today you know that's listening to
to uh
this
listen to what I'm saying
you know
um
they're probably here
he know who I'm talking about
it's no good if you know it and you
can't act on it
I tell you it's extremely embarrassing
to see somebody get into an entry here
and then cut right here don't tell
anybody you're a student of mine and you
train on like this
you get in here you jump out right here
that's not what I teach I I'm telling
you that much does not what I teach you
I don't teach that
that means that you faking like you you
understand what I'm saying and you
mocking out the same stuff you usually
see me mock out but you don't know how
to execute at all you're not a student
of mine you're a copycat
you know student of mine baby you're a
copy again
I watch your plans tonight I'm just
joining disco yeah that's cool that's
cool you know that's cool yeah make sure
you you understand a lot in the playlist
some people you know I have people join
and talk about so what's a fractal
you're not wasting your money in here
you you paying to join this group and
you're gonna ask me something that's in
the free playlist are you crazy
you're gonna waste your money like that
you
you do you understand time do you
understand time
money along with time like do you do you
get that
would you pay for a whole month of
something and then use it
two two days
before the the subscription ends that
that's how you going you waste money
that way no get a whole free playlist
that you could be profitable on just
watching the free
f-r-e-e for free playlist don't ever
have to join a group you can come in
here asking questions that's already
there
why are you wasting your money that way
why would you wait until you've actually
grasped everything and you want to go
deeper into what you already know why
would you waste your money that way it
makes no sense
you you see what my one-on-ones look
like you see where the price is for the
one-on-one you don't ever need that 101
you don't ever need a one-on-one for me
one-on-one for me is with that playlist
you and that playlist that's one-on-one
because any question that you have I
promise you it's answered in that
playlist
and any
question that you have somebody's like
what what's those boxes
you wasted your time partner it's in
that playlist
in that so what so so what is what is a
break of structure to you
is in
that playlist should we should we use a
body or should we use the wick
so so do we do do we wait for it to come
to the 50 of the imbalance
so what what does the confirmation look
like
so you you pay money to join and then
you ask something that you ain't even
have to pay money to
foreign
[Music]
the other thing that I tell people to do
is that
um any entries that you want to take any
entries that you have any issues with
whatever it is make sure you print it
out and take it with you print it out
put it in your wallet put it in your bag
tape it on your walls go to bed at night
always look for a trade before you go to
bed look on the 15 minute time frame
forecast something that's gonna happen
wake up in the morning make sure you see
what happened if you get it wrong you
also learn every day that you get up why
you got that entry wrong the night
before those are different things that
you can do hey Jeremy happy birthday
brother those are different things that
you can do so make sure that you use
utilize all of those those things to be
able to learn what you gotta learn all
right peace out y'all a good job with
y'all later
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you