afternoon good evening good night
how are you guys
um we just make sure everybody's in here
I'm going to leave anybody in the
waiting room
good afternoon here in Cape Town you
know South Africa okay what's up
how you guys doing where you guys from
where you guys from
let other people don't chat
I'm trying to make this short because it
doesn't need to be long
real simple
easy to understand and digest it's just
something we forget to look at
in all of uh you know button pressing
pushing
maybe you want to call it
triggering you know
yeah go ahead Ivan you can record it I'm
going to record it on my end too
um and release it on YouTube
and this is actually going to be the
last video that I
um publicly released
had a um cut this part out but had a
conversation with my family about
time you know sorry
time
I know we all talk about time and price
but
um
in a conversation with the the stream as
well about it
and um I guess I was speaking to myself
in it
uh time time time
something that's not refundable
can't get it back
the time where your health was good
time when you had things
that you were able to do
time that you just had in general time
you know
I think
with a lot of um
people whose
time is sort of
inspiring
because all of our time does expire I
hope you all know that
the consistent thing that you hear them
discuss let me move this uh water marker
then one thing you hear them talk about
is
if I go back and do something
differently I would
if I can go back I would
I would I would I would
okay
and a lot of it has to do with
just the fact that we don't
number our days we always think we got
time
so I'm not a very candid conversation
with my family and uh
I've been trained up some things
we give time to those who value those
that you know those in the group
um but outside of that my
time to have that's free
um
we'll go to fortifying
my family
my future you know
so let's get right into this
um
a few um
you guys know the way that I teach intro
to Market structure by the way this is
just
a quick overview of that
um I'm not going to go too in depth on
you know choosing zones and all that
other stuff I need people to understand
that market structure
is
pivot Points it's swing points it's
you know whether it's higher highs
higher lows lower highs lower lows
however it is you understand it whatever
it is you call it it's just one thing
it's
price at a beginning point
it starts somewhere where does it start
it's one point
one area
there
that's where it begins
here
make that a little bigger there
and
oftentimes this
beginning point
it's usually in a form
of a wick
just like that
and sometimes you might see it
like this
sometimes you might see it like this
something
along the lines of this
with no Wick at the bottom
let me just try to get a darker color
here
sometimes you might see it like this
with no Wick present
down here at the bottom but this on a
higher time frame
is a wick
to move that wind down and immediately
came up
once you get that close above and you
see the two bodies that are present
there
that's a wick on a higher time frame
so
As We Know
or as I've taught
price begins
here
and you have a move that trades up right
you get a low we get a high
we get another low
we get a high
right
we get another low that's
a low a high a lower low a higher high
the reason why this is called a higher
high
is because
it's higher than the previous High
this high is higher than the previous
sign now this all might sound
you know
very Elementary to to those who have
been trading and those who understand
this
but
it's important to have this in in your
mind
because
a lot of the times
we put in this low we put in this High
oftentimes above a previous High
and I'm going to teach about you know
the the previous High what happens at
the previous High we putting this high
above the previous High
and
the minute we go to put in a low and
we're heading for another high
we begin to see people
selling this down
placing their stops behind here
because we're forgetting about what
happened
in the past we're forget about the past
days so
here is how Market structure generally
moves if this high
you have a higher low this higher low
isn't established until we put in
a higher high
until we break above
the previous high and we put in the
higher high
now what what the market often does is
we can
put in a higher low
we go to put in a higher high
putting a higher low
we putting a higher high
and what some might see is
we violate the previous low
right here
we violate the previous validated loan
so when we trade up above the initial
High
this low becomes validated
once we get a body closure above the
previous High
so when we put in a new high
this High becomes validated
when we begin to pull back when we get
when we begin to trade back into
the previous area
now
would we call this
we did not trade into the previous area
what we call this
a
higher high a higher low and then
another
higher high will we call this a higher
high yes
We Will We Will acknowledge this as a
higher high and a higher low
simply because
the market is making
its high it's low it's high it's low
it's high it's low it's climbing as a
stairs a stair pattern would
this is considered a low
and then another high present here
but this is not considered
the structure of the market
so what you have within this area let's
say I'm on the 60 Minute time frame so
it's the uh one hour
Within These
higher highs higher lows higher highs
higher lows higher highs
you should slow here within this pattern
oftentimes what you see let me just
change the color of this
oftentimes what you see on the time
frames that I trade on
is a high
a low
a high
hello
hi
and then you see
on this pullback you see a low violated
and I'm going to show Candlestick
entries to this as well
but you see a little violated
you see us tap back in to the previous
area
and now we we can forming
lower lows and lower highs
we often get to
a particular
area
in the larger or or the higher time
frame
you know order flow the higher time
frame trend
on the lower time frame
you end up seeing us
what we call reverse
we trade up above
the previous High
so when we begin to trade up above the
previous High
we consider that
a break instruction
but what structure is being broken
that's the lower time frame structure
are we still bullish
or sorry bearish as we're drawing back
from the higher time frame are we still
bearish
no now we're bullish but from what time
frame
on the lower time frame you'll see us
going to a cycle of bullishness cycle of
bearishness cycle of bullishness secular
bearishness cycle of bullishness and
here's where people get wrapped up
someone might see
the high get taken
on a lower time frame
and we're expecting
a draw or a pullback into the area
before we continue right
because likewise
the way price Builds on
the higher time frame
like this
it's the same way it builds on Lower
time frame
it's just that these
pullbacks are a lot smaller
versus the higher time frame pullbacks
can go over a series of if this is an
hourly it could be over a series of
sessions
and the following day
you could end up getting your
higher time frame pullback
into the next day
you get your higher time frame
continuation
and the following day
you get a higher time frame pullback
so depending on the time frame that you
want to trade on
if you're trading on the 60 Minute
chart
what you have to remember is
that depending on the type of range
that we're in or the type of
um
sorry let me move this
I'm gonna open this up a little more
depending on the type of range that
we're in
or or the the type of Market cycle we're
in
you may very well see us
trade straight up out of this
clearing these highs
and just continuing to that higher time
frame High
and then you could see
us go straight down after
the same within the same momentum
we come straight down
back to
the previous range that we were
expecting
and what
begin
hi
hello
now let's look at where we are within
the higher time frame trend
this is what
I see a lot of people getting confused
with
let me bring this back this way for a
minute
this is what I see a lot of people
getting confused with
you just bring this higher
take this out of the way
now
when we see this push higher and then
push lower immediately
are we saying that
we're now bearish
are we now looking for the market to go
down because we have this huge Spike up
no
we're not
we have the market shift higher and then
come all the way back lower
and then we begin this uh we can see it
build again
build higher right
a lot of the times when we're on
this lower time frame we forget
to zoom out
so because we watched this huge push
happen
followed by this huge drop
on
the lower time frames as we trade on I
mean most people will follow me I
believe you guys trading a lower time
frames as well
we begin to start anticipating
price trading lower
and in our mind
now that we've seen this whole pattern
take place
we begin to try to
sell everything
so we're selling in here
and we're ending up in drawdown it's
coming back to our entry and taking us
higher we're moving our stops back
and we're seeing
price trade all the way back up into
the new high
that that was created after
we broke structure to the top side
and we're being dragged
sorry we're being dragged
into drawdown
until I stop getting or until we
manually close
because we're not paying attention to
the higher time frame
so
another thing that happens
is when we get to the top of the range
and we go to put in a new high
we see price immediately shift lower
time back in
lower
tap back in
should lower
that back in
and then we're back to
the leg that began taking us up
would we consider
this high this new high put in
we consider that a break of structure
to the top side to continue no
we would not if we Wicked the buff
and we didn't get a strong body closure
above the previous High
it is not considered a breakup structure
is not considered
a new high neither
is this low validated
because as we spoke about early on
the low gets validated
when a new high is put in
and if a new high is not put in
then this low
present
is not validated
so immediately we begin to move this
over soon
immediately
we see press come back down
to the low that brought us up
and we see price run this inside low
right
we see this
go below it
and then
what does the market do
we begin to trade higher
just like that
you begin to trade higher
so if
we're looking at this now let's let's
actually just
move this for a second
as we're heading down
we have this belief that
now we're bearish
and then we begin to see price climbing
back up to the previous High
and we trade through it
where is the validated low in this
scenario
we traded up above this previous High
we violated it but we didn't validate
the law we did violate it
but it's not considered a break of
structure
we ran stops from above
and then we trade it back below
and we ran stops lower
let me just bring this down just a
little more
we ran the stops below
with price moving up
back to this high
why did we stop here
because
our validated low
was actually here
and all we did was come back to
hey I'm not going to zone so I'm just
going to briefly remember this we
briefly mentioned this sorry
all we're doing is coming back to
the demand
that broke structure
or the low
that violated the high
this low is valid
until you hear that until
we get a body closure below it
or
we get a break of structure above it
so what we often see and get wrapped up
in
is
the lows and the highs being
created and broken on a lower time frame
without looking at what our higher time
frame
order flow is what our top what our
higher time frame highs and lows are
telling us
so when you guys see me so zoomed out
um
you know when I'm when I'm trading lead
it's to pay attention to that
what I'm doing here let me just move
this again sorry
what I'm doing here when you guys see
see the chart zoomed out like this what
I'm doing here is I'm noting
the low is down here on the higher time
frame
the high that's present
the low that's present
and
while on the time frame I'm on
I'm seeing
the high get broken
here
and we come back to put in a low
what we're not seeing from
the higher time frame
remember on the lower time frame this
pushed
straight up
and it came straight back down right
but somebody not really seeing from the
higher time frame is the same thing that
I just mentioned
opening up
we have this high that takes this up
and we have this low that brings us down
so what is this considered now with the
higher time frame View
and what we opened up talking about
this on the higher time frame
looks like
one candle a wick
it's just a wick flushing above
but on the lower time frame
it's a full structure break
it's a cool structure break
so
if you guys
watch the Zero to Hero course and the
Zero to Hero video and the intro to
Market structure video
you guys will get a better understanding
of how these lower time frame highs and
lows
are
delivering the higher time frame
highs and lows
but one thing that
we noted earlier this week let me
actually
get rid of this
this is the hourly time frame
if we go down to the one minute
actually let me
if you go down to the one minute
some of this out of here
because I briefly went over this
on one of the streams
earlier this week
we see now that we have a series of
highs and lows right
to use the pies in those
but now we're as zoomed out as
I usually am when I'm
you know when I'm trading you guys might
see little things like this that I know
it out you know just the little things
that I dropped this way or
or I might take something larger like
this and you know I might draw this out
here you know you guys are just seeing
lines but what I'm paying attention to
is
the higher time frame highs and lows if
I go back to the
the one hour
what do we see here oh it's easy
it's easier to follow
the highs and lows from here
based on the one hour
we have this low here
we have this High here
body closure above right
but these candlesticks take a couple of
hours to form so here we have one hour
two hour three hour
four hour
that brings us up above the previous
High takes us four hours
to violate this high
and then what
we immediately go into a range
oftentimes
you know London Asia
gives us these smaller hourly candles
not as much volume in
but if we're paying attention to a
higher time frame
highs and lows
we see that we have a low present here
we have a high above here
we put in a low here right
and then
we put in another high why is this High
put in
why is this low validated
because according to what we just
explained
we have
our low after the break-in structure
full body closure
then we have our high
that broke structure and we have a full
body closure above
so what happens
after this is put in when you guys saw
me bring up this chart you saw
these highs and lows present here
These Eyes on those present here
now again this is over a series of days
here's Friday
here's Sunday
here's Monday
and within the same day you could you
can get a high and low put in depending
on if there's high impact news or
something like that
but here's Monday
we get a pullback into Asia's
the Asian session on Monday
and the next low is put in
on Tuesday
so we're following the higher time frame
highs and lows these are happening
across multiple sessions and potentially
across multiple days as we mentioned
earlier in Nvidia
we violate this low
we get a strong close below
we put in this
low right here
we put in a high
but what did we mention
about our highs and lows
we mentioned that we needed a body
closure
below it
in order to validate
the high
we need a body closure below
so what do we get here
we put in this low
and we don't get a body closure until
here
from the higher time frame we don't get
a body closure until here
so
is this high
validated
no
it's not
this inside high is invalidated so what
high do we need
to rerun
in order to consider it a breakup
structure
and a reversal in price
we need the last
validated High
to be violated
this High did not get violent validated
sorry
because
a closure below was not given just a
wick
so
we end up putting in a load through Asia
I believe this is Asia yeah putting it
low through Asia
but then immediately running and taken
out
hour High
or what would have been on high
should we have a closure below this low
so now if we follow it
this low comes in
and puts in this high above
right here
here was where the low started
we put in a high
we shifted below
we shifted back above the high
and we see that we're in a Range
so now what we're paying attention to is
our load that was left behind on Friday
Friday's low
that we did not break to continue down
and we took out the intermediary inside
High
you guys hear me talk about that in in
Zero to Hero
so when did we get
a breaking close of Friday's low
that's here
Monday morning 9am
so now you take
our Friday loan
and the highest point
of the market before the break this is
considered manipulation we just Wicked
through
been traded back up above so we'll take
the highest point
because that's oftentimes where
the institutional stops are the
protected stops
we call it in intro to Market structure
a protected High and a protected low
so when we came in
to this scene here you guys see me have
this High here
and then you see me at this low
here
right
so if we follow this
we put in this low
we put in this high
this low is validated
because it's after the break instruction
this low is validated the minute we go
up
and trade above to put in a new high
this high is not validated
until we trade below
and put in a new low
so if you see where I put this yellow
line at
you see we have a wick
that trades below it
like this it will wake that trades below
it
and then we get a body closure
shortly after
you just zoom in some
we get a body closure
so after that body closure
you see us
Wick below and then trade back up above
to put in
a high
but the high that we need
to get taken
is the protected High
the protected high is above up here
because this High the protected High the
validated High
is what's created when the body
closes below
the previous low
then put that high in
so we get a body closure below
and then look
we get a wick going down and price shift
back up
what I mentioned earlier
was important
because
this Wick
that came down below is a body closure
on a lower time frame
it's that same
move going down into the move going up
it's the same
bearish Candle Going Down
sorry bearish Candle Going Down
into a bullish candle going up
on a higher time frame
but all this is from the higher time
frame
there's a wick
so
if we had counted
this high above on a higher time on a
lower time frame sorry we cut it this
high above on a lower time frame as a
high
and then we saw this low put in
immediately when we traded up above this
high
on a lower time frame we would
automatically assume that this was
the case to go bullish
if we go back to it
we would assume that this was the case
to go bullish right
you have this
push down below price shifts up above
and now
when we take out
this higher time frame High
this is a higher time frame high but
it's an inside High when we take that
out
it's right here
when we take that out now
we're believing that this is bullish
we're believing that price is coming
back into here
to trade higher
and what do we get price runs below
and continues lower
right
because according to
our higher time frame
the protected high is up here
and anything
between
the low
and the protected High
is a range
that we're in
likewise when I explained the drawing up
above earlier in the video
it showed
a double bottom in it
but
no closure above
so if we pay attention to
the last validated low and validated
High
we know that before we have any belief
that that
price is reversing
we need to take out our higher time
frame validated lows our higher time
frame
validated highs
and that's whether in a downtrend
whether an uptrend
where you take out the higher time frame
lows there's a higher time frame low
take out the higher time frame low
before we believe that
we're now reversing to go into a
downtrend
and if you stay on this side of the
market
you have more opportunities
to hold longer more opportunities to
gain more profit in the direction that
price is actually going versus trying to
time the bottom or time to top
a lot of the traders who you know trade
with me who learn from me desire to hold
longer moves
and those longer moods are only present
from
higher time frame areas
you want to take one trade and hold an
intraday move and you don't want to be a
part of every single turn of the market
that you guys see me you know kind of
noting
this is what you would keep on your
chart
you'd keep
the higher time frame highs the higher
time frame lows and a downtrend as well
as the higher time frame highs and the
higher time frame lows
in an uptrend
because we have the same thing here
well I won't get into that I'll just get
into the
the meat of this portion down here
we have a low present here
we have a high present here this is
following lower time for Mortar flow now
we have a little present here
we have a high present here
we have a low present here
and then we get that run remember with a
run up above
we have a high present here
we put in a series of lows below but we
don't get
a break and structure
until a body closure happens above what
the the validated High
this high is validated
when a pullback it says
and this high is broken when a body
closes
above from the continuation
so what do we end up in here
we end up having this high
with no closure above
multiple times throughout this session
no closure above we traded up above here
at 7am
traded up above again at
10 A.M traded up above at 11AM
and he keeps seeing us go above
you keep seeing us straight above this
high
but we also don't come back to
the validated low
so in order to now
have a bias that
we should be looking to go short
we would need to violate
this low
we trade near it trade back above the
high we trade back down below
and then you see us trade back above the
high and close
that validates this low here
but what happens after that what we just
explained
earlier
we close
validating this low right
and we put in this high
we trade lower
validating this high
and then we trade above the validated
high and break structure
to validate the low
now what do we end up having
a strong close below
validated level
so while
a ton of people would be looking to
you know take Longs all out of here
we need to understand that
what just happened
was that between this low and this high
price just reversed
I just broke structure it says a
downside
now these these areas in here
you know these are called imbalances
these just this large candle
with no wick on either side of the
candle
these are called imbalances that teach
those in the course but again I'm just
going through Market structure
that's it just Market structure alone
the rest of the course will supplement
all the other things that you need to
trade with but Market structure
you need to keep that at the Forefront
of your mind
so
as you see
from the stream that we did last week
we talked about the lows
because
those
highs
lows
highs this is clearly in a downtrend
and it's a downtrend that begun
from Friday May 19th
all the way into the 25th
we were just trending downward
and if you kept these highs and lows
where you need it to you you had a
marker on it
you would understand that the positions
that you were taking up
had they been short positions
they would have yielded you a lot more
profit
to hold than trying to find the bottom
of everything all of these bottoms were
temporary
every single bottom temporary temporary
temporary temporary temporary temporary
temporary temporary
every one of them were temporary
until we took out
a validated High
let me
get rid of some of this sorry until we
took out a validated High
from the higher time frame
let's go back to this hourly
let's follow it
we have this low here
we put in
a high right here
on Candlestick structure if you don't
know what that is you hear that in video
one
and we close below it bam we put in a
low
after this low is put in
we put in a high
and we trade below
and this here
is where you see us validate this high
so we trade up above
when we get the body closure below
we'll get the body closure below
we trade up above and then we violate
bam down there
this becomes validated
so when we come down
we put in the low
and then we trade again
and put in the high
right
when do we validate
this high
we put in this low
body closure below
high is validated
so
we put in this low
and then we trade up above this high
right here
does that high get validated this this
high right here
does this high at the at the green line
does it get validated
well let's see the low that put it in
do we get a body closure below yes
you get a body closure below
at this let me just make it a different
color
yellow line
we get a body closure below
full body closure below
and when we trade up above
you see a wick
Lush up above it
and then
shift lower
so
this high
here
remains validated
and it's not
broken it's not a break of structure
because
there's a wick that comes above it but
we don't get it close
where does the clothes come in
the clothes comes in
on the body of this candle here
so the minute we get a close above
now
our higher time frame order flow
has just given us bullish clothes above
just like over here
down here
we shifted higher
we had a bullish close above the
previous High
and then we violated the low
now we have a bearish close below
and we began a downtrend
so now we have a bullish close above
and what are our expectations now
or a pair like this this is us-30
um when you guys see me try it on stream
is usually not as dead
but these same principles apply to
everything
according to the one hour
now we have
a reason
to now go long
we have a reason to now
be
bullish
so now we begin
looking for some upside
and in the
the videos that
you know I've shared with you guys um
it'll go more into detail with this
but I wanted to you know release this to
you guys talk to you guys about this
because
you know a lot of the times I were
losing in the market or our days where
you know we we have a rough time
it's because the lens in which we're
viewing the market is a bit
off a bit skewed
and it's skewed because
we're not paying attention to
the market structure and and for those
who who still have trouble reading
the the one minute time frame that you
guys see me trade on
it's
because you may not necessarily
understand order flow
order flow
teaches you
you know the one minute time frame order
flow is what I teach more so in the
mentorship
structure
teaches you what side of the market you
want to be on in the sessions we love to
trade the the New York session or or
within news or whatever it is news will
still follow
bearish order flow all of these Wicks
that you see at the top let me just
all of these Wicks that you see at the
top
go back to a bunch of the the news
events go back to the market open
you know uh uh sessions
either Market open times for the New
York session
you'll see that a lot of these wicks
represent either news
or Market open news or Market open news
or Market open
and
these are the areas
that people are getting lost in this
awesome
these up moves and then you see the
market shift down
these are the the sessions
that people are getting tripped up on
even through through London this is 4
a.m here London
3 A.M coming
who Bears 4 AM takes us up and then we
still ship lower
New York session takes us up we still
shift lower
and we're not paying attention to
we're not paying attention to where we
are in structure
what we're doing is paying attention to
that strong move that we get up
strong move that we get up and we
believe we're trading higher and then
the market immediately takes us down
strong move that we get up we we think
we're trading higher the market
immediately takes this down
and it happens almost
every morning with within within these
these sessions strong move up
and then we immediately get taken down
because we're on the wrong side of the
market
we're on the side of the market that's
giving us these
these pushers to the top but we have not
broken any structure to the top side to
even
say that okay yeah we're
we're you know bullish
we should start expecting some upside we
should get into an entry that we can
hold
we're holding these entries
for moves that are not present
so as you guys see I'll you know teach
through the course on the lower time
frame I'll I'll teach on a one minute
you know show you guys things on the one
minute
um but this
Market structure belongs to
the higher time frame
order flow belongs to the lower time
frame
so in the course I'm giving you guys an
introduction into
order flow
but it gets deeper than that and a lot
of people are mixing up Market structure
with
order flow and
though there's order flow present
in Market structure Market structure
comes from the higher time frame
the lower time frame is order flow that
delivers
higher time frame structure to you
or or to where it's going
so when we're in these these intraday
moves these one minute moves or or these
these five minute time frame moves
we have to be cognizant and aware of
what
the higher time frame structure actually
is
because if we're on the lower time frame
and
we see a high get taken like like for
instance here
you have this High ran here you have
this low put in right here
you have this higher end here by this
and then we still trade lower
we still trade back below so everybody's
looking for price to come back into
previous ranges you know discussing
um you know the course
and they're longing everything getting
out getting taken out a break even long
getting taken out of break even longer
than taking taking out a break even
they're getting
trapped under here or their stops are
getting hit under here because they
think that we're ready to reverse from
some area through here
but
Market structure from the higher time
frame
says that we're still short
so as a as a scalper if you want to
scalp intraday
you could use these little one minute
moves but if you want to hold on to
these you know
um
200 Point moves you know 150 Point moves
you need to understand what the market
structure is for the pair that you're
trading the market structure does not
come from the one minute it does not
come from the lower time frame
the microstructure comes from the higher
time frame
so you might see people wait to take two
three setups within a week
those setups are based on higher time
frame Market structure
and they may not necessarily know how to
read lower time from order flow so you
have to
you know be honest with yourself and ask
yourself
do you know how to read Market structure
first
and then
you work on order flow after
if you don't know how to be profitable
in higher time frame structure
that it's not going to be possible to be
profitable with lower time frame order
flow
because the lower time frame order flow
delivers the higher time frame structure
the lower time frame order flow
so if you're not profitable with major
structure then this
range this intermediary structure that
you see
it'll be very difficult being profitable
with it
because you don't have
the higher time frame
in
in the back of your mind
because along the higher time frame
areas
you'll have far more
profitable entries
whether it's here
whether it's taking
you know
rejection out of the
the validated 15-minute low
down to here
whether it's
taking an entry
from the violated 15 minute low here
down to here
was taking an entry on a retest
the area that took structure
down to here
was taking the entry from
the
retest of the retest
down to here
you look at a lot of these moves within
here that are just highlighted and
they don't have
moves coming back to the stop or or you
know to the entry
based on the The Zone you're trading
they don't have moves coming back then
in the video you'll hear me talk about
first half break structure to the
downside second tap gives you a double
top and then short
those have to be in zones where are
those zones coming from higher time
frame
what do those higher time frame zones
where do they have to be
those higher time frame zones have to be
according to what the market structure
is on that higher time frame you're just
not taking any Supply from the higher
time frame and just oh here's the supply
I'm gonna short within this Supply and
then it rips through that Supply
I'm gonna long from this demand and then
it rips through that demand
you need to be sure and I teach this in
the in the playlist as well you need to
be sure
that the demand Zone you're choosing
that the supply that you're choosing
lines up
with
the higher time frame Market structure
so if you're struggling with being able
to trade order flow in the lower time
frame
maybe need to look into following
higher time frame Market structure
before you jump into the lower time
frame
order flow
lower time frame order flow is a lot
different
than a higher time frame Barber
structure
it's a lot different it is the same once
you begin to understand the fractal
nature of price
which I explained in Zero to Hero
would you start to understand it frankly
it
moves through all the different time
frames but the order flow is very
specific
because
let me show you guys this over here
uh yikes
this can happen
you see this shift in Market structure
here
this low taken out
this can happen
on the one minute
and still trade higher
so
you can have your high your low your
high your low you're high
you can get a violation of the low
pop back in and then trade higher
so you were looking for a market
structure shift
on the lower time frame
but if you don't understand order flow
you'll get Market structure shifts
everywhere
on a downside from the top side back
within here somewhere back up here
somewhere
down through here you know through here
so it's not just
Market structure shifts that you're
chasing on the one minute it's it's
you have to understand the order flow
delivery on the one minute and how it
gets to the higher time frame areas
I talk about us getting to a higher time
frame area and then trading away from it
remember we get to a higher time frame
high and then we trade away from it
we don't immediately violate it we trade
away from it go back into the
the low and then you can see us Trade Up
Above
and not even come back to test that
demand like it did here
we get to this higher time frame High
here
it's violet
what happens here
we trade lower
and then we had to violate it
and there are times where we don't even
come back to it
price go open up tomorrow tap back into
here I mean yeah yeah tomorrow
thank God for market open on Sundays tap
back in here
and continue higher
doesn't even come back within
you know your your Zone that you're
looking to come in your your demand that
you're looking for come back and tap it
through your balance that you're looking
for to come back into nothing you might
get into you know it might start just
chewing up these areas up here
rejecting back down pushing up there
running that low there heading back up
above to the high tapping back in here
and the whole time you stop hoping that
it comes back into
your little demands on them down here
and it doesn't
but you didn't know how to get involved
when it doesn't come back
what happens if
you had this low here and price never
came back up here to test the supply
that was left behind
could you get involved with that
could you take a trade based on that
or do you just have to wait
look at where where Bitcoin is at right
now
you just get rid of this yeah look at
what Bitcoins are right now
if price doesn't make it back into this
area
into this Zone
and it continues higher
is there a way for you to get involved
let's say it just it just let me
actually just got another shot
let's say you just
trades higher from here
are you trying to
you know let's say come up here are you
trying to get involved in been a long
hair to go up there
and then why'd you come down and run
your stop
no you you got to find ways to get in
when the market does not pull back
sometimes there's a lot of activities a
lot of involvement
you saw what pushed us up to these areas
the banking crisis
you started launching us out of this
area everybody was like oh there's a
double top on bitcoin we're coming back
down to 10K
if anybody ever shortened this Yeet I'm
pretty ready to try to short this yeet
because what is the what's the
what's the structure obviously you know
nobody nobody would be trading from
you know the weekly or monthly I hope
not
but what's the structure here
was destruction here
structure for the higher time frame is
from the the monthlies bearish yes
but within here
we have these highs and lows
we get a closure above here
and then we violate
so we end up violate and put in this
short we put in this time
we come back down let me just make sure
we validated that
yeah we validated it
we putting this low
we putting this high
we come back down close below it
we validated
a higher time frame High
but since nobody's trading Bitcoin from
the weekly in the monthly and we trade
intraday
or or you know even a little bit of
Swing trading that could end up being
open like a day or two or so
we realized that we get a shift in
structure here
after we get a shift and the the market
structure that we trade with not that we
invest with
the microstructure that we trade with
because when you get into the weekly and
monthly that's where the investing
portion comes in you want to invest from
the weekly in the monthly you want to
trade from
the four hour one hour
I'd say more of the 15 minute in one
hour but you know this you know to your
palette
but we get a shift
in this and now all of the crypto
Traders
oh double top yup we're coming down to
this oh double top again yep we're gonna
make sure we're gonna come down and run
and just get in wrecked each time
oh double bottom yeah we we're
definitely going up to 100 gazillion and
then running their lows
because they have no idea
what
the higher time frame structure is
according to the time frame that they're
trading on the time frame that they're
entering on
you're not entering if you let's say you
were taking a monthly trade so you're
taking a weekly trade
you're not answering a weekly trade from
a one minute time frame
yeah I'm going long here
right now and I'm gonna place my stop
right behind the Zone here on the daily
because I'm gonna get up to the
the 36
000 now and then you stop gets popped
don't worry
Market structures for different modes of
trading for different modes of investing
Market structures for that too
but I I break this up down and of course
you know
just want to help you guys understand
that that if you guys want to be Traders
especially in intraday Traders
you need to know what your higher time
frame is saying
because no one's saying that you can't
short in these areas
but for the most for for most of the
people that trade they want to hold on
to
an entry throughout the session
throughout the
um
whether it's a day or two you know hold
on to a long move holding to you know
100 points or you know your account size
may not be an account size that could
benefit off of 10 points
but I can benefit off of 15 points you
might need
your account size to to you know build
based on holding maybe 100 Point moves
200 Point moves whatever it is
you can get those intraday
would you have to be in the right spot
at the right moment
so when I teach zones inside of the
course you want those zones to correlate
with
what the structure is I also go to
higher time frame structure as well
but
I need people to understand that
direction is very very important even if
you're early sometimes you just early
does you know wrong you're just early
you look over here Dow
right here we had a huge pump
right here how much is this what's this
we had a huge pump
117 points
that might be good for the day
let me see what day this is this is
Thursday
so we had a huge pump
sorry we had a huge pump
but now
when we get back into the zone that we
teach in the course by the way
you want to be on the right side
so London gave us that push that last
push
and then New York
the right side to be on in the market
was
to be on the long side Well everybody's
calling for the market crash oh yeah
it's going down yeah Joey B he
definitely governed like a weak senior
out man you know like all the stuff that
they got to say about him
you know the listen Republicans are
buying these buying these stocks
Democrat Democrats buying these stocks
you know all The Independents buying
these stocks
whether you you know
black white asian
whether you want to be what you want to
be you know
the guy said he identified as a 30 year
old and he was 69 I don't know how that
worked but you know
whatever it is you want to be
whatever these people are that
is
there's nothing to do with
the money being put in here we all in
this same Market just like we all live
in the same world we all live in the
same Market we all have the same
Tendencies we all have the same emotions
we all see the same things we all have
the same impulses
so paying attention to that
oh yeah the the default the debt the
debt seal and default is Lumen
um yeah I I get that you said that
ceiling default is Lumen and
America ain't gonna be able to pay his
bills did you come June 1st but the
market ain't saying that
Market structure is not speaking that
language
so when you pay attention to to Market
structure that
that gives you your Edge
that gives you a place to start in
and what you don't understand it just
know that
you know there's parts of Market
structure that you may not understand if
you look here
let's get some of this other chart look
here
you have this low here
and you have this High here
so this is from
Thursday just before Market open
and this is from Wednesday Asia
yes from Wednesday Wednesday Asian
session
this had tons of volume man this was
beautiful actually
London opened up took us down
New York brought us back up and down
then back up again
there are times where you may not
understand this you may not understand
that we're just in a Range
you may not understand how to read this
so
when you're in here
you might be looking to go long
and then you're taking out a break even
you might be looking to go
short somewhere in here and then you
stop is ran
you may be looking to go long here and
then your stop gets Randy
you might be good looking to go short
here and then you stop your training
and this is just
multiple losses Within
you know one session
we have that in New York where we
we see price take out a high
and then short back below
then
let me see
you've been a little yeah no we didn't
but sometimes the spread takes people
out in this so
they're looking to go up and getting
along price
comes back they're looking for the high
to get taken out they get stopped out at
break even because they're looking for
buy side or they're looking for the sell
side and and we're just in between the
range
and the mentorship I'll go over trading
ranges and stuff like that too you know
but you you guys don't need that you
just you know you become a millionaire
of the playlist that's on YouTube
but you can find your Edge in the market
based on
understanding Market structure
if you use a five minute reviews in the
15 minute
you know because you can't reorder flow
yet order flows you you're only going to
be able to trade on one minute if you
know the order
you need to understand order period
because we break highs we break lows we
break highs we break lows we break highs
we break lows we break highs we break
ones we talk about Market structure
shifting
how we can get a shift in Market
structure and you can still see price
continue back up again
that happened uh
is it Wednesday
no Friday
that happened here
we
we took out this low here
that put in this High here we took out
the low everybody
's coming back in everybody want to jump
short or you know somebody might have
got caught in here
the news but yeah somebody might have
got caught here
and then short shifted to break even and
they're like oh yeah we're coming down
and then price takes them out
and then they changed their bias and
they expecting price to go up and price
go up and then they take the down take
them down there
and then they see this shift right here
you see this
High you see this low you see this high
again
you violate the low you wait for it to
come back up and then it violates the
high
and it's because understanding order
flow
when we get near major High
this is
make sure I quote this correct this is
the hourly High
when you get near it or 15 minute High
even we get near it we trade away from
it
and what we spoke about
how price can take out these lows and
still trade higher earlier in the video
this is how it looks on candlesticks
took out these lows here
everybody's expecting us to come back in
in short and then what do we do belong
Market opens up is Market open yeah
Market opens up and takes us time
even with news it's not good
Market opens up it takes us higher
because order flow is needed to be
successful on the one minute time frame
but then Market structure is needed
first
you know be sure that we're
profitable with Market structure alone
and then move into workflow
and we need to understand that but we're
under one minute if we're scalping
if you didn't find that from a higher
time frame Zone there's no reason why
you're holding to buy side you're
holding to sell side
you holding to to run the hourly High
you holding to run the hourly low
so one minute if you're trading under
one minute
treat those entries as one minute
entries
based on one minute
order flow which can be created and
broken created and broken created and
broken created and broken that's all in
the playlist I'm not going to
regurgitate I'm not going to be
redundant
but it's important to
you know
expect that
it's important to to
trade based on that y'all got some of
these ftml accounts they got you know
all these different platforms they're
using
and
y'all are hitting y'all living so
holding entries holding a one minute
entry that goes all the way up
and it comes all the way back down to
you you break even
so not only did you miss out on all of
that profit now you put yourself in all
of that drawdown even though you lost
nothing
because the the trailing drawing
and you'll see that that'll make you
a lot more efficient as a Trader
trading within the respective Market
structure
along with the other stuff that I teach
in the playlist is very very important
because the stuff that I teach in the
player supplies on all time frames not
just not just the one minute
it applies on all time frames but this
is just something that I want you guys
to understand that the the higher time
frame
Market structure
is King
queen or whatever you want to call it
it's what you should stick within
and then adopt rules to it
you're expecting to hold the zones
you're choosing are not from the one
minute the zones you are choosing are
from the higher time frame and if you're
taking a higher time frame Zone you're
taking a higher time frame Zone
right
that's within that higher time frame
Market structure
within the higher time frame Market
structure
the one minute time frame respects
higher time frame Market structure
the higher time frame Market structure
disrespects the one minute
Market structure whatever you want to
call it
you'll probably respect you stop
make sure your entries you're holding
this from the higher time frame
so
I feel like that was a good um
you know uh
reminder at least
good reminder for a lot of people to um
you know just I I teach in the course
top-down analysis there's a video four I
think it is
I teach Market structure from a higher
time frame to lower time frame lower
time frame higher time from teach that
in the course as well
but these are just some things that I
want you guys to
you know keep with you as as a as a key
to
or a key Point Within
trading intraday
what is the market structure
for
the higher time frame before I enter
into any trades I don't need to enter
into
lungs because the
the market structures loan I can enter
shorts as well
but it'll help me to understand how long
I'm holding my shorts for would help me
to understand how long I'm holding my
Longs forward
when you feel a lot more comfortable in
your trades
the same thing I did with the woman the
the the one hour you could do it with a
15 minute too
it'd probably be better to do it with a
one hour but you could do it with a 15
minute as well
you use the market structure from the 15
minute but just understand that higher
time frame Market structure
is okay now this is a very basic video a
very you know
beginner you know foundational video
and there are a lot more details to
cover about how
order flow
um
you know can even be followed
the basics of that I teach and the free
playlist
and the rest of that that's in my
mentorship so if you are new here if you
don't know me if I you know I don't know
you
you want to make sure you know that
you don't need
you don't need to join my mentorship
you don't
to become a millionaire become wealthy
although you don't need to join
mentorship
but you would do yourself a disservice
joining my mentorship if you have not
digested my free course
and by the time you get to my free
course you may not even need my
mentorship be like man I could make so
much money I ain't even gotta listen to
this guy
I don't know what are you talking about
I ain't gotta listen
just make money take care of my family
do the things I know you do
listen don't worry about the World
Health the the world economic Forum
don't worry about them they don't care
about you they just keep out their own
idea thing that should be your goal
imma take down the government no that
don't even
these governments and the corruption has
existed
long before your great great great great
great great great great great great
great great great great
you understand what I'm saying your
great-grandparents
they existed long before that
and there's nothing you can do
so
money business that takes care of you
money business that pays you and leave
it there
everybody talking about Target we need
to go there and no
just shop at another location this this
wedge means these Publix there's you
know all them different
Budweiser how did it no no it is just
just buy a different bed maybe you
shouldn't be drinking bad you see that
belly you should be keep on drinking
that
they say if you can't see your feet
after 30 you know that's
likelihood of a heart attack it's about
50 percent higher if you can't see your
feet you can't see your feet you should
be worried about the bed we're about to
beat you kissing you know
so I'm gonna cut this part out to
um when I'm posted but
but um I uh this will be only for the
mentorship no no I'm I'm gonna put this
on YouTube and put this on YouTube