so there's this imbalance in here that
this is where price tapped there's a
tiny imbalance within this area here may
we can just plop that
line
there right there maybe
yeah yeah there so this came down tapped
into this imbalance
here telling you guys I'm going to and
balance you guys to death oh my
gosh but it just makes sense because it
it it works so well I mean look at this
the tap of this imbalance if we weren't
fooling around with the chart we would
have probably saw this but top of this
imbalance to possibly this one up here
um maybe even a little higher to this
this is the last High uh if price gets
there sometimes it doesn't um so let's
see we ran through
here oh it tapped into this area so yeah
it could reject from here um and push
further down
possibly then it'll look like this
little
um this
uh Head and Shoulders
maybe maybe you have a test back into
the area and then continue to fall out
of the area to maybe whatever snd is
responsible or imbalance so it could be
like here it could be here you can get a
little bounce up here to take you back
up to maybe this area here um when price
runs this low here you could have a pull
back up into that area and
continue might find some support on the
fractal continue up another fractal
continue up imbalance continue up snd
Blast Off could be like something like
that but we'll
see oh
I so the people was on my zoom last
night they kind of understand where I
placed this and why I'm doing this and
why I'm expecting the rejection out of
this you
know and it could very well come to this
this area here still mitigate this
still but this is
um this is the hidden snd um that I talk
about usually it's a a long Wick that
runs a low and then pushes up and takes
out the high so usually price sometimes
will return back to this area before
trading higher because this area had the
overall responsibility of pushing price
up
yeah oh you just asked that yeah how do
you spot hit in snds so yeah that that's
it that that um the the wick comes
down and then instantly goes up to break
a
high so then um this is manipulation we
ran this low here or this looks like a
equal let me see ohlc uh
252 and this is
uh 253 so look we we just ran that low
just ran it by a
pip and pushed up and we ran the high
above
to so we could very well be coming back
down to this area here to trade higher I
think this was the tap here though so if
you get a run of this High you might get
a pull back into this area and then a
continuation
above
or maybe even down to this Wick
here oh yeah like
beep so if it get stuck at this snd then
obviously you know it's the
um well if it get stuck up here it'll be
like the equal High looking to
potentially run the
low
I really wish I could listen to um
Regular Music on here in my playlist I
have such a fire playlist I know you
guys probably don't listen to um EDM or
or um you know house um but that's
that's like the new wave of of music now
um and uh like you see everybody's
making it Beyonce just came out with a
song that was house music uh maybe this
tapped into this imbalance here this
little sneaky guy let me see hold on
real quick
guys oh no you didn't haha lucky um but
yeah um you know uh um you see Beyonce
just created a house album I mean a
house song um or you know EDM like song
um and uh you know that's where most of
the people are shifting to because again
if America's going into a recession that
means that there's not going to be um
you know any
profitability with the people who are
within this country so now they have to
Branch out what's the music in the
genres that people listen to abroad who
may not be affected by America's
recession mainly house in
EDM so even with them they're shifting
and turning the Landscapes of of just
like what they're traditional music is
to shift with the times not just the
times but where the money is so they're
essentially following the money maybe I
could open this chart a little more for
you guys a little wider for you guys to
see I realize that it's really wide on
my screen and sometimes it looks very
small on the stream um so just you know
let me know about that if if that does
happen
[Music]
um Rev taken off again what what exactly
is
Rev Revlon oh the the Hair Company blow
dryer
company taking oh brother we look barish
I don't know
what we okay we tapped into an
area I don't really like this
area um we did get a double bottom on it
it but I don't know if that's
because okay better um
but now we had this bounce here we
tapped up
into we tapped up
into the um imbalance Above So this
might be a rejection that runs the
low uh so you might want to be careful
with that um that uh uh r
is serum we have CCO and Kina not
touched by the
West um we mean not touched by the West
the the
uh those um little small lands off the
coast um would you wait for it to break
structure then get in or would you wait
for it to break structure below um
so
with go back to this so see it's still
at the rejection point we just ran the
low of it so we could have a tuck back
into this area we could have like 15 20
more minutes um of consolidation
sideways um before potentially
shorting
but yeah this
essentially so look we just ran this low
right
here this smaller low just got hit sorry
bro I'm talking about the music what's a
bit late oh okay
okay I'm like yeah uh I don't I'm I
can't recall what that was for but yeah
okay the music so yeah this looks like
it's going bearish um we ran this low
here here um after the top of this area
so now
we let me move this uh now we look
to so now we could potentially come up
to this area and tap this snd and we
already tapped this one tap this one
rejected down here we could potentially
tap this one and then continue down um
or we can just continue down from here
but this was the imbalance touch this
tap right
here remember the imbalance to the left
I said that it wasn't tapped into as of
yet from here this was the touch so now
you want to watch and see what it does
here because if we end up flipping back
up to the upside we want to make sure
that you know we're not going to take
any of the
highs but this was just a tap on the I
should I I should should have actually
put this price balloon here
um whatever uh so yeah look at this here
we just want to make sure it doesn't
flip above here um because then it'll
look like it's the double top coming out
of the area to trade
higher but look at that that imbalance
tap that's 23 Pips up in one
candle just off of the of
it and know we short
and I don't have Rona by the way
so it's just a cough that was dust in my
throat I don't have
it let me
stop uh so we have this imbalance
here is it just targets if we're
shorting you potentially shorting to
some of these areas where you could
expect a bounce up but again when we
come below certain lows we often get a
cross of the low and then potentially a
pushup so we want to watch
that oh but this was
the the low that I was
saying
look at that little Candlestick
formation that I talked to you guys
about this
here and the thing is with this often
times when you have price trade out
sometimes price just comes to test this
area and then it'll continue
short also if you guys have any other
tickers you want me to um to look at um
I'll definitely look at it let me
actually go back to this rev thing cuz I
realize that this guy is saying that
it's going to
$10 um and I just want to see how far
away or our unlikely $10
is
um so we put in the
high we have a low
so price is in this
range right
here oh this was a gap right
here this area down here is a gap up so
price is within this range within this
range we
have this hidden snd that's
here we have this hidden snd
above we go to the 4
Hour so we put in this low we failed to
run this high or establish a new high so
we're running the low which we just ran
inside of there um if you guys look here
so we expect price to come back into the
range of this it Taps into the range and
yeah BR I think this is bearish I I
don't I don't see anything working in in
the favor of of bullishness let
mean yeah I think this is
uh
I think this is a gap
fill filled the Gap we tapped on
something in here I think we said it was
an imbalance
maybe but the imbalance could just be oh
yeah cuz it hit this imbalance
too so yeah unless we're coming back to
this area a second time maybe $9 I would
say maybe but I mean it does
I could be wrong you know it just
doesn't give me
any um indication
that that we're going
up um not only that let me see what area
we hit
here oh actually I should have did that
on on this time frame I'm
tripping yeah yeah man this um this hit
a
um daily imbalance and rejected from it
um left imbalance to the bottom side as
well as this area that when it flipped
up above so you you could have it come
back to
here you could have it come back to
there um
potentially I mean that's that
that's I don't know maybe I would put
that bad boy or something may maybe this
is news like maybe something happened
somebody's buying them out or something
I don't know um but it looks
the move looks late if you're looking to
buy it looks like it's coming down
so yeah that's um that's that's what I
have there my man so hopefully that
helps um good morning yo yo W
brother what's up it's my Jamaican
brother over there khif how's everything
so look you see we tapped well I don't
know what we tapped here so let me not
even make up anything we tap something
in here from the lower time frame more
than likely um but we mentioned that we
could possibly come back up to this area
here um I should have actually put this
here so we have two unmitigated
areas um up
there and then we also have this area
here with this
imbalance but if it goes above this then
we would be coming up to
[Music]
here so I realized that there's not much
um latency
anymore um in terms of how long it takes
between when I say something and when
you guys hear it it's not as much um I
don't know what that particular change
was for um
but yeah that that was pretty
awesome let see I
have this here but we already tapped
into that so now if we do come back up
here we could potentially be looking at
either this or
this if we come up above here we could
be looking at a rejection within this
region to come back
down but then this is also that
vshape pattern that I tell you tell you
guys
about as well as this is still around
the imbalance this had one touch of the
imbalance this had the second touch and
then look oh I didn't even spot this
this is that little pattern that I tell
you guys to look out for you going try
to train your eyes to look out for like
that because it's
essentially you know then when you come
down here
um you go back
up tap into the area and then
leave so this little pattern
here is what I try to get you guys
to like understand and
learn
because if you could learn that look at
you see this looks like an inverse Head
and Shoulders but if you look it has
rules this High here is slightly above
this high so we put in this low we put
in this High we put in another low and
then we ran the last high so we tuck
back into the range of the area and then
we leave and that's exactly what just
happened right here and it happened on
the imbalance
so that's Prime for you to you know th
this could potentially even take this
High um when this happens on the
imbalance um but we do you see how we
came up to this area here I had
mentioned
um we could potentially run up to this
uh and it looks like we might be taking
the high now areas that we have so we
have mentioned last night that that we
were coming back down to this area here
um and this morning when I woke up
um I actually saw it tap right into this
area give us the Candlestick pattern we
like to see and like I said price oft
times come back come back to test that
pattern the the bullish
flip you know price comes back to test
it cuz you see it left this whole area
here after it pushed away there should
have been like a little double bottom
somewhere within here and then leave but
it's mitigating itself as it's leaving
if it's not going to come
back but because you had this double
bottom and then this push right away we
had the area tap back into it and this
is why I say I I taught this secret to
some of these guys um yesterday but to
you guys even as well you know like I
told you guys take a double bottom a
double top don't don't care about the
Wicks that are there because the Wicks
are just manipulation place a square
around it and watch price come back to
the center of the area and leave look at
this this is another another double top
up
here but this is actually where the
double top is look at how price comes
back to the center of it and
leaves oh but this is a double bottom
here look at how price trades above it
comes back to the center of it didn't
leave so that's that's sauce that I was
showing some of these guys yesterday but
you know like we do this you know all
the time we talk about this we we try to
like just hypothesize different things
that price does and and and how we could
kind of get better at you know trading
and um you know we come up with some
pretty neat stuff you know we got some
other guys who have some amazing
techniques as well um some guys who stay
up late night owls you know um but look
you you get this is what I'm I'm talking
about with this let me let me just uh
show you guys this I get real excited
when I see this look at how within your
area of Entry you get the Candlestick
pattern of this but if you zoom out look
at how within this
area the structural pattern follows it
let me move this here
too and
this if you guys look the structural
pattern
follows it as
well so it's not just the Candlestick
pattern in there the structural pattern
follows it and when the structural
pattern follows it then overall you may
see like higher higher highs put in
because the structural pattern is
stronger than the the
Candlestick uh pattern so the
Candlestick pattern is what I use when
I'm at my areas where I want to
enter so I'd be using this because we
hit this snd back here this area here I
had circled this area for them last
night and I said this area is
responsible for the break of structure
above so when price comes back into it
it could tap into this area and leave
higher that's why I had this put out
here so price gets to the area and now
you get your double bottom within the
area but you also get the Candlestick
pattern that we like to see so then
price pushes is up and you get the
Candlestick pattern to the top side as
well but what happens price comes back
to this
area within this area that it left
behind and what do we get the same
Candlestick pattern
again knowing that if we did take this
long we came back into the area we can
take this long again out of the
area but we got our confirmations within
there and it was just finding those
patterns within the areas of our
entries and that's you know just the
Simplicity of of what we were learning
um on
Zoom um and you know I look forward to
to doing that a lot more
um you know throughout the days
throughout the nights whenever it is um
genuinely um had a lot of
fun
uh hello Dave how are you I heard you
you on a live Zoom call how can we be
part of this um do you do this on a
regular basis so I I do Zoom calls every
now and again you as sparingly it's not
a real schedule for it last night I
actually um I had a friend who I wanted
to show some stuff with
um uh uh trading and um you know I asked
them if it was okay if other people um
came in too so I could just teach
everybody in one session and he said it
was cool so I had sent it out to the
group um this is the the telegram group
um I sent it to that remember we have
these levels up here guys we just want
to make sure that they're not tapping
into um so we do have this level from
across the way we still have price
lingering in this area um you could have
these little pushes up but often times
um that doesn't signify that it's
breaking out to go higher into like the
um there's just things that need to
happen um before then so I had mentioned
that we were breaking to um the upside
uh here we could possibly run the high
because of what happened within our
imbalance here so if you look
here and this is why I want you guys to
be able to spot the imbalances yourself
because you can see when price gets into
an area of an imbalance right
here tiny one right inside of here what
happens in our area of
imbalance that Candlestick pattern that
we like to see so we get the Candlestick
pattern and then we get the test of it
and then we go you see what I said this
pattern is important and why I'm
drilling it in you guys heads so you
understand this we tapped into this
imbalance we got the Candlestick pattern
that we were looking for Price traded up
and came back and tested tested the
pattern and then left that's the same
thing that happened here we got not only
did we get the Candlestick pattern but
we also got the structural pattern
too so when the Candlestick pattern was
formed here price came back to test it
let me um just clean some of this up
because it looks ugly price came back to
test the Candlestick pattern that we had
and then we left so we have this
structural pattern created and and we
push above and then we create the
Candlestick pattern again where could
price go and
retest if price usually has a retest on
the pattern where can price possibly go
to
retest what area did you see the pattern
happen in and not give a retest to it
that area becomes the unmitigated area
this portion here so Within this portion
here you might want to look
at you know um uh if there's any
imbalances within here or anything and
maybe gauge that as where price could
potentially come back into tap and maybe
trade further if it wants to trade
further but when it gets there you want
to see the same pattern set up
here and that's if it crosses this and
this because this could come back to the
imbalance a second time and then leave
and trade higher
too but if it comes back to the
imbalance the second time it has to give
us the Candlestick pattern here and then
it trades
higher so we're always paying attention
to that and that's not necessarily just
a Candlestick pattern that you see it's
more so uh you know there's rules to it
you have the low put in you have the
high put in you put in another low then
you run the high then you come back to
test it and you
go so there's there's rules behind it
too it's not just oh when you see this
trade it looking like a Star Wars
fighter jet or something you know which
it it does look like a pretty cool you
know fighter
[Music]
jet you know but you're you're not just
trading it because you see that like
there's rules within this as to why we
get involved in in a market like
this um slim what's up man
slim good see you man how are you
brother uh could you record Zoom calls
and upload them to YouTube in the future
I was actually thinking about that um I
was I was really thinking about if I
should record the zoom and then put it
on YouTube but the truth is with the
sorry that that was pretty pretty loud
my bad with with the the truth is the
zoom um there's like some Secret Sauce
in there like I don't know what what it
was last night I don't know if I was
just tired and I just ended up in like a
very creative mood and we just started
like explaining everything you know
throughout I have no idea what it was um
so we tapped into this snd by the way
this snd was responsible for this
structural break to the top side um in
the intermediary structure so that's why
we tapped here and we had a push up um
but we still want to monitor here we
didn't run any lows here so this could
still continue to try to trade higher um
unless we violate one of the lows which
there is a a trend line you know forming
here
um sorry I don't know why this thing
doesn't click sometimes look at me
talking about I don't know why it
doesn't click sometimes it's me
obviously I'm not clicking
it I'm blaming it on in
technology I'm on my Boomer
Behavior but um yeah no I uh I was
actually going to send it um a little
earlier but um you know I sent it pretty
late uh but the zooms there's so much
sauce in there like these guys on the
zoom last night I'm sure they'll never
ever need me for trading again if
something ever happen to me they'll
never a day in their life need any other
teaching and Direction other than what I
taught them last night so there's
there's like some Secret Sauce in there
that that like people who I see that are
very engaged and really really have like
that strong desire to learn those are
the people who I want to share this with
like I I don't want to share this with
people who who um you know will just not
not do white not do right by you know
like the stuff that I taught them
yesterday in the zoom they'll be
millionaires
by probably sometime next year you know
like or even the end of the year if if
they continue to like you know um use it
in their trading they'll be millionaires
another
time that's how great the info was but I
just want to make sure that that people
really want it you know like I I wasted
my time a lot when I first became
profitable I wasted so much time trying
to get people who did not learn or or
know about Forex to understand it and I
spent countless of hours I missed
birthdays I missed um you know just
opportunities to do things and it was
because I was showing people things and
they weren't applying themselves or or
they would just they wouldn't study in
their own time they would just wait
until they had access to me then they're
trying to learn and they're trying to
make money but it's like you got to
study this too you know because then you
put most of the work on me you know one
thing I love love love is is that um you
know some of the people in the group
they're seeing the same things that I'm
seeing and that encourages me to let me
know that you know like there's some
growth there you know so um I was a
little discouraged early on where I I I
had did one Zoom call some months back
and never did another another one again
because I was just a little discouraged
that people weren't applying themselves
people weren't hungry for it I mean this
is the right
information not something that like oh
study and learn you might be able to get
it no this is once you're exposed to it
it's instantly going to click for you
and your mind is going to be blown
forever that's the type of information
that I was teaching on the zoom last
night and for the people that was up and
they got it cool for the people that
couldn't I understand you know it was
late at night too but we're going to
have future zooms as well that we
continue to you know like work within
that that's same stuff that we were
teaching so I don't mind raching it
again but you know we'll definitely have
those um in the
future uh let's see I am late for the
top no no no you're you're not late for
the top down um it was just like a suo
top down little little fake top down not
really much because um we pushed up
heavy into these areas um
like very very heavy into these areas um
we were uh gapping at some point up like
look at look at these gaps within here
look at this Gap here we were down here
price closed
at
3180 price opened up at
3198 that's within a
flash that it did that
on this 10:00 candle and this is because
um consumer sentiment news happened
within a flash it pushed up like that
you know so um with these gaps we could
also return back to them I didn't notice
that this Gap was here until I just saw
um I saw it in between the indicator if
you look within here this is a lighter
shade of green than this is so it kind
of exposes the gaps a little um since
they're not necessarily the the same
green
you see
that but there's gaps everywhere you
know within this that's why price often
comes back down to these areas to test
them and then leave um and this is a
pretty cool indicator as well guys I
keep vouching for this I keep telling
you guys this is the imbalance indicator
there's somebody named travel and
something that created this you know he
was pretty spoton with it um kudos to
that guy Travelin Trader or something
like that
um I don't know if he's an actual Trader
or or anything like that but um travel
and Trader he created this pretty neat
indicator if you can't spot imbalances
by yourself you can utilize this but
understand that this doesn't account for
all the imbalances because look we have
a huge imbalance below right
here and price the the indicator did not
even pick it up and that's a huge
imbalance in here so you know this would
train your eye to see him imbalances but
again any and all indicators are lagging
it's always in past time that it's
letting you know whatever it is so I'm
completely against indicators you can
see everything on the indicator that
everything that shows you itself on an
indicator can show you itself where
price so you could see where everything
is just based on you know the the price
here if you want to find a a I don't
know like
a 200 day
you know like
um 200 day moving average like where
price has has been trading within that
so we know that within this time here
let's take this area to this area we can
just take 200 days actually
um let me see so it's about 200 days
here we know that our average was above
here so if we look down below where
price is is we know that we're
underneath the 200 moving average you
don't need an indicator to to like you
know let you know this price can show
you this and when price shows you it
then you know that makes it all the more
powerful I didn't see this um this
weekly imbalance I mean monthly sorry I
didn't see this monthly imbalance here
guys something to probably note um for
the future um because then this would
indicate that we could potentially have
another leg down in the stock market and
that would essentially
be to here
29193 so we could potentially tap into
this area before flipping bullish the
market could have another leg down
potentially um in the in the long term
um so let's just something paying
attention to this is on a monthly chart
um you know so maybe that's where we get
our tap and then we push up to to come
back to a higher Market maybe it's it's
this that they're aiming for this
imbalance um so yeah that's how you're
able to figure out the the moving
averages I don't need an indicator to
show me that because I just took
the 200 days within the the um the
monthly and I was able to capture what
the indicator captures we're under the
200 day moving
average price can show you that you
don't need the indicator to show you
that now granted the indicator probably
shows you it faster in terms of the
averages like but the averages only
matter really in stocks the moving
averages do not matter in Forex at all
like at all I know people use them and I
know people have these theories about
them and cool great amazing if you use
that that's that's cool if it works for
you that's fine too all of this is
distribution up here so um this is
potentially um shorting back down to
some of these areas so um just be
mindful of that but yeah um you know you
you have let me move this indicator off
before people come in here and be like
you use an indicator you say you don't I
was just showing you guys that for you
know so you guys can see that um Dave
that is like give a man a fish and he
will eat a day but teach a man had a
fish and you would eat forever exactly
exactly he should apply what I taught
him that that's exactly it like that
that's exactly what I was you know like
saying to people that like I could show
you where to take a trade from you guys
see that I call this stuff out all the
time like I'm like oh might go here okay
here oh bounce up this imbalance here
that might run the high here oh just
like a equal equal High here oh that
could end up running a low you guys see
me do that all the time like within all
the past
videos I can tell you where to get in on
trades I can go to the 15 minute and be
like yeah you can take it from here and
then you can get out here cuz I do it
all the
time
but when I'm not here I want to travel
I'm
not if I'm not traveling with y'all I'm
not talking to y'all while I'm traveling
no I'm kidding I'm I will sometimes be
in the group you know talking and
chatting um whenever I can or if I don't
get in trouble but um you know other
than that like
I I you it's a no-brainer it's so so
price came back into this area and
rejected out of this area this could be
a rejection that's sufficient enough to
um end up running the lows uh back into
some of these areas I know there's a
little imbalance within here so just
look out for that um and I pause
sometimes while I'm saying things just
just so you guys don't miss certain
things cuz I see it but that doesn't
necessarily mean you guys might be able
to see it um and look at this look at
this imbalance to we tapped here and
look at how far we came came up 63 Pips
just from this tiny imbalance within
here you got the
top you got the high put you got the the
high ran you tap back into the area we
disregard the Wix because that's
manipulation and
then we pull out of the
area so you're looking for the range of
this high and not this low but the
body that's only when price trades below
the wick to the left so you see how I
said we could be shorting out of this
area I could have easily gave you guys
this trade and been like oh yeah we
could short out of but if if you guys
don't know why it doesn't serve a
purpose and then you get this rejection
here and you might be scared and be like
oh you know price looks like it's not
going down it could very well just be
this
here right here tap into this area this
was an unmitigated area when price took
out this High here after putting in this
this low when it took out this High here
and never trade it back inside so we got
the tap
here so now from the area that we were
talking about where there was the
possible rejection down to the area that
it tapped this is 23 Pips in just 1
minute $20 in a minute $200 in a minute
$2,000 in a minute whatever it is that
it means to you just understanding that
simple principle just got you what
people make an hour or
sometimes so I can I can show you guys
trades yes like get in here get in there
get if I showed you guys if I showed you
guys my trade history you wouldn't
believe you wouldn't believe the the
amount of money that that like I come
across in these markets both lose and
win well now it's not really losing
anymore so um it's like sparingly on
trading but you know the both both both
lose and win if if you guys saw it it
would be like what you lost or you're
you're you're in draw down by like
$5,000 and then immediately you're Plus
$220,000 in
profit after $5,000 draw down and $5,000
draw on is
just like couple
Pips it's like very very like you know
um high frequency in a
sense
and I did see something with binary
somebody told me about um binary like
synthetic indices um it looks like it
moves the same exact way so if you guys
learn this and that's something that
your country um does or is interested in
then you know like it's the same thing
too we could be shorting down to um this
imbalance guys so just be mindful of
that even if we run certain highs and we
pop back up sometimes that's just a
retracement back into the area to
continue
short so just be mindful of that um but
this is what I want you guys to
understand cuz the same way I talked to
you guys about this and this and I
talked to you guys about the Candlestick
pattern here and I talked to you about
it here look it happened on the top side
too we get this Wick above we have this
area here and this area here and then we
trade away but after we trade away what
do we do we come back up and test the
area and this is this is one that looks
sideways
we test the area come back into it test
the area and we leave out of
it so the actual move is up
here to take you
down but most people they're trading the
trend line break to come here look at
the difference in value that that is
let's say you traded the trend line
break to here 23
Pips but if you saw this happening and
you you saw the test of this
area that's 40
44 so not only is this the discount area
but you're discounting yourself down
here discounting your own trade down
here if you're not you know utilizing
and and learning these
principles you're discounting yourself
there so I want you guys to expose
yourself to this over and over and over
and over and the same way that I talk
about it over and over and over and over
and over and over again that's the same
way that I want you guys to learn
this listen to it if you have to if you
can't watch it if you have a long drive
if whatever it is like like just listen
to it then you know my voice my voice is
sexy enough you know no I'm kidding but
just listen to it you know like you
don't always have to see it but just let
it like like travel through your mind
let it just wander in those those empty
places or or not empty I don't I'm not
calling people empty mind it but I'm I'm
just saying like let let it like get
into into there you know like let it
just in random places it's coming up you
know like now when I hear I know um an
America we have football here um that
they play it's a huge sport here um and
everybody's like oh the s
you know conference title and I'm like
the SEC plays basketball or or football
or whatever and then I'm like oh the SEC
is a conference in football it's not a
like it's not the governmental Authority
for stocks or Securities and stuff you
know so okay but sometimes you know I
get that you know
so so yeah it's it like that that's how
much it's going through my head I'm I'm
sure that I have friends who are tired
of me just always talking about this all
the time I'm more than sure that I have
friends who are tired of that like
absolutely like give it a break bro you
know but just just getting it in your
mind having it like like just go through
your mind at all times I'm in church and
I'm thinking about this I'm in the
grocery store and I'm thinking about
this I'm checking the market to see if
it moved what it's
closed that's how submerged I am into it
it's closed and I'm still looking at it
like you know let me look back and see
what happened you know during fomc okay
yeah that was it there and the market is
closed I can't do anything but I just
have the obsessive nature of of loving
what happens with the market you know so
you guys definitely got to you know like
get to that place because then you'll
start to see things the way I see it
then you start to understand things the
way I understand
it and that's when like it BEC so much
more powerful now I trade when I want to
trade I don't have to trade I trade when
I want to trade I trade when I want to
get something so the other day um not
the other day like you know some time
ago I went to Colombia um
and for me I was like you know if I want
to go to Colombia make that money and go
and then I I've successfully earned this
might be pushing up above this high so
watch it I've successfully earned cuz
this is a tap back into um this pattern
um i' I've successfully
earned that trip to
Colombia so because I've earned that and
because it's it it's something that I
worked for I'm going to enjoy the hell
out of and I'm going to do whatever it
is that I want and I'm G to even make
some money to to have as cash on a side
and now I've funded my entire trip just
because I was able to go into the market
and work for it set it
up you know so that's that's the power
that you now
wield you now possess sorry you now
possess that
power to be able to live lifestyle where
your salary could be
anything
anything your salary could be anything
that you want
anything your friend should
know um the power know the power of
Forex Trading and have the freedom they
want in life exactly this is why I
wanted to run around and teach everybody
this everybody I'm like oh my gosh we
have our little tiny Minds thought that
it was so so inaccessible to becoming a
millionaire we knew there was a way but
we thought that it was hard work nope it
is not hard work yeah maybe the hard
work is the
learning but the actually like like
making the money look that might be a
equal high right there making the money
no
no not hard at
all once you actually learn and you get
like the real information after all of
that garbage information that you took
him from
places it's so easy to become a
millionaire that is the goal the goal
should be like if if money was a goal
the goal should be to become a
millionaire because of how easy it is to
become a
millionaire through through
this technical analysis do this cuz I'm
analyzing the us30 mind you guys I said
I could analyze stocks I told you guys I
could analyze Commodities look this is
gold maybe um did I have a trade in gold
look at this look at this oh my gosh
look at
this you guys know where I found this
trade
from Ali don't don't beat me up for
this this area here from this area to
the left look at this tiny area right
here remember the Candlestick pattern
that I tell you guys
about so I love teaching this because it
I I prove it in real time all the time
nobody can tell me anything about it so
um Miss Brown I don't know how to
exactly um pronounce your name or you
may not even be a Miss I don't even know
I'm so sorry about that if you're not
but um you had asked me about hidden snd
zones right
here
I told you it's the manipulation
down and then we end up immediately
running the high
here so we ran this
low and then we ended up running the
high so now we're looking for price to
come back within the range of the last
high and low which is around here
but while we're looking for the range
most people might be looking at this snd
here and then price what goes below
it but there's this long Wick that was
left
behind this is the snd below the
wick so if you
take the
wick and you place this around on the
wick where do you get a
top here and then you go that's where
the real move is in the hidden snd
Zone but I have mentioned well not
mentioned I saw this on gold um I told
you there's there's like a couple
streamers who stream I go in and try to
find a trade um that they're they're
trading um like a a trade on the
commodity that they're trading or or
whatever it is and um so I go to to find
the trade and then I come back later on
to see if it played
out um look at this so I had this area
here um this is June
16th so this is a couple days ago I had
this area here and I said price would
tap here and go up but that was after
all of this imbalance was left behind so
price never came back here until not
never but it came back here later on
over here
so look price Taps into the area right
here price Taps into the area here and
look at where it pushes up all the way
up here this is a $5 movement on
gold mind you these streamers are taking
a dollar or 10 Pips or or 50 um this is
a 50 pip movement that's 10 Pips is what
they take so every morning I come in
just to keep myself fresh I try to look
at other streamers find what it is that
they're doing um and then look for a
trade within their area um so you have
this area right here but then you also
have this imbalance here tiny imbalance
on the inside of here so and and then
not just that this is the Candlestick
structure that we say we want to
see not well the the structure this is
the structural shift that we want to see
the bullish flip on structure
but then within this Candlestick
here did we ever get a test that came
back into this area
no we
didn't price left the area left this
Candlestick structure behind or this
this Candlestick pattern
behind and we didn't get a test so this
becomes an area for later
on this morning I went on the stream to
you know just see what what these people
were trading saw some people waiting on
movements for gold and all that stuff on
the 30 minute or the hourly or the 4
Hour and then they end up taking 10 Pips
on gold 10 Pips alone cool you take 10
Pips on goal you know maybe that's
enough for people you know fine but I
went and found a trade while they were
waiting for a setup and I got a tap on
gold here from across the way all of
this here equal lows all being ran it's
it's liquidity below that if price
doesn't react here and give us a new
high then we're running the lows which
that's what we end up doing running the
lows so as we running the lows to come
back down here I said to myself okay we
could tap into this area but this this
this second line here is the imbalance
the the first line at the top is
imbalance the second line here is the
actual Zone the Candlestick pattern that
I told you guys you know to pay
attention to and where we get retests
from
sometimes uh so we tap into this area
and we push up look we push all the way
up $10 on gold this is a 100
Pips 100 Pips on gold
in 10
minutes and this these people are uh on
the the 30 minute the hourly and only
taking 10
Pips from the from the 30 minute I
should be getting a th000 Pips if I'm
trading that high
up but this is what I'm talking about
with people who lack the ability to read
price because they
can't so we get a tap into the area back
here because of that Candlestick
structure that we saw where it wasn't
retested so look at what we have here
same thing on
gold uh not here let me actually use
here look at
this low put in high put in low put in
We Run The High come back into the area
we leave so even if even if I saw this
trade here and I got into this trade and
my stop loss was really low his stop
loss was like 30 Pips for for just 10
gaining 10 Pips that's
crazy but now that I got this this entry
here from the left
side this entry usually is the scalp
up so with this scalp up I mean it just
kept going I told you some scalps can
turn into long moves but if we noticed
this Candlestick pattern I mean this
well the Candlestick pattern turned into
a structural pattern once we saw that it
turned into a structural pattern what
are we looking
for price to come back test within the
area and then
leave and look this is where the second
entry
goes we get a test into the
area and then we
leave so now that's two trades but with
this trade if you were getting a test
into this area your stop are behind here
that's a lot of risk that's on the table
so we like
to the same flip that we see here we
like to see it at our
entry so now what do we have
here and this is why it always gets so
Saucy we have this High put in right
here we have this low put in what do we
have Wham a run of this high so what are
we doing coming back into the area and
this we came back into the area by 90%
so that's why sometimes I'll use the
last candle of the area and then we come
out so guess where your entry
is your entry is here or if if if we're
being honest about like where your entry
probably would have been it would have
been the middle of this candle here
stops behind the zone don't care about
the wick because it's
manipulation and we're trading
higher so now we go
from
a 50 pip stop loss to a 7even pip stop
loss on the second
entry and then since we know the
structure was created this way now we
know that we're running the high
too because the stru structure created
the pattern as well so we get the
pattern with the Candlestick we get the
pattern with the intermediary structure
but then we also end up getting the
pattern within the larger part of
structure so what you might have here is
gold run this
High run this High come back within this
area and then leave out of the area so
then what you end up having here what
you end up seeing is
this run of this High to come back into
this area is only testing this
Candlestick setup here the structural
setup remember I said we always get a
test into the area and we leave it's
only testing this area if it goes up
above this High comes back into this
area and then leaves so that's how we're
able to kind of see moves ahead of time
because now if it does
this now we're looking at a larger setup
here that happened to let us know we
could potentially be coming back up to
some of these highs up
here
whereas smart
money is going like this and they're
waiting for the trade to get up
there or they might be down in
here they could be down in here
but how do they get involved in here if
price already tapped they look at this
and they go okay don't chase let's let
it get back up to this area because it
looks like it's been
downtrending ever since we tapped into
here we came back up here we tapped back
up here we tapped back up here and we
could be coming back here to continue
making more lows because the real move
could be down here or below
it
so this could be this entry here this
area here this was that Candlestick
pattern that we talked about that was
untested below
here so that's why we can expect a
rejection here and potentially continue
down to this area before going long and
potentially tapping up further into the
actual area here and then we can
continue short and crash through all of
these here that could potentially happen
over the long term but within these
things that we're doing here we're
essentially just creating a story on
each thing that's that's
touched so I hope that I hope that that
explanation helped some people
because that changed my trading
forever that whole explanation that I
just gave about this on this other
streamers trade changed my whole life
forever and this is just on the this is
on on the the five minute on
gold I told you I can trade anything it
doesn't matter what it is we went to the
Hong Kong exchange right here we could
potentially find a trade within here so
price breaks up above this High we have
our little Candlestick pattern
here that we like to see
we also like to see the rules within
that
pattern so we
come here put in this low put in this
High we put in this low and then we run
the high we tap back into the area and
we go same rules same thing I'm trying
to get you guys to see this all the
time all the freaking
time because it happens everywhere it
happens at the top it happens at the
bottom this is a sign of a
reversal so this is actually how you
find the
reversal using utilizing this pattern
and if price drops out of this area and
comes back into this area around here it
can just be retesting this overall
pattern to continue trading
higher so this becomes the area and what
makes this area important too if you
look to the
left this area was responsible for the
structural
break this
pattern so over time if this is trading
higher we could expect to tap
into this area
here somewhere within this area here
and then price to trade higher but if we
go below this area then we're
potentially looking
to
short if we go below this area but we
would have to significantly go below the
area cuz
this this is the last
high and this is the last
low so now
since we have this area here we just
broke above
it this actually
becomes let me see hold on here here
here this validated this so now we're
we're within this range of this High
here and this low here and look at how
many Pips are within this area from down
here to up
here so now the next the next cycle of
of the week or or the next couple
weeks price could do whatever it wants
in between here and all you have within
this area
here all you have within this area here
are losing
Traders that's all you have cuz this is
the area that they bought
at and they bought you up and then sold
into this area and this is where they
started buying and then when they bought
up and broke this structure they came
back into it and sold into this
area so now you're within this range and
people are just losing within
here because they're not seeing that now
this is the area they bought in and look
at how these lows are forming one low
here two low here three low here and
their higher highs building the
trend and they bought you back up into
here and made you think we were going to
run the high and they immediately traded
below they they traded lower to here and
they just tested the area that they
bought up from and they pushed out of
the area and finally got us above here
so now this is an area that price can
come back to within this lower part of
the area so if they end up running this
low that's okay if they want to trade
higher they could come down here tap
into this area and then put in a new
high but if they don't they could come
down into let me actually move a lot of
this cuz I know it looks a little
um distracting if they don't want to
come back into here they still have this
whole area down
here that they could short back into and
this is where the right move could be
at and then they continue up but that
doesn't mean that you can't get a
reaction within this area you still can
get a reaction within this area but this
reaction within this area would come
down to here to bounce back up tap back
into this area before shorting below it
so the real short could be the retest of
this area
and that's it's the same thing over and
over and I just explained this on gold
same explanation on on the Hong Kong
exchange I explained this on Japan
yesterday like every Market any Market
same thing happens same thing applies no
matter what Market you're trading in no
matter what market so I hope that
explanation you know helps you guys
happening so look at this this was on um
EU I don't remember exactly what I was
um putting here but I said we can come
down into this area down here we can go
up above to this area here and then if
we cross this High here we can come back
into the area and then leave so what
happened from across the way when we
crossed this High here we just crossed
the high we tug back into the area but
look
Candlestick pattern
here this bullish
flip it takes us up and runs the high
this bullish flipped flipped off of an
imbalance so we have price come back to
an area for us and what do we get
another bullish flip around here so we
go up but what do we notice as we're
going up we notice I know that looks bad
right now guys but bear with me we
notice the larger structural
flip so if we're coming out of the area
and we see the structural
flip then we know that we're taking out
the
high and that's where we're trading to a
run of the
high and that's because these same
principles this is on a 4X pair I don't
trade Forex pairs like to make money on
I don't trade Forex
pairs but analysis is analysis no matter
what Market you're trading in analysis
is analysis period there's there's no
other way other than analysis
pered analysis look this is a 5
minute if you were looking at the price
on the 5 minute when it was here look at
this imbalance that it tapped into tap
of the imbalance and what are we going
to run the low possibly and then what we
can get another tap into the imbalance
again
if price does come back up here before
trading down here if we get another tap
into the imbalance then that's a recipe
for the lows being ran and I already
probably have these lows being ran
because there's some imbalance within
here we already tapped into lower
portions of the area and traded above
but we didn't give another high so this
is an equal high on a higher time frame
so the first thing we could expect is
this low being ran but we need to be
careful careful around this area because
look we have the Candlestick set up that
we usually like to see so this could
potentially just be coming back in to
give the Third Leg of this setup and
then trade
higher and it looks like a little cat
paw bearish claw whatever it is you want
to call it you know like make up your
own name for it and run your mentorship
teaching it you know but it's it's
essentially you know this same thing we
just don't have a um a mitigation to
this
area so because we don't have that this
is where price could be sending us down
to tap into this area and then
potentially go long from here but it
could send us down from this imbalance
or there's still this area above here
that it can come into so you see as said
price can tap into this imbalance here
or it can trade higher into this area
and this is where the short could be the
long could be within this area or just
below this area right here I mean any
anywhere within this region really um
because um when they talk about discount
and premium areas you look at this whole
move here from the bottom of this move
to top of this move here this is not a
discounted area for for them to continue
to put in new
highs this is the discounted area down
here so you're more so looking for
anywhere between the start of this area
which is the Run of this low and
potentially trading higher from some
area within here but not within this you
know so that could be um EU for for the
day look we get another tap into this
imbalance and a rejection away again we
get a tap and a rejection that's fine
but we want to make sure that we get a
equal High somewhere along that line so
maybe we'll look on the one minute and
see if we get a equal high within here
and then the equal High could be taking
us out of the area here and what retail
Traders are usually seeing within this
is that they're
seeing this
here and they go oh support term
resistance and that's not the real way
to to
trade so we want to see that so we know
we were coming up to this but we want to
see that happen within this region or
else it could just trade higher within
this area so we have rules to why we get
into trades and why we get out of Trades
and those rules stay consistent like
even within here a lot of people
probably don't see but there's a mini
imbalance within here right here and
here yeah right here and here so you
could have price come to sweep these
lows tap into this
imbalance or tap into this imbalance or
within this snd
here and continue trading higher why
because it's it's below the premium
level that you know Banks usually want
to trade from the imbalance is near the
premium level but the imbalances at the
lower level could end up being more
likely than this imbalance here because
it's it's below the premium so the
premium really is this area here so if
we're expecting a tap back into this
area here you know this is like
75% down here is like 80% or so but this
is the premium of this move so that's
why you can expect a short down into the
premium but when you get to the premium
you want to see the same Candlestick
setup so we have this Candlestick setup
here within this region but when we get
down here we also want to see this again
within structure so we know that we're
possibly running the
highs and that's you know essentially
the the way that we trade here um if I
can take a minute and and tell you guys
um that I'm not a financial advisor this
is not Financial advice this is just my
perspective on the markets anything
taught within this channel is all always
based on my perspective and the
education that I'm giving into the
markets if you choose to take trades
within this then that's on you if you
lose your money blow your account that's
on you has nothing to do with me I'm
just well with my teaching if you apply
your teaching you're not going to blow
your account but if you do blow your
account that's on you so we could
potentially be getting the Candlestick
pattern up
here the pattern that we like to see we
could potentially get that up here so
you could even even have a run of this
low tap back into this area it shows us
the Candlestick pattern that we get and
then we actually get the short below
into
here and then that would only correlate
if the dollar is
longing if the dollar is longing then
you should get the short from
um from EU because obviously anything
within anything against the dollar if
the dollar is belonging and going higher
then obviously
the the pairs that are against it are
going um down
essentially so the both this this looks
like it's shorting EU looks like it's
shorting and then dxy looks like is
potentially
longing and where could it long to
potentially here and get a rejection or
here and get a rejection uh but we put
in another low so we want to make sure
that if we go above we don't want to run
this this high High sorry I don't know
why this doesn't click sometimes we end
up running this high and if we run this
high and we expect price to come back
into the area within here why are we
expecting price to come back within the
area because then it'll show us our
Candlestick setup
here and then the dollar might long up
into
here and why are we longing into here
because obviously we're putting in lower
lows but this is our Candlestick setup
from the top side we did get a retest of
it right here so we could possibly even
look to go past it since we already got
a retest of it when price traded out of
the
area so this could essentially be
looking like a long to potentially go to
the high or take this High tap into this
High here and then the short may
actually be within sorry within this
region
here shorting from here
potentially shorting from here
potentially and this could be where the
long is to take us
higher and it's just the story that
price has given us just utilizing these
things and the reason why this area is
likely to short is because look I mean
likely to to break up above is because
look this is trend line
liquidity whether it's this here whether
it's this here it's all trend line
liquidity so we could expect price to
run all of it tap into this area reject
and come down but if we come straight
down from here then this could be where
the long is running these equal Lowes
across here and then potentially taking
us back
up above this High here if we get down
here first so all we essentially do is
just find ways to you know get involved
in the market whereas smart money
they're waiting for the market to come
to them and it's cool if you want to
wait for the market to come to you You'
just be waiting a pretty long time and
that's kind of why I use the the trading
techniques that I use because you know
like
it I'm I'm joining in on whatever it is
that the market is doing I'm joining in
on a continuation of the
market so look at
this you have the short out of this
area and where do we short
to there's an imbalance between
here this is the imbalance that
originally sent price up so because this
imbalance was tapped already you could
have a second tap to the area of this
imbalance and then price trades up again
because remember I said the first tap on
the imbalance is usually the scalp up
and I mentioned this this scalp gave you
60 something Pips price returns back to
the imbalance again and now you're
looking for your move here I told you we
could be trading higher because this
area here I had said that I said watch
it you know we could have a pullback
within this area and continue higher I
think we were like right here when when
I said
that because it was the tap the second
tap of the imbalance the double tap of
it and the double top of it traded us
higher so now if price is going to shore
out of this area we know
that this
imbalance has done its job or price has
done its job in filling this
imbalance so then we'd end up looking
for it to potentially short below the
area of the
imbalance to potentially some area
within
here because this is still an
unmitigated area this is still an
untested area of this
setup and this is it happening on the
top
side just like it happened here on the
top side so this happens over and over
and over and over again and I try to
teach people about it so they won't need
me because I'm going to be traveling I'm
going to be seeing the world I'm going
to be in Aruba and Greece and all those
different places and you guys may I
might not have internet connection I
didn't have I barely had internet
connection in Colombia and I had the
audacity to be trading when I barely had
Connection in
Colombia barely anytime I left the hotel
there was no connection at all no
internet
connection look at this you see this
this area that we like to see look at
the test within this area we tap into
the area we test but this could just be
coming back up to tap
into this area here before leaving
because this would just be the retest
but usually the retest comes after the
run of the low so um we probably want to
wait to see the run of the low first and
then potentially tap back up into and
then that's where the final short could
potentially
come
yeah so this is pretty much different
than um it's just it's some of the same
rules within smart money but it's not
all of that you know oh wait for the
market to come to you you know don't
overtrade if you don't find a setup
today it's all right there's more
tomorrow
no smart money doesn't teach you that no
there's a setup every single day on
every single time frame and there's
multiple
setups multiple setups I could find
three four setups on an hourly time
frame and watch it play out throughout
the rest of the day or potentially into
the next day there's no way that I
should come into the market and not find
a setup absolutely no way absolutely you
see how I just said to you guys that oh
this could be a retest of this area but
when I looked above I'm like oh wait no
we usually break the low first and after
we run the low then we get a retest of
the area and it
leaves so that was you know some
indication to stay out of a long going
up and potentially ENT a short but where
to the run of the low and then we get a
retracement and look we just ran this
low here and now we're getting a
retracement back up potentially to here
potentially back to the the area
above but we ran that low and where did
we find support on the run of the low
right here
OB forget the wick that's manipulation
don't care about that tap into the
OB I'm telling you guys I I I do this
every day to show you guys that like
there's nothing better than look at this
look at this up
this come on man this is just a scalp 22
Pips up just noticing this area not
paying attention to the wick taking this
area having price tap in and go look
price already tapped in here and gave us
another high so that means that this
area is an invalidated area to begin
with it's just that just because it's
invalidated doesn't mean that it can't
give you a
reaction so this area is an invalidated
area we're not expecting this area to
give us higher highs because it already
did we tapped into this area here and it
gave us the higher
High I mean unless this is a double
bottom to the area who knows but you
know nonetheless the scalp up is usually
the
first entry that I
get we scalp up
20 something Pips come back into the
area to potentially test the area look
we got the test right
here and we could potentially go back up
to
here but this when you begin to learn
these things and you begin to like
familiarize yourself with this stuff
then like it all starts to come to you
just as fast this is on the one minute
in the New York session most of the
times I'm talking and I look up at the
time and I'm an hour and a half in look
1:49 an hour and 49 minutes hour and a
half in because price is moving so fast
and I'm trying to you know teach while
helping you guys adjust to to everything
within the market and then you end
up you know with like beautiful stuff
like this because there are reasons
behind
it so we talked about shorting from here
to potentially the imbalance here but
then there was this imbalance within
here that price was just double tapping
and gave us another push up and within
here there could be an imbalance further
below here I'm not saying that there's
not there could be because on a higher
time frame it could be like a 5 minute
imbalance that price is tapping
into
um so no this is not a 5 minute maybe a
minute little tiny one here within the 3
minute that's the double tap uh no two
minute let me see the 3
minute no nothing there so so this is
definitely like within this area this is
definitely um an imbalance in a on a
lower time frame than
this but because of how far down it came
below it but then we still saw our
Candlestick setup and we still got a
test of the Candlestick setup which I
mentioned that we look like we're
testing the Candlestick
setup I mentioned it right here when we
were Downing this area so then we ended
up trading
higher after tapping into this balance
and after testing the Candlestick
setup so we don't have the same thing
here you see how I just mention mention
that that this was a retest of the area
and it was just taking us back up to
here if anybody took that
trade 32 Pips up just within 3 minutes
that I just mentioned this so that's why
I'm trying to get you guys to understand
the like how powerful the the techniques
are like how how important it is to
grasp what I'm saying because it's
happening right in front of us over and
over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over
again it's happening over and over
again and if if if you bunker down on
learning
this man you will never need me again
you will never come back to this place
again to trade ever you will never come
back to this place to trade again so
because you may not come back you you
might want to hit the like button and
subscribe if you're new if you like what
you're seeing if you like the teaching
if you're learning things subscribe you
know we do this every single day we do
this sometimes in the evening during the
Asian sessions we do this whenever we
want because this is our life I don't
have a full-time job this is my
full-time job and I will never again in
my life have a full-time job not saying
that it's bad that anybody else has a
full-time job by the way I'm not saying
that um watch watch this this High here
we could potentially come above this
high and tap back in before trading
higher just because this possible setup
here within this area um but we do this
every day like And subscribe guys turn
on the notification Bell only 20% of the
people that's following me have the
notification Bell on turn the
notification Bell get in for these top
Downs they are the most important part
of trading every single day is the top
Downs those are killers absolute bangers
and then we just teach the algorithm
within the one minute and and that's it
so subscribe if you like what you see if
you don't like what you
see you don't have to like the video
that's okay you can dislike it if you
want to but also share this with other
people that you know who trade so they
can get the real deal for the stuff that
that like you have to pay thousands of
dollars for this information I know that
this information is thousands of
dollars and I became Robin
Hood so I'm actually teaching this let
me actually save this template
um
uh since she wanted to tell me that I
should use a gray background I'm just
going to save it at that but I'm Robin
Hood guys this is why let me show you
guys my chart
actually uh is this it here this is why
I initially started with let me take
this no gap on candle indicator off I
initially started with black and green
candles when I started first trading
because I considered myself Robin Hood
I'm taking all of the
information that's put out there in
these secret groups that nobody wants to
really share that information with the
public and I'm like hey you know who do
I know I could pass away next week
this could help people help generations
of
people why should it be all hoarded for
those who could afford it doesn't make
sense so this is how my chart was
actually um in in the beginning because
it signified being Robin Hood I have a
um a it's interesting I have a tattoo
here um on my uh bicep here uh you see
that guys it's
uh right here it's an
arrow I love arrows what they represent
I love that Robin Hood used arrows to
you know like do what he
did and for me I like I embody that
that's the person that I am and it's not
the Robin Hood that turned off the buy
button with GameStop it's like the real
Robin Hood so um yeah I I
essentially you know believe
wholeheartedly in and if people are poor
they're not poor because they want to be
poor some people are born
poor like it's not your fault if you're
born poor but as Bill Gates says it's
your for it's your fault if you die poor
and for some people it's we have
exceptions to that we're not saying
everybody who dies poor is it's their
fault because the truth is there are
some things that happens within
government within laws that that you
know essentially causes people to be
liquid liid at times that's what this
whole recession is this recession is
liquidity all the money that they gave
out within the stimulus they recouping
that back up liquidity but for me I just
want to be able to help people uh hi bro
one quick question um isn't that a
rising wedge or that
doesn't oh uh so so yeah um I yeah this
this could be um a rising wedge
uh here
uh within
here
yeah this could be a ryen wedge um
pattern within here um and a breakout of
it a retest of it and trade away um but
I don't I don't trade um retail Concepts
um I more so just trade the algorithm um
of the market so in terms of retail
Concepts again some of them could be
profitable look it's falling out of the
wedge yeah you know like it it could
totally be a a rise and wedge um but the
retail concepts are only like 30% of the
time that they actually Rising wedge RIS
and triangle whatever you want to put it
they're like 30 40% of the time they
work you know like it's not um it's not
consistent so I really don't use them I
just utilize structure with
um you know like supply and demand zones
or
imbalances and and that's it um
you know just the way price forms how it
moves uh but yeah if if you like if if
this is you know what you're seeing and
you're trading from this this would be
you know trade to Short from yes because
you see the distribution happening at
the top side you are aware of the break
of the trend line but you're also aware
of the break in structure below not
really a break of structure but the run
of the low you get a retest within the
area within our candle Candlestick
pattern that we usually teach here on
the channel we get the retest of the
area within this and then we ended up we
end up shorting out of the area so we
could potentially shortpass this snd
because this already gave us a higher
high above this High here so we're not
necessarily looking to um utilize this
anymore for entries to go longer because
this is already invalidated so we would
essentially be looking for a short pass
the area potentially into this area you
might get a bounce from this area to
come back into here and then you can get
another short into this imbalance price
hasn't tapped into this imbalance as of
yet so you can get a double bottom on
this imbalance and potentially come back
up to whatever area that could be up
here and then you can get another short
down to run these lows into potentially
like an imbalance within here here to
make price come back up maybe test this
area here before shorting again and
that's how the overall trend can be
built and on the higher time frame this
just ends up being the Candlestick
pattern that we like to see but just
from a higher time frame that's how the
trend could potentially roll out so um
yeah you you could utilize um you know
the the retail trading patterns as I say
but they just have to
you know essentially make sense in terms
of structure if they don't make sense in
terms of structure then that could be a
recipe for disaster cuz you could end up
just having it come down to here you
know out of the wedge and then
potentially trading higher after um
sorry after the the top of this area but
again we're not necessarily looking for
the top of this area to give us another
high but there is a possibility that
down here if price gets to it it could
potentially put in another high for us
depending on if it's within an imbalance
maybe might give us a double bottom
within an imbalance to come and run this
trend line high right
here run this trend line
High you know run the liquidity of up
here and then finally give you the short
um and it could it could end up looking
like a manipulation Wick above here and
then you know tap back into the
area so that's just something that that
you want to consider and pay attention
to as you're in the trade so you're not
caught up with um you know just
like the you don't see the structural
shift in price which you know show shows
you that you shouldn't be shorting down
into this area but because you saw the
wedge pattern the wedge pattern just
might make you think that you know it's
safe to take it down through cuz I think
they use the back of the pattern like
here so they would say okay if if the
back of the pattern is 86 Pips then when
price falls out of the wedge you could
expect it to go 86 Pips down which it
could technically go you know 86 Pips to
this balance and maybe trade higher that
could be right for the wedge itself but
if you see a shift anywhere within this
area here then you might miss that shift
where it could take price
higher and now it comes back and hits
your stop loss so um the the wedges are
cool you know um you know but that
that's essentially um why I just use
structure and um just uh zones really um
great thanks for your answer you're
welcome brother um thank you Dave for
your dedication and time for us all
appreciate this slots you're welcome man
you're welcome God bless you too man I I
do it because I just you know I want to
see people do well you know and I want
to see people have an advantage the
retail Trader we don't have an advantage
already in the market because we don't
have the money but if we had the
information that could give us the
advantage we need so it's just the
information solely that that we're
looking to to get because the money's in
the information the money is not in the
actual Market or the product it's in the
information behind the market cuz if the
stock market crashes guess what I'm
trading in Japan I'm trading in Hong
Kong I'm trading in London's exchange
trading in Spain's exchange or Europe's
exchange you have so many other markets
to trade in if this Market crashes
you're the crypto Market that's a global
market Trad in you know like you you
don't really need to limit yourself to
to One Market but if you learn the
analysis of it
now every Market you want to participate
in you're in and doing well in so yeah
oh um hey bro great content so what is
the lowest time frame you would consider
a break because sometimes if we say H1
it might be too late to enter because uh
the 30 minute break was actually enough
um
so a break of of structure for me
usually is um the body closure below the
last
low So
within this area
here we have this low this high this low
we have this High we have this low we
just put in a high so now we're working
within the range of the last High
and the last low here we're working
within the range of that until we end up
putting in another low and then a body
closure above of a high if the body
doesn't close above then this low is not
validated so when this low is
invalidated we could immediately come
crashing through the this low if we're
shorting because this is not considered
a low on the the overall like structure
the larger structure so this is probably
like a 5 minute structure that I just
drew out or maybe even 15 I'm not too
sure but um it's 15 5 15 minute swing
points but um this is um and This is
Swing point on a trend I mean um this is
the the smaller Trend within that so you
have this High and this last low and
price just broke the structure to the
top side here so now not only do we have
this and this
area we also have this High put in so
that means that within this whole area
here price can do whatever it wants so
we would need a structural break out of
the
area in order to give us some indication
that price is going bearish so once we
get the structural break out of the area
we might get a retest back into this
area and then
leave but the structural break usually
is with the body closure um below a
particular swing point so if you're
asking for for the one hour you're
looking at potentially um a Break um
sorry let me
you're looking at a break on the one
hour this this hourly here right here
this is not a this coming up above this
this is not a structural break this Wick
here unless let me actually zoom in so I
could show you guys a little better I
keep forgetting that you guys don't see
the screen as large as I do so with this
here this is not a structural break
right here this Wick coming above this
high this is not a structural break the
structural break is the body closing
above the high so if this body right
here if this body here closed Above This
high now that validates this
low
here because you got the body closure
Above So now now we're looking to come
between this area
here and this low here we're looking for
an area within here that price could
potentially trade to and then give us
another high to break this so what we're
actually looking for is a tap within
some area within here I always talk
about the imbalances because as I
mentioned they're stronger areas than
the SN D zones are but if you want to
use the snd zones you can um or the the
supply candle the demand candle if you
want to use that you can but usually
what you want to see when price comes
back into this area to let you know that
we could potentially be running a high
is let me delete all of this real quick
to show
you usually we want to see this
here the Candlestick pattern that we
usually talk about we want to see this
within an area of Interest so this here
is a
fractal this area here is actually a
supply uh I mean sorry a demand area on
a lower time frame so let me select this
area here and actually show you on a
lower time frame what it looks
like you take this and you take this
price came below it which is fine
because we're still within the range of
this so for the range of this we
essentially have to be below the
50% below the 50% in order to get a
sufficient enough reaction to take us up
and put in another
high so we get the 50% of this move we
have to be below the 50% of the
move we get into the below the 50% but
then we spring up up out of the
area after we spring up out of this area
you look at the lows and highs being put
in low here we get a run of this High
the lower
high or the higher low whatever we get a
low of it we get a run of it so after we
run it we come back into the area of the
range that was ran and we
leave and that's all within
our structural break we found a
structural break so we're expecting it
to happen within here because the break
of structure to the top side we're not
expecting it to run below this at all
because we put in a new high which means
that this low
becomes the protected
low here that becomes the protected low
somebody just ring my doorbell so hold
on real quick it's probably a delivery
man
FedEx
yeah so this becomes a protected low
here oh my gosh did I check the the
music oh my gosh this stream is probably
going to get taken down I'm so upset uh
the if the music is not um uh no
copyright then um often times you end up
um getting the copyright hit on the
stream damn it come on I'm so upset
about that cuz the then they they end up
if it's a song that's that's blocked in
C a certain number of countries then
they end up just blocking the whole
stream all together so um that's the
sucky part but yeah um as I was
explaining the oh you get it now okay
great great I'm glad you get
it I I go off into like talking but I
want to like explain the whole thing um
for you guys so um yeah that that's
that's how it'll look and on a lower
time frame when you get down to this
area are here now all you do is I mean
obviously if you ask me about time frame
you probably know um about this too but
let me just you know show you on a lower
time
frame if you see the top within your
area now you just want to see it happen
again and look it happens again
here same thing same exact thing put in
a high put in a low right run the high
come back into the area
leave and now you see that
happen within your your hourly area and
now all you do is
just take the hourly
move and even though price comes back
to um this area
here price comes back to this area here
I mentioned um to to the guys on the
stream I mention that often times
when when you have this area put
in when you have this area put in you
usually get a test of the area before
trading
higher and that's even on a higher time
frame you get a test of the area before
trading
higher or or a reaction off the area
maybe you may not put in a high like
look right right here there wasn't a
high put in but you did get a reaction
from it so now I mentioned that you can
just take a
square Saucy man you can take a square
and put it around this area and now look
you get a tap of the square in this area
so you get a tap into the 50% just as if
it's a a um demand Zone because it is a
demand Zone look at
this on the higher time time frame this
is one
candle here but maybe it's on the
15 here this one dogee
candle where we tap here and we
go but we're just finding the demand
zones as they're made and then we're
seeing the mitigation of it but because
time is fractal you see everything all
on the same time time frame got ah head
to work but thank you once again I
watched most of your video library and
it has helped a lot I'm glad Walter I'm
glad that it helped you so much so happy
about that um let me go back to hold on
I'm getting a call from my my kid hold
on
sorry about that guys if you haven't yet
already please can you like the video so
I can get to the other side of trading
Forex and um it would get people out of
all of this garbage information that
they're learning um and they'd actually
get to learn the the real things so um
please if if you can you know like the
video it's good for the algorithm
subscribe and send these videos in these
groups that you guys are in these um
telegram groups or these um uh only if
this has helped you if this has not
helped you at at all don't share it
don't go lying to people about oh my
gosh this guy's a great Trader you could
learn so much and then you haven't learn
a thing from me don't do that I don't
want any Liars here I don't want like if
you're not really learning don't share
it to other people as if you're learning
make sure that you're learning something
and only share what you actually learn
something from not just the excitement
behind the person because I tell people
all the time you want to make sure that
you're sharing information with people
who they are actually like the
information is verified it's real
information it's things that can go back
and be tested tried and true and if you
can do that and and this does that for
you then this may very well do that for
someone else so just you know share the
video like the video share it in these
groups I know you guys are probably in a
bunch of telegram or Discord groups and
stuff like that just be like hey this
guy teaches live and live markets you
watch him you don't have to watch him
but he has some pretty good Concepts and
if you've learned something from this
then hopefully you you know can also
teach other people this too I don't care
about making this into a commodity I
don't care about making this into a
selling selling a course or cuz I could
put this all in a course sell it for I
could sell this course for $10,000 I
promise you I could sell this course
each course that I create based off of
ways that I have to to trade I can
certainly sell each course for
$10,000 because that's how good and
accurate this information is I don't
care I make my own money I don't care
about nobody else's money now if it's
taken away from me like let's say I
start doing consultations one-on ones
with people and stuff and I start
charging for consultations because it
takes away from Trading then obviously
there's a possibility that I could do
that but if it doesn't take away from
Trading there's no reason I I'm I'm
doing this because I love it I love
watching the markets I love watching all
of this happening over and over again so
this is just my love for it I used to
watch charts all day and all night and
not
stream why not show people what I'm
seeing and why why create like a a
commodity off of this why create some
type of service off of
this why would I do that I I shouldn't
have to do that I shouldn't want to do
that at that
like I should want to foster a community
of people who are making money and who
are learning different approaches to the
market and we could actually help each
other out with real life
skills like I know things about so much
like so many things I know things about
credit repair I know things about
getting business loans I know like the
The Well of knowledge that I have in my
brain is not just when it comes to
trading it's just the way my brain
processes things and the way that it
works but it's not like you you guys see
me do this and I'm very efficient in
this but I'm just as efficient in like
all the other areas of the things that I
consume too so I'm very very big on
sharing bad information with people
don't do that I'm not okay with that
this is people's money that's on the
line this is you know like people are
trying to get a better life people are
trying to change their live in
circumstances don't do that if the
information does not work
don't do that I don't care how much you
like me I don't like none of that I
don't care about any of that if this is
not helping you find something that
helps you and then teach that to
somebody else and send them the video of
whoever that was that helped you but if
this is not helping you don't share it
with other people until it actually
begins to help you and that's how
serious I am with this I'm not building
a brand I'm not creating an Empire or
anything like that I'm just trying to
help people you know
and I I want to do it with the most
accurate information possible the most
accurate information possible and that's
why I'm I'm very big on like not sharing
certain things um with people because
again you know you want to make sure
that that you know it's it's the right
thing so I share Pips of Persia sham I
share um smart money Source because
those those guys I've tested seen that
they're tried and true with their
information it's accurate you can go
back and test it and see it in live
markets you know like amazing guys and
they don't even know me they don't even
know that I stream I've never had a
conversation with any of them but I know
quality work when I see it so I'm going
to continue to offer quality work to
people you know so yeah um yeah this
helps me a lot bro made like 1K using
your strategy oh that's great man I'm
I'm so happy about that I want you to do
that every day I was taking $600 and
making $1,000 every day with
$600 that's only $600 in my account I
was making $1,000 every single day and
this is when I was using retail patterns
I wasn't even trading this stuff I was
just using trend lines I'm like oh price
falls out of the trend line I'll get it
on a quick short and then wait for the
next trend line to form and get on a
quick short because the one minute forms
a bunch of trend lines
and then runs them or runs portions of
them so I was using that and that was
when I didn't know how to trade I don't
recommend using trend lines only to
trade with they could be a good source
of like helping you to notice something
and then like waiting for that
particular thing to happen I think I
have a trend line somewhere um
within
Jesus Christ there's so much stuff
here add a trend line somewhere in here
I don't I don't know exactly oh my gosh
I think I deleted everything yikes let
me see if I can go
back yeah it looks like I deleted
everything oh that makes me so sad who
asked me that question and made me
delete all this no I'm kidding I have um
uh this chart over
here so yeah this this is where the top
down one's done that's why I have two
charts just in case I make a mistake on
one um they usually overlap sometimes uh
with the top down and stuff but yeah
um yeah this this was
it so yeah look at how I mentioned that
we can come back to this area
here come back to this area now we want
to watch for this pattern potentially
forming here because we got one area
here right here we have another area
here but this would have to take the
high first and then come back into the
area to give us that other area and then
potentially go long up into some of
these areas here or maybe even just to
this
imbalance so this is just what you want
to be careful of this is not really a
um we're not really finding like this
low right here is not really finding
support from like a particular area
that's fresh or
unmitigated so this can just have like a
suo pushup to tap into an area and go or
it can just continue to fall as we
mentioned from like up
here
um so yeah um uh but I'm glad this is
helping people um and I want to continue
to be able to um it was this imbalance
here that I had mentioned guys so just
be careful of it right
here tap there and go um yeah exactly
naked women you you know what's so
interesting let me show you guys this uh
real quick
um where is it uh oh wow you guys I
guess you guys really like what you see
that's 14 followers already today that's
good thank you for that uh let me show
you guys
this uh right here
analytics my my
audience uh let's
see let me show you guys
this um look at this 94% of my viewers
are
men the ladies don't love me at all
what's happening no I'm kidding uh but
yeah 90 94% of my viewers are
male and only 6% of the views come from
women and I promise you I promise you
because of like how amazing and
fantastic women can be I promise you
that the women in the chat could wipe
the floor with the man like they're just
so meticulous about things and like I
promise you it's be the day of
Armageddon if we had to trade against
most of the women because they're just
like so much attention and detail and
I'm telling this's one girl here now she
she would scraped the floor with me or
money she would scraped the floor with
me and she's going to probably be like
the best Traer in the world you know but
th this is what this this particular um
you know this this particular teaching
can afford you you know so look we have
this area above we also have this snd
here this is a hidden snd Above So price
could very well tap into this area and
go but this could be sufficient enough
to just you know put in another low if
it
did um that's if we were going to
continue short but this is why we trade
and we watch the algorithm and let the
algorithm show us exactly what it is
that it's
doing CU if it shows us that then we're
not making any decisions based on what
we think because I always say trade what
you see not what you think and I stole
that from the trader Jessica Lanes she's
a pretty good Trader as well um with
retail Concepts but I stole that from
her trade what you see not what you
think and I'm not endorsing her I don't
know um like people are great in
hindsight but Forward Motion you really
don't know what people are doing um so
that's that's a a real thing by the way
so I'm not endorsing her I'm just saying
that this is what she says which all of
them have like great sayings and stuff
like that
but you got to be a little skeptical of
that because know it's like those
millionaire motivational videos got to
sacrifice you got to pay the payment the
pavement you got to make sacrifices that
when you come back in the future you're
going to look back and be like yeah it
was worth it it was great and then they
tell you to go go to work and put in 16
hours on a shift and and then go back
home and listen to the video again to
pump you up for the next day no those
millionaire videos are garbage those
videos should only only be displayed if
they're show showing you exactly how to
become a millionaire other than that
they're useless um so NZ you have
mentioned
um uh q n 100 it went
up uh as you analyze and it filled the
Gap um so I didn't know there was a
there was a gap but I remember I did
analyze it for you uh look at this so
this this is the this is the analysis
here I told him that we could either
come to this area here or this area here
so we tapped into the
area we formed the little Candlestick
structure that we like to
see and then we pushed up out of the
area look at where we're at now all the
way up here from this particular area
that we could we said we can get a
bounce from um later on in the day I
think this was yesterday it might have
been um but just within that area alone
you know so yeah I'll um I'll analyze it
again um but it looks like we still have
some some areas here from the top down
that we
did
um here yeah see there's there's still
some areas within this um top down but
what you want to consider if this is
going to continue bullish
um
tapped into the Zone came up you see we
got the double bottom on the imbalance
and we left we going to make sure you
see that at the areas of interest that
you're trading from um so we took out
this
High we ran this
High
um we want to look at the area that's
responsible for running the high as as
well as the range of the area
so that's
here so this is the last high this is
the last low we just put in a new high
so we're between this high and this low
here so we look
like it looks like we're coming back
around to somewhere within this region
here um
somewhere within this region let me take
the whole move
here
um yeah we could be coming back to tap
within this area um let me actually just
look at what happened in
here before I let you guys know that uh
uh uh um we got a test of this area when
we broke
above
yeah we already got a test of this area
um we got to tap into this area this is
unmitigated down
here
um so we could get a tap within this
area on NAS if we're coming
down um this could actually be the area
that we begin to trade higher
from
um did we get a test oh so this is the
overall schematic
here um this is the overall schematic
here you see how we said we like to get
that in place and then we want to see
price trade out of it and come back and
test it and then go
so if we're going to continue um bullish
to the top side
um price would end up tucking back into
this area and then
leaving but if it continues bullish like
it did here you see how we had this area
here we pushed up
bullish we ran this
high and then we flipped bearish
so the area that we may potentially be
coming back to is this area here
[Music]
overall we could be looking to test this
but we have quite a ways to get up there
so um what we may end up doing
is having a tap within this
area coming back to here and then
trading higher and then if you open up
the schematic a little more you begin to
see that it looks like a larger 4H hour
setup like
this so then as we continue to go up we
come back and possibly test this area
now and then we put in more highs that's
if price continues to trade higher
that's how it would be moving on the
higher time frames so again like we said
we could see all time frames from the
same time time frame because time is
fractal so um if you're looking for a
more immediate move then no it's it's
cool if you have a bunch of questions I
love that people ask questions I love
that people want me to look at charts
I'm completely okay with that trust me
there's no issue at all I'm asking
questions so this is a low
that this is a 15minute low so this is
this is an important low but
then
we have this area above here we already
mitigated this snd Zone with this so
this is left
unmitigated we tap into this
area we push above
it we tap into the center of this
hidden snd right
here we tap we reject
out
um
put in this low came back
up we ran the high but what happened
first
here so we traded above the high went
into the low and then we came back up so
this area potentially is already
mitigated just because it did
that
um but then we tapped up into this area
here this area here that it left behind
so we might be trading higher to come up
into these areas
here because if you look right
here
this was the tap of the area
um we tapped into this area pulled back
up we have a snd right above
here we have a snd above here if it gets
rejected from here
then
here if it gets rejected from here then
that could potentially be um the equal
high that results in the run of the low
or the run of the lows in this
particular case but we may still be able
to get up into this area here this is
mitigated this is mitigated this one is
not this one is not
yeah this one isn't so just be mindful
that if we do make our way up above this
High we could potentially be going to
this area here because there's a lack of
mitigation but sometimes you have it to
where price comes to here I know this is
a 15 minute um so it could take some
time to get here but sometimes you might
have right here you might get this
rejection
first here you might have this come up
to this you might reject back into here
you might have it come here reject back
into here then you might have it come up
here reject
here create a equal
High run the low come back in here and
then leave the whole area um you could
potentially have that up within this
area um but it looks like there's a
potential for price to continue to um
push higher um so that's just what I'm
seeing with nas um and you can just
follow that potentially and um see we
might really be going down if we run
this low here so we're within this range
right
now on this low here we're within this
range right
now so this
is this is the top of the
[Music]
range I don't really use this but I know
if it might be helpful for you so this
is this is the range that we're in here
and this
is 126 pip range so you just got to see
what kind of happens within here the
story of what it tells within here and
then that gives you the breakout whether
it's below or above and that's how the
that's how the Nas is looking so look we
just got the top of this area we want to
see what it does there if it doesn't
give you a double top there on a smaller
time frame then it could potentially
still be traveling to the the areas
further
above um but you can correlate um this
chart you can correlate the the us500 or
or the Russell 2000 is it um you can
correlate that because they move hand
inand this one has already moved 1 th000
Pips since it opened this is the S&P
moves more than all of the other indices
together all the indices generally
follow the
S&P um so yeah that's that's the top
down for NZ uh you welcome uh for that
um I know I spent you know quite a bit
of time there let's go back to us30 see
what we have Happening
Here
Yeah so look here here was here's here
was the the um entry you see the
manipulation manipulation down then
price shifts up and breaks the high we
tap back into the area that was
manipulated and we longed from that area
to go up
here it's the same thing over and over
over and over again and I want you guys
to see it because it happens over and
over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and
over over and over again like over and
over and over people think I'm a
magician no over and over again remember
what I said about this I said we could
potentially come up above this High we
can come back into this area and we
might go long I said that when this was
consolidating here because I said here
was the stab but I had mentioned that
we're not really in an area um like an
important area um we're not really there
so I don't really see this pushing up to
break the high it can not too sure but I
did see that we were gearing up to come
back up to this area up here and it was
because the rules and the principles
within this
here within this this same pattern that
I try to get you guys to see maybe on
the five minute it looks
cleaner
same pattern that I try to get you guys
to see over and over again I'm like a
mother
repeating things over and over again
same pattern here within an area of
Interest here so this is where the the
higher time frames become pretty good to
you know take a look at because if you
guys look at
this on the five
minute it's it's fine to take a peak um
if you want to at them but if you look
at this here look we went above this
area here so we dropped down we ran the
high of this area price never came back
up so what do we do we look for price to
return back into the range of the area
look at the tap that we get beep right
there and we trade higher so we could
potentially be looking to trade higher
if we go up above this here but it's the
same thing that's on NAS areas above
that we have
us500 well this actually looks like
um this actually looks
like it's going
up it looks like it's
still pushing up
um
so this grabs the High
um you could potentially have it to
where the rest of everything goes up
above their areas
too but look at
this free forget the high cuz as we said
manipulation trades back down within the
range of the area don't care about that
forget the high look we tap here go
where do we go down to and imbalance
here and all it takes is just spotting
this stuff real fast in real
time I hate this area because I feel
like when I'm trying to like Center it
exactly my hand starts cramping up and
I'm like not now I need to get it
perfect cuz I'm a little bit of a
perfectionist so look we short from
here we short from this
area and we come all the way down to
this area
here and we get here in 3 minutes after
noticing the tap there but but then we
get a tap here and what do we
get we get the structure to know that
we're going to flip the high we get the
Candlestick pattern to know that we're
flipping
above but what is it
that we talk about we put in this low we
put in this High we put in this low we
get a run up the high we tap back into
the area and then we
go and it's it's this simple over and
over and over again it doesn't always
look the same but it always happens the
same way and this is why I was telling I
think it was um Tav it might have been I
was telling them about the inside you
want to look at what's happening within
here you need rules for this the rules
is that we put in this low we put in
this High we ran this
low and then we ran the high directly
after
manipulation downside and upside we tap
back into a premium area and then we
trade out of it and that's that's all
you ever need to know with trading just
spot that that's it nothing else so look
we took this High here and I said we
could be trading higher let's look at
this here oh my gosh these delivery
people are always ringing my
doorbell look at that what did we do we
took this high
too I said if we were taking the high on
S&P 500 then we're probably going to
take the high here I don't know who this
is hold on let me
check
sorry that was my obnoxious kid uh so
look NZ we still didn't get up
above but we took the the recent high
that was here so now what we want to
look for is is this test tting the
Candlestick pattern that it left for us
here is this just a test of it to trade
higher up into this
area or are we
running cuz we we will eventually but
are we running the trend line
low so is it going to be like
this we could tap into this little area
here this little area here because this
resulted in the structural break above
here or maybe there's an imbalance
within here that price is going to let
me let me zoom in cuz I know I'm seeing
it from like that very tiny uh portion
of it but you guys are probably not not
really seeing it well uh but yeah this
this area here you know we can tap up
into
this you know potentially get a tap and
oh we it looks like we already got a tap
on top of it
but we can tap into the middle of this
and then continue up as well but this
only happened here this push up only
happened because of this imbalance below
so we could even come down to the tip of
this which would also be a second touch
of the imbalance and then potentially
trade higher so this is an area that you
want to watch out for if you're in Nas
by the way um and I'm supposed to be
doing us30 sorry
guys goodbye back to the
[Music]
30 yeah okay so you see how this
Candlestick pattern here gave us a new
high after tapping into an area to the
left now granted we mentioned that we
didn't think that this area was strong
enough to give us a high but we said
we'll see we saw this being created down
here on the entry so we were like oh
wait okay no this looks like this that
pattern that we usually see this looks
like a could be heading to the top side
and what did we get from this area here
going all the way up to here at first we
thought we were just rejecting from here
so that was our bias to come up but we
pushed all the way up and came back in
and got rejected in this area not only
did we get rejected in this area right
here you guys see this let
me so we come down here we come back up
here we come down here and then we end
up running the high
here running the high here look we ran
the high right there we came back into
the area here actually no wait let me
make sure I'm not lying because people
be lying on God's internet and I'm not
trying
to be that person at all um let's see so
we put in a low we get a run of the high
let me see if this candle
actually I want to see if it went up
above this High first and then came back
below the
low because sometimes it'll mitigate an
area just within the same candle so let
me look um whoop There we go mitigate
came back into the center of it and then
left so
that's that's what we got within that
area so this here was only a second
touch within the area so I told you the
first area is the scalp up this if it
returns to the area second time that
becomes your longer move but when it
returns a second time what you need is
not a tap on the second time you need a
double bottom for the second time so the
first entry was actually
here this one here stops behind the zone
and you're looking to potentially take
it to
you know like the next structural area
usually I say um utilize the imbalance
or the snd so that's the top quick tap
you're out then we get the second entry
back into here but remember we're not
only buying because we saw this push
back into the area we're going to buy
because the same thing that we saw
here for us to get involved is the same
thing the same thing that we see here
this this entire thing
here
sorry why is this not I'm always maybe
maybe I'm getting like carpal tunnel or
something I don't know my clicks don't
be clicking the math be mathing but the
clicks don't be clicking so we get this
area
here right
here and we end up making the pattern
within the area but within this area
here where your second entry is
look for the double
bottom and it's not really a double
bottom what it is is the same thing that
happened
here you see this
here the same thing that happened here
like this or that happens everywhere
we're looking for it to happen around
our entry so what do we
get
we come down from
here we make our way back up
here we make our way down here we run
the high we tap back into the area and
then we
long so now you not only
had this one
entry across the way as a scalp now you
have the longer move
here
because we returned a second time and
gave you
that so now with this move we're
expecting this move to either come here
or to run all the highs because once it
runs this High these Highs are going to
be ran as well cuz all of this is
mitigated so that's how you get the
second entry and now you end up walking
away with 31 Pips here 52 Pips here 83
Pips on the day
within within 24
minutes 80 83 Pips within 24 minutes now
if if this was um if this was the
regular like the the low lot size that
I'm
using this is I mean for both trades
this is over
$88,000 for my lowest lot
size this setup
over
$88,000 with a six pip stop loss so I'm
only risking
600 on this trade and with an 11 pip
stop loss where I'm only risking 1,000
but I'm risking a th000 to get 3100 and
I'm risking 600 to get
5200 so the risk is still captured in
all of this but it's just made
small and it's because you're using
structural areas where you know
this is where the banks are hiding their
stop loss uh this is actually a 12 pip
stop loss don't want to lie about that
to you guys next you know somebody make
a whole YouTube video about me look at
him he said it was 10 Pips or 11 Pips
and that was 12 you know like people
make videos for like the craziest things
you guys ever saw those ASMR videos they
be
like can you hear me and they get like
millions of views on it just up millions
of views from
that out of this world man but this is
essentially like like how all of it is
taught find area of
Interest understand what's going on in
structure find your setup within that
area of interest and that's all you
want first entry is a scalp second entry
you find a double bottom or a double top
on it and then you take get to that
direction and that's it over and over
and over and over and over it happens
like clock work over and over again so
look this tapped into this area
here and this is how you can comp
compound your trades
too this area here was responsible for
breaking this structure and this above
so you want to look at the area that's
responsible for the structural break
that's this in particular
so right here forget the wick we tap
into the
area and we trade
higher we trade higher so this is your
scalp
here bam up to the snd 21 Pips but now
you're waiting for price to come back
and give you another entry on a test of
this
manipulation a lot of the times I
mentioned that if the wick goes below
the following Wick and pushes back up
that's a manipulation and you don't want
to consider that so now what do we do we
take this to
this and when price trades above it we
consider this area potentially being the
area that price Taps into and goes
long and what do we get we get that long
so we get the first scalp
up we get the the first scalp up
that's
here and then we get the long entry here
to take us up
to where it went
here but then
look we might be breaking structure to
the downside maybe with this
Wick so with this Wick coming as low as
it
did we could potentially expect price to
tap back up into either this area or
here sorry why why is this here what is
this for oh I have this stupid thing
on
yeah all right bye
now now we potentially get price to tap
into
either here where it just
tapped
or
here further
up so we'll see if we get a tap into
this and a rejection away from this and
possibly back down but this move up
could have been from this minor
imbalance in here and then we got no
this could be taken to high because we
got a tap on this IM balance and it
pushed up but then we got a double tap
on it it again so we got we have to um
make sure that this isn't the
Candlestick pattern that we usually see
to trade us higher so we would actually
want this to be
broken um to give us some idea that it
could
potentially
um come back down so again remember it's
either the touch of this it could be the
touch of this cuz look at this liquidity
grab
candle
right here pushed up above the wick
traded below
it but then we just got the test of
these three candles so let's see what it
does does it take you up after the test
or does it short and run the lows and we
have a run of the low so then this
rejection
here is the rejection that we were
looking for for it to potentially run
the lows and if this runs this low we
have to see what it does in this area
because this could just be running the
low to come back to the same imbalance
area testing the imbalance again and
then trading higher the same way that
we've been doing the entire time this
morning Taps into the imbalance here
pushes up test the imbalance pushes
further
test the area that's created here with
this pushes
further so now what are we potentially
looking
for potentially an area or a test back
into somewhere
here and if we get the test back into
here we could trade higher but if we
come through this area then we're
dropping because at that point it would
be violating major swing points on this
time
frame because these are major swing
points here here
here here here here
here here so none of the lows were
violated as of yet all of these lows are
still intact so you essentially want to
wait till one of the major swing points
are ran and if that's ran then that
gives you an indication
that price is going to go bearish out of
this whole
area look like a little shank to stab
somebody with but yeah that that's how
you know that price is going to go
bearish out of the area this is
intermediary structure smaller time
frame structure so with all of this this
can easily reverse this can easily be
broken you know like we don't really
test our longer trades off of that
within this area these are just like
little scalps and
stuff that that you could potentially
look to um uh gain some opportunity in
so I'm wondering you have this hidden
snd
here here let's see what price does with
that could continue
through could give us another tap into
this one which would be a double bottom
into to this this area that it already
tapped into and then you would expect
for price to give you a double bottom
somewhere within here in order to take
you back up if we were running the high
so you see how double bottom is a term
that's used in retail Concepts but if
they have rules to it they could be way
more beneficial than trying to get you
to look for double bottoms and double
tops now you're looking for structure
then you're looking for zones and then
you're looking
for the double bottom or the double top
maybe you know within that area you're
not just trading them because you see
them all across the board so yeah um
what do you think about setting up a
limit at the top black line so it's
interesting that you mentioned that um
this is why I don't use limit orders at
all because withit limits I mean I get
it you know limits um you know they help
with the slippage but I don't use limits
because price is tapping into a
particular area if I had put a limit
here and I put my stops behind here or
even if my stops were behind the Zone up
here my stop loss still got
hit if I put a limit
there that's why when it gets there I
want to see what is it doing
here do something for me here that shows
me that you want to come
down do something for me
nothing made her dance
here so she kept
climbing little chaa slide through here
paked you out made you think it was a
equal
High nope ye kept
going and I told you within the equal
High you want an equal High here yes you
want both highs you know close in the
range of each other even if one was
higher than the other you won't both
close in the area of each other
but within this right leg here or right
arm or whatever it's called you want an
equal High to happen within here as
well and then that gives you some
indication that the equal high is going
down like um let me see if I could
find so here with within all within here
you
have this High put in right here then
you have this High put in but then you
still have price just giving you some
sideways shift from this area but all of
this still gives you some indication
that we're potentially um facing some
resistance so we could go back down tap
into an area and then continue up but if
you look there was this equal High
here sorry there was this equal High
here but look when price traded up to
here it gave you this equal high and it
gave you this equal high so now we have
three almost equal
Highs but it's not only three almost
equal highs that we have
it's actually
structure because look at
this the Candlestick pattern that we
like to see is present even if you use
the larger structural one the
Candlestick pattern is here that we like
to
see so because it's here and we like to
see it it's it's what we like to see
we're expecting the runs of
the lows that facilitated this area for
us and we got a run of every single
low that facilitated the area from
this
here we ran every single low along this
trend line we ran it tapped into here
and then
left and this is what I was talking
about in terms of of trend lines yeah
there's people that use use them and and
some of them are profitable but they're
essentially just a storage of of
liquidity essentially that the price
ends up just running
later so you know like that's just
something that that you guys want to pay
attention to with the limit again I'm
not setting a limit here because I want
to see what price does within this area
before I get
involved so you see we just had a run of
this low here we could have a
retracement back up into this area and
then a continuation
down and then this would essentially be
woff and I say that this would be woff
because look at this let me just delete
all of this um maybe to
here
yeah this could essentially be W off
because what would we have if this
was we have the selling climax the
automatic
rally the secondary test the sign of
weakness we
have this could be the UT or or or this
could be the UT within the
area then we have a
utad and then if we put in another sign
of
weakness the other sign of weakness
actually usually comes and runs the low
of the
AR so we could run the low of the AR
coming down into here we can come back
into this area and then that's where the
final short is within this area and then
if you scroll out you'll see according
to you know the the things that we like
to see of
course
you'll
see price flip below this come back into
this area and then leave and what is
that the Candlestick setup that we
usually
have so this is how you anticipate those
moves
forward uh Monty can you just block this
person maybe from the chat or something
like that I don't
know I don't want any sex okay gez get
out out of
here yeah yeah so I I don't know why
these these spam bot hey bro I had to
leave the office so I don't know if you
answer my question earlier um oh yes I
did I did um uh answer the question I
believe it was
um uh
wait oh no I didn't I I didn't see this
um
some oh maybe maybe it was this question
was it the the break oh no no no you I
already got to that the break it was
here okay my bad um at
29800 got me because with that close I
was so sure we were going
lower and and the higher low at
30151 but the price just left to go up
is this something that I missed um so
where where was that again at
29800 uh that's what what time frame is
that the hourly time frame I believe you
said
um oh you're talking about down here
down here you you thought that that with
down here it was going to continue
short
um was sure the market was
going but the price left me to go up is
that just the market being the market or
did I miss something so this was
essentially the pattern
um that I usually teach on the Channel
with
here
this pattern and and the rules um that
are laid out uh for uh this particular
pattern um so you're looking
for
this this looks like it came up
here uh actually let me look and see let
this looks this looks weird I see what
you're saying
um just go down into to the bottom of
it and take a look um okay
so so here's where the different types
of structures come into play we put in
this
low we come up we put in this
High since this is the hourly time frame
you want to see
um you know the the larger
swings but you also want to consider
Candlestick structure so this puts in a
new low
here then trades above comes back in the
area comes back down here so what we
would do here since this is the hourly
time frame I would be using Candlestick
structure um in here I wouldn't be
trading from the hourly I would more so
be trading from from
um you know this this particular time
frame uh the 1 minute time frame but if
I saw that it was an hourly move then I
would understand that but look I talk
about the v-shape recoveries that people
tend to see you see this here
um this is just a liquidity
grab
this so we're down here we're
making you know a this is a a lower low
lower high lower low lower high lower
low and then it just pushes you out of
the area so you're trying to figure out
what exactly happened here because price
didn't trade above it put in a a low it
put in a lower low um but if you look
within
here
down within this
area
here we actually have the same issue
where we look like we're
making the the movements in
price within
here we get a lower high we come into
the area and and then we leave but this
is why I also teach Candlestick
structure because Candlestick structure
would have gotten you into this trade if
the intermediary structure
didn't right here so we begin
to make our Ascension down into the area
when we get to the area we're putting in
a series
of lower lows lower highs we run this
high we trade back into the range of it
and then we
leave but when this happens we need to
make sure on the
hourly this is happening in an area of
interest to the left side so let me
actually check and see where what is
this
um
29700 let's see if there's
any area back here at
so that's
here we have this Gap in here we have
this this candle that pushed down and
pulled up and look price never came back
to mitigate the area so now this is a
likely area to be mitigated because when
price traded above it never came back to
touch it just like the area that you
were faked out on price never came back
to touch touch that area until later on
so all you do is take this area
here you might base your entry
there you might put a stop loss
there
dang this thing is scrolling forever so
look at
this you get a tap on the beginning of
the area or is this the middle of the
area this might be the middle of the
area but this liquidity grab down is
into to the wick of the candle that's
over
there so now it becomes that oh sorry I
don't know what happened there my bad
now it
becomes
that this Wick was manipulation down and
they left this hidden snd Zone
here so now the actual
entry is here at the hidden snd
Zone I don't know what this this this
spam thing uh let me let me see if I can
go and block this um this particular U
page
um
let me just report
them unwanted
spam where
is Amani can you comment in the
chat as well as um aim comment on on
YouTube so I can just give you guys a
um a moderator
role yeah because these things and and
this is what I'm talking about in terms
of the Discord like this will happen
over and over again um in a Discord if
if there aren't those tiers
so um that's essentially why um you know
like we have to switch up the model it's
not going to be the same way we wanted
it to be but um we definitely had to
switch it so look this tapped into the
hidden snd to the left um if if you're
still here um uh Alfredo this tapped
into the hidden snd to the left so the
hidden snd was uh you know IC um no um I
I watched like maybe two of his videos
um I know he knows what he's talking
about but because of like the the little
tangents and some sometimes he goes on
um it's really difficult to um like be
able to
um you know like keep up with some of it
cuz he goes onto his his little Rants
and stuff but he definitely knows what
he's talking about I know that for a
fact like he knows what he's talking
about he understands the algorithm but
some people can't just really keep up
with the the Rants and stuff so um but
he's he's good at what he does yes he is
uh yeah I'm familiar with the
Candlestick structure but I always
believe that Candlestick structure is
most valid on the one hour and above
yeah it it is valid on the it is more
valid on the higher time frames but also
remember we took this area this
liquidity grab towards the left this is
from the same time frame you're trading
from the hourly so I would find an area
of Interest first we tap into the area
of Interest
we go to the lowerer time frames now
that we're in the area of Interest what
are we looking for the same type of
setup to happen here so now that we're
we're in our area we find the liquidity
grab down this is the same liquidity
grab within this area we have price
shift up above this high this last high
that was put in we get a tap into this
area here
here we put our stops right behind
here and then we look
for the hourly move that we find that
that we found this this particular thing
on and whether we think it's coming up
to the imbalance whether we think it's
just going to run the high or whatever
it is we found the area to the left
already we found this area on
um on the charts we found the hidden snd
cuz I told you there's always these
hidden snds that's around that makes us
think that price is going to run the low
because we pay attention to these Wicks
it's like oh yeah if it goes below the
wick then or it might go down and fill
the wick nope ye hit the middle of it
and then just went right
up to it but if you saw it on on your
time frame that you trade on now you
just go to the lower time frame to find
the entry and you have a 32 pip stop and
now you're potentially targeting you
know some some area above here from
finding your entry on the the um the one
minute reflective of the 1 hour and look
then you just
climb and it
becomes a smaller time frame move a
smaller time frame entry with a longer
time frame move and now you're risking
or I would be risking $3,900 to make
$94,000 and that's how the hourly would
play out for me if I was forecasting my
trades from you know beforehand like
from the higher time frames but because
I could see things in every time frame I
really don't you know care much
about um the higher time frames because
I can see everything on the one minute
or or most things I could see on the one
minute um so
yeah look we might be getting that
formation of the Candlestick pattern we
like to
see here
we might be getting that but look we we
almost got it here it looks like we
almost got it
here so what happened with
it and we tapped into this snd and then
started to trade back above we were
actually supposed to run the low first
and then trade above so because this low
was left
intact then we're still looking for it
to continue
because a low wasn't violated on this
time frame we have to have a violation
of the low first and then we pull back
into the area and then go so that's
usually um um the the requirements that
I have for even utilizing a a bullish or
or bearish flip um so hidden snd zones
are basically unmitigated areas yes
that's that's all they are unmitigated
areas but they're hidden the areas that
obviously it's it's not like look this
here this Wick here this is a hidden snd
zone so this may go up and flip the high
soon because of this area here but it
might just be going to tap into this
area if it doesn't hold at this area it
could flip the high but this is
essentially it this one Wick here this
long Wick that you see manipulation cuz
look we have price tap right back into
it and go all this becomes is an snd
Zone
here and all we're getting is our
Candlestick pattern inside of the snd
Zone The Hidden snd
Zone that's all we're getting within
here is this and yeah this could push up
above here come back into the area to
test it and
leave and then go up and potentially run
the high that could possibly happen or
it just just go straight up and run
but we had a hidden Zone and we watch
this happen within our hidden
Zone So within the hidden Zone they're
actually making their me their next move
in here meanwhile you believe not you
but but retail Traders meanwhile we
believe that this is just ranging this
is
consolidation we think that this is
consolidation and guess who looks like
the clown we
do because it's not consolidation I mean
it is consolidation but it's not
consolidation as in like ranging we
can't trade that you should stay out of
areas of consolidation blah blah blah no
anybody who tells you that doesn't know
what they're doing there's no such thing
consolidation tells us the story we need
consolidation to happen in order to tell
us what the next direction is going to
be
and I talk about the Candlestick pattern
happening within this snd if you don't
believe me uh here we go we put in this
low we put in this High we put in this
low we run this high with this
Candlestick we run it we come back into
the area of the area that we violated we
come back into this area and then what
do we do we trade
out and what is it in the hidden area
that we have we have the Candlestick
structure that we like to see and then
if this continues to trade higher or if
it does trade
higher we could have it come back within
the area to test the Candlestick
structure that we put here we could test
it and then leave and create another
high
potentially if this area did not do its
job which I mentioned that we could come
back up to this area um earlier before
all of this
was I think I had mentioned remember it
was
here I said that we got the tap here to
go down but price can return to the area
a second
time so then it could be this candle
that potentially was
hit which that's what it is is this
candle so we have an imbalance between
here so watch it this could be an
imbalance tap only to trade higher or we
can just run through it and come back
down to the untested area here or we can
just run through this area too if this
is not the area that price wants to stop
in you know like there's a bunch of
possibilities with all these different
things all these different time frames
all like a bunch of different
possibilities and this is why I take
time to teach live because I know
everybody else Lolly gags and chats and
talks about all these different things
which I go into my tangents too but they
not give you any real information real
substance for you to take with you when
they log off just like yeah that was a
great chat join the
mentorship okay you know like it's not
really teaching you anything um again
this this teaching I've never seen it
anywhere ever in my life and it's it's
me teaching it so yes I I get that it
sounds bias but I've never seen a
anywhere in my
life anywhere like nobody you know
taught me this nobody like like nothing
at all I've never seen this I've seen
some people teach some of these Concepts
Stand
Alone um but nothing as comprehensive as
as essentially you know what I teach
here nothing as
comprehensive so this area this push
above was just that we hit this
imbalance and had this push up but what
are we having here what do we look like
is going on here right now I told you
when we come up into an area of an equal
High we also want to see an equal High
happen
towards the right side of that area but
we want to watch this because this is an
imbalance here and this is the
Candlestick structure that we like to
see just happen within the imbalance so
this
gives a a little more like areas like
this give a little more hesitancy for me
for take to take a longer trade out
because of that particular thing um is
the Candlestick structure the
engulfing uh or any relevant pattern
tweezer
tops um just confirming that I'm
understanding correctly so the
Candlestick pattern is essentially a
series of highs and lows being created
with just the Wicks of the candles alone
or the bodies of the candles but the
pattern that I'm talking about is
essentially that it's it has rules to it
it has to run a previous high and then
tap back into the area and then
go so I I call it Candlestick structure
Candlestick patterns but it's usually
that um you see correct they give you
motivational speeches but most no
substance yeah exactly it's it's not
nothing nothing behind exactly what it
is that that
um that's like the reason why price does
this or why price does that so you
mention what an imbalance is let me just
take you here um remove some of this
price
action
here
um
yeah that that's that very well could be
it a third trend line touch and then
likely be broken by um the liquidity
yeah that could happen but again since
we're scalping like you know a lot of
the times those quick moves are the
scalps and then the longer move we want
to reassess what that possibly is what
could possibly be happening you know we
just want to reassess that
um let me
actually yeah all
right slim is there okay cool um slim I
just made you a moderator just in case
um you you have those spam stuff coming
through or anybody that gets on your
nerves you could remove them no I'm
kidding but uh yeah I just made you a
moderator just so you can help out with
that I hope that's okay brother um but
an imbalance is between three Wicks I
mean three candles sorry you have this
candle you have this candle and you have
this
candle with this candle here it closes
this candle opens and this candle goes
engulfing up into this
area so you had some buys here that
turned into cells and you had some cells
here that flipped and turned into buys
so between this Wick
here and this Wick here sorry maybe I
could find like a better a better way
to let me just use this between this
Wick
here and this Wick
here
there's this area this gap between
here this this Wick and this Wick
they're not touching from either side so
there's this Gap in between here this
Gap is called the
imbalance or inefficiency or fair value
Gap or IPA whatever they want to call it
it's all the same thing
imbalance so this is an imbalance what
we expect price to do often times with
these imbalances is for price to come
back into this area tap into the area
and then leave or it can just give us a
quick reaction as a scalp maybe a
long-term move whatever it is so we take
this entire area
from this Wick to this
Wick let me actually just do
this we take this area here and we're
expecting price to tap back back into
this area and then give us a trade
coming out of it the first tap usually
is a scalp the second tap is the longer
move and by tap I mean it Taps into the
area and pushes
out and then my band button is up and
running and then we tap into the area
and we push out but then we can come
back to the area second time and then
leave again so I don't know if this
imbalance was tapped I didn't check it
um so you see how we tap into this
imbalance and we
leave we don't hit the 50% of this area
at all I don't know if we end no we we
don't hit it at all so we still have an
imbalance within this area here that
price could potentially tap onto which
would also be a second entry because
this tapped into the imbalance but it
didn't hit the 50% so price can come
back down here and tap again into this
area and then end up taking you up so
all you really do
is you
take this area
here and uh this area
here and now you're expecting price to
potentially tap in here and give you
another move up where that move is going
it could potentially run the high or it
can just be coming back into another
imbalance above or another Zone above
that's unmitigated before trading
lower so this is what an imbalance
is it's price moved quickly out of the
area and it wasn't able to fill all of
the buy orders pushing up it wasn't able
to to fill it with the demand of or or
or the supply at least of the sell
orders coming
out so we got sell orders coming back to
fill
these this this imbalance but we didn't
get enough of it we want at least 50% or
even down into 90% before leaving
because if you don't have a seller then
you don't have a buyer you don't have a
buyer you don't have a seller so it's
supply and demand essentially that's all
the the market runs on is supply and
demand so if you look if you look up
here we talked
about which candle was it was it this
candle here or was it this
candle here oh no it was this one I'm
tripping so we talked about getting the
equal high but we want to see an equal
High happen on one side of the
high right
here we have the equal High
but we want to see an equal High here
created and then price shifted away and
tested that equal high and then that's
where the long is I mean the short sorry
but the longer move that's where the
longer move potentially heads to so if
you see
this if you see this as it happens I I
mentioned this when price tapped here I
said you want to see an equal high in
this area and then price shorted out of
the area um but I went to obviously
explaining something um so you you got
this you got to tap up into this area
you got a shift
away you got a tap back up into the area
again and then we made an equal high
around the entry so then we left we ran
the low of we ran the first low of the
equal high but then we tapped back into
the region of the equal high and then
now what we run the second
low and where do we
tap this imbalance
again but I want a further Mitigation Of
The imbalance at
least you're welcome brother you're
welcome
so um we have this low put
in we have the Run of this
High we come back into this area and
let's see if we make our way above it
did we cross a low no we didn't cross
the low of this snd
here so we tapped into this area we
would need a run of
this a run of this High here in order to
maybe tuck back into this area and
potentially long for
him let me see
yeah he's so
crazy all right let me
uh there you go yeah all right got you
um so yeah you know like it's it's the
same rules over and over um again same
thing over and over and over and over
and over and over and over
and again over and over and over again
and again if you learn this you will
never ever need anyone to trade again
ever you will
never ever need anyone in your life to
help you to trade again you will never
need to watch another trading video now
I still watch trading videos of other
people teaching like I was watching tra
track effects the other day because I
don't ever think that I've topped out in
knowing enough and there might be
something very slight within their
technique that I might be able to
utilize for myself you know but I just I
I still watch videos even though I know
that this like my style of trading is
all that in a bag of chips you bring any
other Trader to me and we rival at it we
can trade for charity we can be like hey
you know we start with x amount and
whatever we come up with we trade for
charity and I will blow them out of the
water because I know a fact how sure my
setup is but I'm also not saying that I
can't learn anything from them because I
can learn something else from their
particular trading style I don't doubt
that at all you know I I definitely
can so you I'm not pompous or anything
like that in that sense look this this
tap right here was the the test of this
area
here the test of this area
area that's the tap that you get hold on
real quick
guys sorry just checking on the kids um
I wonder is my latency
to
too
much let me see let me put my hand up
one two three four all right four five
seconds that's
fine um yeah so so we got to tap into
this area and we pushed up
above now look at
this this is the last high this is the
last
low here we tap into this area and what
we probably come up to this here if not
this then up here and if we make it past
this then we could potentially be
trading higher because the areas up here
are already
mitigated um are you in any trades at
the moment no I I usually just teach
most times um when when I'm doing this
because um teaching you guys definitely
need some undivided attention or else
the quality of the teaching won't be so
great if I was trading obviously I'm
paying attention into my money in the
market you know I want to make sure that
it's not doing anything that that is not
supposed to um but look you have yeah
you have this High Here We Dro in this
low so we would have to come above this
high if we were continuing higher
members section at least here um you
could actually just tap into hey armoney
you can actually just tap into uh this
area here um you know click on that and
then just oh damn it put my phone number
out there I don't care uh but yeah it
just Taps into to that area
there so um you can do that and and just
reach out to me personal message me I'm
fine with it no problem um and we can
chat from there but yeah that that's the
analysis that I have on um uh gold uh
and we'll just see if that if that
actually plays
out
look at
this so you see how we had this
tap came up tapped further into the area
went into the
low and then broke the high
here so we R trce down some let's see
what happens within this area do we get
a tap out of this
imbalance
do we get a tap within this imbalance to
take us back up and deliver us
to you know some of these areas above it
it could very well just be this area
here cuz this is a mitigated
here this is an unmitigated area here um
and we have one just directly above it
and then we
[Music]
have this
sorry yeah this was already
mitigated so we still have this area
above of T if price tries to make its
way back up um but if it crosses this
area
then there's a possibility that we're
running the
high
but you see how this is diverging now or
converging whatever they call
it this is making lower
highs um but this is also price is
bouncing up between these
areas you know high low and it's coming
closer and closer together with the
highs and lows that it's making so they
usually um with retail Traders they'll
have a high here and they'll be like
okay sell here and it's going to go
out and then there are other people who
view the market and they're like okay if
this TAPS in first and retests this
area you buy
here and then you potentially sell out
so both people are viewing the markets
in different ways taking different
trades this guy is going going to
here for a quick
scalp this guy is going to here for a
quick Scout so we have a lot of activity
happening within here then you have the
conservative traders who want to see it
come out of the
area tap back into the area and
leave and then you have the other people
who want to see it drop out of the area
tap back into the area and go
so there's a lot of anticipation
followed by a lot of volume that could
potentially happen within this area
because all of these different things
that are here buy Stops Here Sell stops
here buy limits Here Sell limits here
stop loss behind here to sell down into
here stop loss behind here to buy up
into here there's a lot of stuff
happening within this area
here because you see price
converging
and one
of these Traders are
right some are impulsive and are going
to be
wrong some
are right and are going to walk away
with some profit today some are going to
blow their
accounts but nonetheless this is all of
the engagement in the market this is how
everybody's
playing to there two there two there two
there and they're playing with these
patterns and for other
Traders they are
essentially waiting for structure to
show us what it's going to do because as
far as structure is concerned it's
making higher
highs I mean sorry it's making higher
lows but it's also making lower highs as
well
so both people are viewing the market
and not really understanding what's
actually
happening and this is
where we're trying to make some sense of
it we'd end up being in the middle of
the
market so we fell out of this SN after
we failed to make a new high we crashed
through the snd so this snd no longer
matters this doesn't matter you still
have this snd above and you still
have this imbalance here below with this
snd down here so you want to look at
what price potentially does within this
area in order to potentially run this
there's liquidity here this is trend
line
liquidity here some here some extending
even up here going into down here
so this is but this is why you want to
pay attention to when these are
happening here I gave you guys the rules
to this what did I say I said that if we
run this High we can go bullish but if
we run this High
here if we run this High since we put in
this low and ran this High we're looking
for the retracement back into the area
and then we
go
and look we just double tapped within
this this region up here and got
rejected
out so these these have rules to them as
well you know you're you're not just
taking it because you see this pattern
on the bottom side you're looking to see
if there was any shifting in price that
happened in this entire area here
what happened we put in a low we ran the
last High we retraced back into the area
and then we
left it's the same thing over and over
and over again so it's in those videos
um the you if you guys take time to just
learn that stuff I promise you you guys
would never need me again you guys would
never come back to this channel you guys
might unsubscribe because it may be too
many notifications or whatever it is
like that's how it
it is you know so so you guys if you
take a look at that like it would
definitely help you guys like
immensely greatly help you guys you know
so um I just want you guys to consider
that