all right so look at this right here
um look at this right
here this Candlestick pattern that we
always talk about look we came back into
this area this is the snd responsible
for the break above but what do we have
inside of here we have an
imbalance so that's where we got to tap
same thing
here
imbalance we get this TA down we come
into this area here because this is the
area where we flipped pushed up to here
came back down to this area and then
ended up taking it
above
so imbalance to Zone to look this
Candlestick formation that we talked
about happened on the downside here look
at it happening up here
but this could just be coming down to
this Wick and then pushing up or this
could be trading lower to the actual
sndd here that's responsible for this
break so let's see are we touching
here don't worry I'll do the top down in
a few guys
um want some other people to come in oh
my coffee that's right ch you right my
coffee I think that's what happens I
think I got to get up and have coffee
earlier that could be
it sorry about that guys
um I can't hear the music on my end but
you're good oh that's because I turned
it down here let me bring it back up
some
yeah should be able to hear it now
slim you crazy for that I think I was
muted when I laughed at
that yeah yeah remember we learned 30
times faster on the one
minute so look this could be coming up
into this area and rejecting
out we could potentially have this type
of rejection out of
here before actually leaving or maybe we
tapped into this snd here that gave us a
strong enough push up but it didn't tap
into the middle so I'm still a little
wary of
[Music]
it come on people where are those likes
that's funny no um I guess the emphasis
on liking and sharing and all that other
stuff is is High um for any YouTuber
really um but I'm not really looking to
get paid from YouTube um and monetize on
YouTube views it's more money in Forex
than there is in
YouTube so um people like it people
don't have to whatever it doesn't matter
to me
um this could be running this High yeah
and coming back down into here maybe
feel the imbalance maybe
not but we came up into here
tapped up into that area
there and this is what I love about um
you know these plays at
least because um if you ever end up in
any type of draw down from from where
some of these entries are you know like
let's say you thought it was shorting
here and you end up pushing up here
ended up what 20 Pips and dra on it so
it still came back to the entry um here
maybe you know one pip less um but it
still came back to the entry allowed you
to get out and then flip your
bias so I'm to top down in a few um good
morning thank you for blessing us with
your knowledge once again you're welcome
Walter you know I was looking at
something interest in
um with uh YouTube the demographics of
people that watch and it seems like most
of the people that watch are between 25
and 35 and then there's that 35 to 45
age bracket that you know I only have a
very small portion of viewers with and
then the people underneath the 25 age
bracket it's just like 6% so it seems
like it's the Millennials that you know
I'm really just stuck within that crowd
I mean I'm Millennial too you know it's
probably just the same beliefs that we
have and
stuff um so this could have been tapping
into here because of this here so there
was this low put
in this High put in
and if you
look when price ran out of the area
right across
here when price came out of this area
here let me fatten that up for you guys
when price came out of this area
here when it traded below this area and
the low of this area it never came back
in so although a wick came out and then
came back up I always talk about there
being second rejections when it returns
to an area that it quickly traded away
from so we got the quick trade away from
the area with this
pullback we come back into the area
again we get a rejection from this area
back
down why because when a body closes
below the area and then comes back into
the area
area often times that's the touch you
want to see but sometimes there's a wick
that could pull out of the area and come
back in and then take you short and
later on when price returns there again
there's usually another rejection
waiting so that's more than likely um
you know what took place in here but it
looks like
um you know there's
some well we ran this low here here so
after running this
low here we have this high as well up
above here but because this High pushed
up and came tuck and tucked back into
the range of it price could
react here exactly where it's reacting
now because of
um the uh this Wick went Above This high
and traded back inside of
it so the reaction you expect is from
the body of the candle rather than the
wick price could still make its way back
up here to this Wick because this is a
hidden snd Zone that they left above but
we saw the rejection from
here because if you take the low and you
take this body right here you measure
that out price came back into this area
tapped in and then rejected away
so when now now what I'm expecting is
potentially the Run of this low maybe
come back into this area and then short
that could be a possibility or it could
be a second tap on this imbalance and
then price takes the
highs because if it goes above this High
here this high and this High they're
already mitigated I mean they have small
snd zones well this one was mitigated
this one has a small snd Zone on top of
it but that potentially so see we just
got the run of the the
low we got the run of the low
here I'm going to do the top down in a
few I'm going to spend probably like an
extra 45 minutes or so on here because
of the uh technical
difficulties um I want to make sure I'm
not too loud for you guys am I
loud look we got the top of this snd
Zone
here we'll just see what happens around
here mind you when we're looking for a
reversal so the top is the scalp and
when we're looking for a reversal we're
looking for a return back to this area
and consolidate so the top is always the
first scalp up which if we tapped here
and we pushed up here it's about 14 Pips
or so just on a
top wow I wonder if I'm getting
allergies so look we went below this
low now we can come back up into this
area or even up into this area
here and we'll wait to see what we get
up here but we could possibly get a
rejection and then when we ran this slow
so maybe somewhere within here it comes
up to or maybe up into the hidden snd
that was left behind because we already
got this rejection from here down to
here but you see how this becomes so
easy we mentioned this rejection here
when this green candle was up in here
and we had said okay this is probably
rejecting out of this area from here
because this Wick is manipulation you
don't count the wick
and then look we get the short from
there to
here it could have been a potential
short from here but price ran through it
and just came to this area
here and we got the wick
rejection and then we push back up this
could be a fractal that it's rejecting
off of to come back down to here I can
test this area again and then pull back
up to here maybe to test this area up
here maybe reject back down run the lows
possibly into this snd then tap this snd
and then take the highest possibilities
it's just if if this is how if this is
what I'm anticipating price to to do
then I'm looking to get involved in
those different types of movements so
you see I said we just rejected from the
fractal when coming down here there's
this snd here that's not fully mitigated
this one did get mitigated but we can
get a double tap in this area and then
start to look to go for some of the
highs maybe within this area or this
area up here or price is going just
short right through here and come down
to here you just got to always keep that
possibility
open
yeah
let's see I'm going to do the top down
in uh five minutes or
so um I hope that's okay with you
guys
look we got this tap here spring up to
here we come down
here now we want to look and see if we
get some sideways movement within this
region to give us some signal that it
could be
reversing but we could get a tap into
this snd here
and I'm wondering if we tap down into
this
snd if we'd end up coming above this to
hit this area after maybe come back down
into this area and then possibly look to
take the highs and it'll look like that
Candlestick pattern that I usually tell
you guys about it's a
possibility this is a double tap on the
imbalance right here so it could very
well be the imbalance that does
that then you want to see a flip above
here price come back into the area
here and
then potentially look to take this High
here
possibilities again we still have this
area
here just below
it it's just hypothesizing this is
wouldn't be a a trade that I would be in
or
anything unless it showed me those
rules
trying to be an
artist so what we get to tap back into
this
area and then what are we going to do
here we got a equal high right here on
Candlestick
structure see
that so let's see if it then puts in the
low and then runs this
high
and if you guys have any charts any
tickers you want me to look at I'll
definitely take a look at it for you
guys look at that see even on
Candlestick structure equal High Here We
Run not this low not only this low but
we run the second low too responsible
for the equal High I'm telling you you
see this stuff everywhere EU
um I think I did some work on EU
yesterday
um was
it yeah probably did let me go to what
what time frame do you
want oh yeah look I did
have something
here
where it tapped
into I don't remember what this is so
don't quote
me
uh oh one minute okay um so let me look
at the 15 minute right
now uh we came up into this we got a
rejection from this imbalance
we mitigated this entire area but this
looks like it could be coming
here it going be coming up to here and
possibly
um get
rejected from here
um let me
see uh
could go like
this could do that even even up until
this Wick even could do that as well but
this is an imbalance rejection I
believe yeah this is a rejection at the
imbalance so you could have a second tap
up into the imbalance and then a short
from it um or you could just be shorting
from this so both of these lines that
are already here are uh perfect for that
it's here or here 53 54 one of those
um yeah that's what I'm thinking we ran
both of these highs
already
uh yeah so the Run of this High could
facilitate back into here somewhere and
then another push above but let me look
at the one minute
now
so there's a minor imbalance in
here
uh so it could be between these two
areas
here could be between this area here um
the only thing you want to be
considerate of is um let me actually
see uh so we got the imbalance here we
got the snd above here there's this
other imbalance inside of
here which I don't really see
we lingered around here
fell I don't really see that this
imbalance is important but it could
be um because
of could form an equal High when it gets
up here and then end up running the
low um which would make it consistent
with
this tap up into the area run the low
potentially get a along
from down
here to take you up
further let me
see slight imbalance
here yeah so just watch this area
here
um very minor minor
imbalance and I mean even if it's minor
it's still an imbalance
um and then you also have one down
here so this is just after you see a
rejection and then you see a bearish
flip that happens up here this is when
you want to look to potentially get out
of here get out of along here maybe
somewhere up within this region only if
you see a bearish flip if you don't see
a bearish flip you're not getting out
you're taking this bad boy wherever it's
going so um if you see that um and you
get a rejection from up here the
rejection can possibly come to the
downside of
here
here or
here or here
sorry
so save these areas for later because
later on you might actually have price
come back to these areas and still give
you a reaction off of them um what is
that 105
353 uh 105 353 this is just an
imbalance I believe from the higher time
frame which time frame was I just on the
minute uh no that's not that's this snd
Zone
here yeah that's this snd Zone here so
you see I would just push through
that and it hit the imbalance that's in
here yeah this was a little tiny
imbalance that we said was in here you
see why imbalances are more important
than than zones at least for me you know
other people may
um think something differently but um
then you have a minor imbalance in here
so watch it that's where price could
potentially tap find support and push
you back up and then you can get your
equal high up here possibly where the
equal high will facilitate the
um the run of the
lows so yeah you just want to um pay
attention to that
um let me see Torres what's up how's
everything
uh hey Dave the EA teacher why going up
I didn't miss the top down no you didn't
miss the top down yet actually I'm like
five minutes late six minutes now on the
top down cuz I was uh looking at EU my
bad um see look at what I was saying
guys about this rejection
here
you see what I was
saying I said we can tap back into this
area but look we didn't even get the tap
we did get the flip though cuz look we
flipped Above This equal
High yeah I'm telling you guys this is
like sauce sauce sauce man we flipped
Above This equal High here we pushed
above it with this green candle this red
candle tapped us back into this
area and then took us out
out to go above to
where the areas above that I mentioned
we
had and we even tapped into the hidden
snd Zone that's
here so this is exactly what I'm talking
about like I I mentioned that it could
possibly do that and I said we could
possibly run this High remember I put a
circle around it I said we could
potentially dip back in here come up
above this high and then have a
retracement back in what broke this high
this snd down here within this region so
you can get a tap into this region and
then get a long out of it to potentially
take the highs but be careful because
this could be the Candlestick pattern
that we always talk about
here this could very well be a beish
flip look we ran under this
low we came up
we violated the low we
retraced and this could essentially take
us further down into this area
here
um all of this is mitigated here
underneath this is mitigated down
here I mean there is this little snd
that's unmitigated here but I don't
really see price taing into it and
taking out a high cuz it's pretty
small
um and even with this
here we didn't run this High
first so if we ran this High came back
into this area and then longed from it
then I would
understand there's still some
um let me just go to the higher time let
me do the top down now let me stop
wasting
time trying to analyze on on my time
frame let me just give you guys a top
down um 6:30
so this is probably about 25 Pips in
difference but we're doing the top down
for the well let me just find something
that's that's easier um to use because I
hate destroying my history of things but
I guess if I do this every day the
history shouldn't matter
right
yeah all right let's get the top down in
Armani um last night when I had
mentioned a double tap of the imbalance
um right here I think we were on the 15
minute it might have been
let me just show
you remember guys all of this here could
be a violation of this low here we
dropped below we violated this low we
came back up to the snd that was
responsible for violating the low so we
came back up this could very well
continue short below this area here
below the 200 area down into somewhere
within this area
here you know this this could very well
do that so um just be careful of this
area um let me go to the
Daily uh
let's here we go go a fresh chart let's
go ah here we go so
um we have this High
here that seems to be looking like a
protected High look at that Candlestick
pattern that we like to talk about here
possibly forming possibly you have the
same thing down on this side
too and you have the same thing up
here and if you look up here there was a
short provided if you look up here there
was a long provided back up into this
area which we had talked about this area
potentially being the target when we
were just down here so we got up into
this area surprised we didn't run this
High here
though and if we result in running that
high we may also look to run this
one so these are the same areas that I
had before
um this is
143 this is
970 1043 my bad and this is
814 so we also have some areas down
below
here which
is this here and I'm I'm guessing that
just a guess don't quote me on it I'm
guessing that this is the um protected
low yeah I'm guessing that this is a
protected
low um let's
see did we mitigate this by at least
50%
we came close to it but not
much this may be indicating a bearish
day uh let me go to the 4
[Music]
Hour oh look at this
yikes but look at this also
below this is something that you want to
pay attention
to I mentioned yesterday that these are
hidden
snds so we have this area just
above
here
and then we also have the beginning of
the
area because price Taps on the beginning
of these Wicks sometimes and then pushes
up off of it so you just want to make
sure you note
that
um and let's go to the hourly now let's
take a look at what's in the hourly oh
okay we have an equal High here inside
of an snd above here I think uh this
was aim or Armani I think it was that
had mentioned that we were coming back
up to um this snd
above this one right
here see that
see how we got the mitigation
of the tap
here now this could be a wick fill that
these people be talking
about but
uh ah look at that look at that look at
the Candlestick pattern we like to see I
like that inside of a Zone
too I like that I like that for
shorts this
here so we look like we're shorting
certainly um we could have a run of this
low
first and then
um have price pushed back in before
leaving the area back down so just watch
it if we run this low um just be mindful
of
that uh go down to the
five see anything on the
five
um so we have the areas Above and Below
guys um on the top down I don't know if
I went through that too fast if you guys
want me to go back and you know just
give you the areas I can do that
too
um minor imbalance inside of here makes
this area probable area to Target Bounce
from this imbalance here was filled
already so you disregard that unless
there's a second imbalance touch that's
going to happen here and then push price
further so it looks like yeah we're
shorting down to
488 another imbalance in between here
just above this Zone but then there's
also one in here so this is what you
want to pay attention to this was
completely filled
so it could be the second Touch of
this there's a slight imbalance within
here this one I don't really see this
doing anything U but this one there's a
possibility I could tap
into so again we could still have the
pushes back up retracement into this
area then continuation down you know
like you could still get all of that um
and you usually get them from uh snds
zones or from
um from imbalances I've seen some
imbalances break highs and lows like
give you new highs and lows so um that's
something that you want to consider look
there's a tap of the center of this
imbalance and then price starts to push
back up this could either you know just
be creating this Wick next candle opens
maybe retraces below comes back in to
fill this imbalance and then leave
possibility this is a FIV minute chart
so that could happen over the next 40
minutes or
so
um now we want to see are we going to
get a flip of this
[Music]
high and mind you guys that that was the
um top down um that I did that's overall
um and then when I come down to the one
minute what I'm usually teaching is the
movements of the
algorithm so if this if this does come
back above this more than likely it
would be coming back to tap into um the
imbalance that's
here that's
here did this get
any play yeah did there
it didn't
there so we could have a touchdown into
this and then I'm push up from
here or again we could just end up
running the low and then the low is
where we have that excitatory pushup we
got a minor imbalance within here I told
you I'm going to imbalance you guys to
death so you understand how how
important these areas
are and I've I've you know done many
many many like whenever I introduce
something to you guys I've done many
many many many hours of of going back
over it and and looking at you know it I
I would say
that you know I found it about
imbalances like what
maybe I don't know was it last week or
something can't remember it was track
effects teaching it um
find out about it then
and like I just see how powerful it is
back testing it and I back tested it for
probably about I don't know 40 hours or
so um and it's interesting because you
see I said I back tested it 40 hours
people and forward tested it but um
people tend to put that time into a job
so to have an extra 40 hours to do
something outside of the job can be
taxing for them so that's why I do it I
know when my friends are struggling
trading Forex I was trying to figure out
the ways that they were trading and just
tried to make it better look this could
be a double bottom within this area here
on a lower time frame so this could
facilitate the break of this
above right
here or maybe
not I know um there was one earlier
uh I don't remember what time frame I
was
on
um it was one of these time oh it's this
one here wait was it no I wasn't
streaming when I mentioned it it was
here right
here this is a double
bottom on a lower time frame you have
this push down push back up you have
this down again right here and then you
have the pushup and mind you I'm not
saying double bottom double top as in
like retail patterns it's more just a
double tap in the same
area so look you see how we got the tap
of this we never made it above this high
this is why the tap is always the scalp
and the structural break above is the
long longer move when it comes back
down so the structural break above will
tap into maybe the imbalance imbalance
would form the pullback then the
pullback would be facilitated by coming
into an snd and then it'll be sent above
the imbalance and that's how it usually
forms like look at right
here we have this low put in
we have this higher R tapped into this
imbalance we have a low put in again we
got the double tap on the imbalance to
the left so that facilitated the
pullback we tapped into this snd here
that facilitated the push out of the
area and the reason why you're expecting
it to come out of this area is because
this imbalance is already
mitigated and this snd here was
mitigated as
well so when you get this tap you're
looking for a clean tap to come out of
this area and just come straight up to
the next area what's the next area the
imbalance in here and the snd here this
is an area here too this hidden snd but
it's small so it could obviously easily
be broken but this imbalance here would
have been the next area and that would
have been directly from here to
here quick scalp two minutes got you 95
Pips if you just noticed that this this
flip what's responsible for causing
these pullbacks if you just notice that
that could help you with in terms of
your trading and look even even so let's
say you get a structural flip above the
area now you come in you come back into
the area a second time I told you price
can come back to your area a second time
it can give you a second entry usually
this one could have been the scalp up
which is 90 pip scalp up insane and then
this one is the second entry here that
takes you up to the snd that we actually
get a rejection from we get rejected out
of it then we put in an equal High which
usually results in the Run of not just
this low but this low here
too if you have those principles I'm I'm
I think I was going to write to you guys
I meant to um write to you guys
yesterday that the key to your next
level in life is just understanding this
understanding the why of
this understanding the why of this that
why makes it so much more powerful for
you to trade makes it so much more
powerful for you to you know like hold
your emotions in a trade so you know if
you get that you've you've gotten the
key to your next level in life and
that's why I put an emphasis on that
repetition is the mother of learning we
teach children not only discipline but
we teach them discipline through routine
routine always will be the thing thing
that sharpens anything that you do
anything routine is it so that's just
something that you guys want to consider
um you know when trading again we get
this equal High out of this area as I
mentioned but there's there's rules to
the equal High look there's an
unmitigated area right up here this area
here I don't know what happened
here because this candle closed up here
at
7:01 but then it opened up up here at
720 but clearly this is manipulation
this was supposed to be like a huge Wick
or something up you know it ended up
just gapping up and coming back down but
um this is a gap fill right here this is
also the mitigation of an snd or a
bearish order block up here
so there's rules to all of this it's not
jumping in just because you see a equal
high or you see a equal low there's
rules to it and then when we talk about
the head and shoulders patterns you know
that that people use I always talk about
it because I see it all the time I can't
unsee it but look you have this here you
have
maybe I don't know would you have used
this High here
maybe we tuck back into the this
area and then we push up here maybe
they're looking at this little slanted
function as like the next the neckline
break or
something and then you get in for a long
here targeting whatever up here and look
you get dragged back down here that's
why you don't want to trade these
patterns um unless there's structure
involved in
it but yeah we get that top and we come
down into this area and then what do we
we come to we come into this area
here right
here is this filling the imbalance I
don't know could continue down we did
have what was this lower area here 488
what did we say was was here on the top
down I can't even
remember
[Music]
um oh but this is still equal highs from
a higher time frame so 428 is look we're
looking for potentially a bounce here
here there could be a bounce back up
into this area and then you leave out of
it it can come back up into like
somewhere around here somewhere around
the 600 area and then continue down or
it can just continue down from here but
this is the area that we said we were
shorting
to this is why the top down is so
important for you guys like I continue
to talk about the top down all the time
even though I'm like putting all of
these different areas here talking to
you about what could potentially happen
the top down still is like the ruler of
everything that's whether we're going
for some highs above that's whether
we're coming below it's the ruler of
everything and that's you know kind of
what what I want to get you guys to um
to
understand so if you look at here um on
the one minute we got a double tap
within this
area so this could just be looking to
come up to like an imbalance or
something like that that's up here
before oh this was the the the imbalance
rejection right
here um that I just I forgot who A was
it chain okay yeah this was the
imbalance rejection right here
596 and look at this back down 26 Pips
in 11
minutes on a pair
um EA teacher can you do I love that
name EA teacher
uh Nas 100 okay um Nas is doing the same
thing as us30 shorting down um if we
want me to go to like the hourly maybe
um just take a look at this so the us30
we put equal highs on the hourly but on
the nas we went higher than the previous
high so
um I wonder if the NASA is doing good
but the us30 is doing bad look we have
the break of a high on on this as well
but we came very far into this area
after running this high
so uh this looks like it could still be
coming down um this was an imbalance tap
to take us up the imbalance gave us the
run up the high but it's a wick of
course not a break of structure so we
have this area here we have a equal High
inside of an snd
um we have this snd below
here we have this snd below so Nas could
be coming down to this here oh is this n
this is this isn't even
n my bad so look this is
exactly this is mitigated this this
mitigated this
area this this candle here on the US 500
this area is not
mitigated and on the us30 this area is
not mitigated look we just made it to
our 488 area woo TP smash guys right
yay I don't know why people do
that uh cuz I could just call another
one let me
see yep we mitigated this hit an snd
here too uh did we really
uh let me see we traded
above came back in tapped into the area
could get a double tap within this area
um so Nas could be coming back to this
area um
11581 if it's not coming back there
then I mean if it if it runs this low I
really don't see anything else down here
um that NZ
could find support on because you
already have this
um this double
bottom entry up into this area then you
get this double
top so it can come here and potentially
go back up or it can just run these lows
and come back down to this area here and
that's just from the hourly time frame
um so yeah yeah it could potentially be
that let me look at a lower time frame
15 minutes see what we're doing here so
we have this little Candlestick pattern
that we like to see
here
um we have this area
here and then we still have the 581 area
but looks like we also have an area here
at
546 so maybe we get a
mitigation down into this
area and if the mitigation holds within
this area we could potentially be
looking to give another
high
because we have we have an equal High
here but if we find a strong enough area
to tap
into and then we go long from there wait
so there's this area down
here oh but that that doesn't matter
because price gave us a new
high so it was imbalance to new
High this is why I'm going to imbalance
the hell out of you guys because this is
very very powerful to use so we
imbalance to the new high we could have
a second tap within the imbalance and
then take us up or it can just run this
area remember if it runs this area
then it ends
up so see look where're where this is
the range that we're in between let me
show you
guys we're in this range
here
this whole
range this is the last low and the last
high that was put in So within this
range as I mentioned price can do
whatever it wants go up to the top of
the range come all the way back down to
the bottom of the range come back to the
midl range it can do all of that
um if this does run this low though if
this does run this low here I'll have it
potentially coming back up to this area
here um the 640 area and then continuing
short down to here um if it does run
this
low that's kind of what I have but you
want to pay attention to um the S&P 500
as well you wouldn't pay attention to
this because they correlate heavy um Nas
and the S&P 500 so um you just want to
look at that um and if you look at that
it'll give you some indication on how to
um
like when to get out on certain
reversals or or whatever it is like it
it would definitely help with that this
is trend line liquidity so this could
potentially all be ran down into like an
area down
here this imbalance was filled there's a
small imbalance in
here so yeah this could tap into an
imbalance above come back back here and
then potentially give you a rise back up
into this area
here
uh this could be coming back to this snd
here because structure is just broke
here let's see uh uh uh uh uh so this
broke
structure gave us a run of this High
came back down so yeah we could
potentially be going up to this area
here for the S&P we could potentially be
coming up to this area and continuing
short but if we come up to this area we
flicker Above This high and then come
back in it could just be a retracement
to go
long
yeah
so look we got this tap into here we got
a
run of the high here we could get a tap
back
into well no we got to tap into the area
just now so now this could look to go
and take some of the
highs and this is the S&P so Nas and
us30 could correlate with this if this
is happening but if this is happening
Happ in then this would essentially be
my little Candlestick pattern that I
talk to you guys about all the time
here I got to find a way
to do something with
that like Market that because it's super
super powerful look this is the snd that
broke this High here that's why we
tapped into this and potentially pushing
out of there so
if you look at the us30 and N we didn't
get the break above that high but we did
get it on Candlestick
structure so you want to watch this area
because this could be a double bottom
area too and is this a double bottom
within an area of
Interest oh look at that bad boy come on
guys look at that bad
boy oh oh man
wow I hope you guys are like really
taking this all in like this is great
information to like to learn from like
wow and and I'm teaching myself too as
well the the imbalance okay the term
imbalance the term imbalance is
imbalance is always between three C C
Les there's this one candle here with
the wick that you
see there's this longer candle here this
red candle going up and then there's
this green candle right
here
so what happens with this usually is
between this Wick here and this Wick
here there's no candles on either side
no Wick no bodies on either side so this
entire area here is considered an
imbalance price moved too fast going
down to capture the to to balance the
cells coming out of the area with
potential buys coming into this area so
because you have that huge push out of
the area we created what's known as an
imbalance or
inefficiency or ICT calls it fair value
Gap somebody else calls it like IPA
something there's all these different
names for it I just prefer imbalance um
but it's the same concept so this area
here has a group of of orders of of you
know cells that were waiting to be
filled or or that has to be filled to
rebalance the market if you have sellers
you need buyers to fill the orders of
those sellers that's supply and demand
period you know so um what you're
looking for usually is a tap into the
imbalance and often times it's within
the middle of the imbalance that you get
the top right here within the middle of
the
imbalance so if you get the top within
the middle of this imbalance often times
price would come up tap in reject away
and then you may get another tap and
that other tap may even come through the
imbalance and then you see that double
top that's there and then you you can
take that one out the area for a short
you can take this first one here you can
take that for a scalp a scalp out of the
area the second one when it returns here
sorry I'm just like messing up this
whole thing the second one when it
returns
here you look within this area and this
is where you want to see the bearish
flip you want to see high the highs put
in lows High put in We Run The Low we
come back to balance the area there
could be an imbalance in there too and
then we short out of the area for a
longer hole down into somewhere within
you know an area where we begin to see a
high put in a low put in the high ran a
low brought back into the area and then
out of the area so it always look like
that that's the reversal signal it's a
sign of it reversing for us
this happens this particular formation
now it doesn't always look that way well
it it often looks that way if you have
the rules of this High being broken and
this low being broken if you have those
rules it it always looks that way it
just looks larger or it looks smaller or
it looks like very tiny candles you
could find it in different ways but
that's what you're looking for at the
second entry of an
imbalance at the first one it's always a
quick scalp out of of the area but the
quick scalp sometimes can just turn into
a longer move like you see this here
this is a quick scalp coming from this
area but if you look to the left you're
in you're in an area already a a
um a a supply area or an order block or
or whatever it is you want to call this
area you're in this point of interest
already so because it tapped this is
just the double top to your point of
Interest and then you short coming out
of the area so you find the point of
interest you get the scalp first it
returns to the area and then you short
out of the area but you short with rules
what are the rules so look we have this
Candlestick structure I don't know if
this this actually um went there I'm I'm
just guessing not guessing really but
I'm just utilizing
the Candlestick
structure so this is a Candlestick short
or or a Candlestick break we put in this
high and then we ran the low actually no
I'm actually tripping um because this
High happened
before this low was put
in so this this was it you got a low
here you got a high here you got a
fractal
low high here this candle opened up and
continued up then the low that we run is
this one here we run it with this candle
so now that we run this low we have this
entire range through here sorry this
looks really ugly I'm sorry about that
guys we have this entire range through
here yeah it just looks bad it looks
like a broken leg or like somebody bone
leged up there sorry I'm just very
particular about things but we we come
back into this area here look at this
we come back into this area between this
low and this High We tap back into this
area and we leave but remember what I
said about
manipulations I said that we don't count
the wick so we didn't count the wick Bao
our entry is right
there
beep deep gone tap
gone out of here bye-bye no draw
down and this is the first entry here
stops behind here this is the second
entry here stops behind here and you
found two entries to take price down all
from a POI that you were trading
from and that's essentially what I try
to you know get people to um essentially
learn on the channel I get we have this
double tap within this
area right here but we end up not going
anywhere what do we have
here we have price within this area we
made an equal High here that brought us
back down
to this area here so we tapped into this
area let's say you got a quick scalp up
here up into this area here it's 30
Pips now if you saw a double top forming
again within this area here a double top
forming again all of this is within an
imbalance look at
this there
there so what do we have the top of an
imbalance we have the second tap of an
imbalance quickly traded
away then we come up we have a third tap
of it we're we're failing to go above
this area we get a rejection away again
but then we get a double top within that
area and then we
short so these things you want to pay
attention to these things that happen
around these these particular areas you
want to pay attention to that because
often times it can give you some
indication even within this area here
give you some indication that we're
potentially
shorting because you should see a quick
tap to your
area you should see a tap and a quick
move away from it
that's what you should always see tap
into the area quick move away from
it and if you're not getting
that you know you're not getting any
play above this area and you have this
quick push out of this area three times
already and then we have a equal High
put in right here prime example to get
out you get out in what 25 Pips in
profit or so if you spotted this and
then you entered into a
short and then you short it out of the
the area again hey EA teer Jake that's
me oh okay okay yeah bangas exactly
exactly Shan
bangers calling out
bangers oh man user Raymond I think what
you who's who's Usher Raymond don't tell
me you think I look like Usher don't
tell me that somebody in Florida told me
that that I am it's my cousin she said
that I look like um Usher Raymond this
was years ago and I'm like um don't see
it you know and then with that little
Scandal he has going on he's giving out
ush bucks instead of um real money so
when he goes to certain obscene places
to throw money he's throwing ush bucks
he's not throwing real money that they
could
use wow yeah this is celebrities these
days you
know see look we get to tap into this
areir area here the beginning of the
area and we get a huge pushup not a huge
but 17 Pips pushup and then we
continue so that's why if we were in
this short and coming out of the
short does not
matter about what happened here didn't
give us any sideways movement to get out
so we're
continuing now we're back into this area
again this area here let's see what
price does with it does it run the low
or do we catapult out of this area for
another
high yeah I I I get that like quite a
few times where people think that
um it's like oh you look like Usher I
don't see it at all like at
all and his his um his reputation is
pretty bad right now so I didn't even
think I want to be compared them so look
we ta this line
here and we quickly got to push
up into this area here 16 Pips off of
this line
alone and and you know I get a lot of
people who ask how to find these zones
and I often show it you know
um like I I select exactly what I'm
doing and I I expect people to see it
and find it as well um you know most of
the time I'm finding things that people
aren't taking time to show me um and I
just try to simplify it and show others
in a simplified manner you know like I
could show you
why you know this could be an snd from
like a higher time frame area or
something like that um you know go back
and back test all the times where this
happened um but a lot of the times it's
that I really really really want people
to like one have some initiative and two
be able to learn this so it could very
well benefit them this is an area that I
told you guys about yesterday I said
that this was a hidden area a hidden snd
Zone that you often have in these Wicks
so look you get a tap from this hidden
snd Zone and we go all the way up to
what here what is this 31 Pips on this
scalp up you're
out and then if price comes back down
and gives us like a double bottom
somewhere within this area then we know
that we could potentially be gearing to
come back
up but if we're not
then you
know let me actually see so we put in
this low we took out this
High I mean we took out this
low we put in this we put in this High
took out this low trade it back above
the high and then came back within this
area so as long as we don't go below
this low we could potentially be looking
to continue
up cuz I don't really see another area
down
here yeah I don't really see another
area down
there um could this be the double bottom
so the reason why I I teach a lot of
this is because if you guys go back and
watch these videos the same way I
watched all of those garbage videos that
taught me nothing spent hours watching
them and taught me nothing at all if you
guys utilize that same amount of
time
to to watch the content that I put out
there you know and you consume it the
same way like you're writing down taking
notes of things if you guys do that I
want you guys to understand that you
will you will definitely be just as
profitable you would certainly have just
as much range that I have in terms of
trading I can go to any time frame I
don't know people that have that type of
range they're either a swing Trader or a
day trader or a
scalper but I don't know people who have
that same type of
range to be able to like do it from all
different time frames there's just a
select few people that I know that have
that it's either one specialty or the
other and some of them got some of them
have have nothing you know no
specialty but they be out there trying
to scam
people the the scamming part for me
that's what that's what makes me kind of
upset
because people already already don't
have money to
waste and if they already don't have
money to
waste why are you lying to them about
money that they could
make when you know that you don't even
know how to get to that level to make it
you see what I was saying about the the
the double bottom here guys I said that
could be the double bottom within
there look at this madness so you get a
scalp up that takes you 32 Pips
then you get a longer trade
up look at this look at this just from
noticing this and not just noticing this
double bottom in the
entry not just noticing the double
bottom in the entry but also noticing
the larger schematic of where we are
here also noticing that we tapped into
an area to the
left here so we're within an area where
we expecting a double bottom or or that
pattern at least and then within the
right side of the pattern we're looking
for the double bottom the first tap of
the pattern is the scalp the second tap
when it comes back down is the long into
potentially whatever area it could be
going into now it could be coming here
or it could be coming to this and
balance that's here that we have here
but it's just utilizing the rules it
happens over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over just as annoying as that
gets that's that's how much it happens
within this so what maybe we're going to
this imbalance here I don't know I
mentioned that if it comes above here
this area then within this let me
actually draw that a little cleaner
before somebody's like you said it was
going above the red line and it didn't
if it comes above this area here then
we could potentially be looking to take
it to
here this area or potentially even this
High we can come back to this High a
second time and this would be what an
equal high from across the way this
would be a second rejection out of the
imbalance from across the way as
well as well as the swing points this is
the last low this is the last High
so price can go all the way up into this
swing point and leave but price can
reject out of here too this imbalance
right here and take us back down why
because this imbalance was untapped we
just tapped it here this imbalance was
untapped and not just that the imbalance
is untapped but within the range of this
and this did this already tap into any
premium levels uh no it didn't so maybe
this this could continue up there a
possibility no premium levels within
here
yet we'll
see but we got the imbalance T that's
why I say that you don't forecast longer
than then immediately where you are you
don't forecast longer than
that because look we got the tap with a
scalp coming
down 19 pip scalp coming down now we
could be looking to take the high and we
have another imbalance above so let's
just watch this and see what could
potentially happen could it be a
Candlestick formation of a um double top
here yeah that's true that that could be
possible because look we have this
here and we have this snd Zone above so
let's see if it runs this
low
cuz usually the Run of this
low would cause us to push down give us
a retracement back up into the area give
us a double top up inside of an snd Zone
here and then potentially shorting out
to run the lows that could potentially
happen
[Music]
do we have any imbalances in
here you would think that my whole
system was based on
um imbalances because how much I talk
about
them uh but it's not it's actually just
based on the the
algorithm I kind of like this song has a
nice little jingle to
it I don't know what it's saying
but I kind of like house and edum a
little so a lot of people were bad
talking um the Drake album we trashing
it watch we got an area up here guys so
just be careful of that a lot of people
were back talking the um the Drake album
um and I mean it's it's clearly just a
house album um house music um a lot of
people who don't listen to house music
won't
really understand how like that that
album was a masterpiece most people said
it's garbage because they expect it
rapping I mean I don't listen to rap but
you know they expected rap rapping
coming from it and
um you know which which is
understandable if if it's his flow it's
usually what his fan base May um want
you know in particular so that that
makes some pretty good sense um this is
the last unmitigated area above up
here so you just want to make sure that
it doesn't come above this if it comes
above this area then it's going to
Target some of the highs but this could
very well just be the retracement back
down into somewhere within here and then
we end up pushing out to the highs if
this does retrace back down so that
would make this little low here fair
game price would just run that
low uh let me
see there another oh no there's no
balance here you see both of them touch
each
other this Wick touches this Wick even
if it extended down lower into this Weck
that's fine it's still a
f but there's
potentially an unmitigated area
somewhere within
here within
here but remember you do have this
imbalance
directly
above so you could have a short into
this area and then it Springs off of the
imbalance or it could end up coming down
into the unmitigated area and springing
off of that but it could spring off of
that give us equal highs up here and
still end up coming back down to run the
low
so this top was the top of this snd
here right here you see the Candlestick
pattern
here that we like to
see I tell people I don't say these
things for my health or try to like
sound good with it or you know like yeah
to Sauce I'm nice you know like I'm I I
don't like I don't need to I because if
I had to do that every time this
happened I'd be doing that the whole
stream you know CU this happens all the
time little Candlestick pattern I said
I'd like to see it gives me some
confidence that I'm in the right move is
there you know and this Candlestick
pattern here is just this larger chart
pattern here on the higher time frame
this Candlestick pattern is just
happening on on like a um one second or
something so look we tapped into this
snd here down below we got to push back
up are we just tapping into this area to
continue rejecting or are we coming
above it to actually run it and go up
into some of these highs we'll
see I mean this snd here was responsible
for this structural break above so
that's what probably why we tapped into
it and then we started to trade
higher but all of these different things
if you spot these things in real time
it's so so easy for you guys
to you know be able to trade off of it
like there there has to be like like a a
ton of Pips that we call all within like
all of this like coming down there has
to be a ton of it we talked about this
imbalance I mean this this area being
tapped and this was the last area that
price was in before it began to fall out
and look at this all the way down if you
held it this is 392 Pips in hour and a
half so if you were just on a measly one
lot size which let me not say measly
because it could come off as judgment to
other people but if you were just in on
a one lot size and you got the tap from
up there and you just held it all
throughout the stream while we were
talking at no point did we give an
indication that price will reverse and
go for any of the highs we even went
back and showed how it was possible that
would be bearish over the next couple of
days or so potentially you know because
price can change at any point Anything
Could Happen um but we mentioned that
that could
happen and that was just from up in this
area when when we finally got the stuff
going within the stream and stuff like
that we had this tap coming down so we
had price trading to this area because
we said if we ran this High we would tug
back into this area and then go long
so we had a long into a
short and we've been shorting ever since
which we said that we were bearish
overall but we were finding things
within here that were tradable so we did
find this imbalance that it tapped into
we got a rejection away from
it at this top let's say if you got in
on this imbalance price tapped
here and price took you all the way 154
Pips in 30 minutes just on that
imbalance
alone we're noting the little imbalances
that are here but we also like the
strong rejections away that's what we
want to see when it comes to the type of
imbalances we want to see a strong
rejection
away and that gives us that confidence
that prices moving out of that
area but again the first tap is the
scalp the second tap is the longer move
[Music]
all right me and my measly one
last you know you you're going to be
trading 400 500 Lots 1,000 Lots soon so
don't even worry about
it I mean I started
um I've never used anything you know
what's so interesting about that I've
never used anything lower than a one
even when I was losing I was still using
a one i' never used anything lower than
a one then I was like let me see about a
five and then let me see about a 10 and
then let me see about a 40 and then let
me see about a 100 and see how 400 moves
and and I'm like oh this is beautiful
great wonderful
so look we just took this High to the
left right here we just grabbed the high
that was
here let's see what this
does let me go back to any of
these things here this
is
gold so gold didn't give us another high
after tapping into this area
here we tapped in we left and we're
returning back to it
um because we didn't put in another
high
oh but we also didn't run the
low so go could be coming
here or this could be
where where it's reversing from if you
incorporate this high this whole range
here could be tapping into this and
going but there's also this little
imbalance in
here imbalance imbalance IM balance
imbalance IM balance IM balance
imbalance IM balance IM balance you see
how you could have thought that it was
going down to this area here but when
you actually factored in the
imbalance we got to tap here so we get a
scalp up from the
imbalance right here
this is a 144 pip scalp up usually the
TP of some streamers with your trades um
and then you can get a run of this
low and then or price can sideways
consolidate within this area as well but
we could also still make it down to here
realistically speaking I don't want to
mislead you guys to make you think that
we're ultimately not coming down here
there is a a possibility that we come
down into this
area
here so we end up running a low may not
find support then we'll end up running
through the imbalance
to
here so we're either going to here for
gold 126 or 124 possibility if we end up
running through um this imbalance here
but you probably just want to find
something on
the the higher time frame that could
potentially facilitate the low back down
and that might have been this imbalance
here and what often time um support and
resistance Traders are seeing is this
so they utilize this and if price comes
back up here again and gets rejected
they'll take the short out of this area
but there's no real
principles you know within this other
than I know ICT teaches something called
the breaker block or something like that
where price trades below it Taps back up
into it and then rejects away um I've
seen that happen I've seen it not happen
it's just just not as accurate for me to
um put it in my trading style at all so
yeah no I
wouldn't I wouldn't do
that so we tapped into this snd below
and we traded
higher within here
we tapped into this and put in another
high remember that we have this
imbalance
here see look even when we got our equal
High here even if you were shorting from
here
short to the next zone or the next
fractal or the next
imbalance short to that let that be your
take profit for
scalping for
scalping if you get the second entry to
take it for a longer trade still
consider the zones if you see these huge
Wick rejections that's enough for you to
to get
out you know to
to let me
see so we put in this low we took this
High we could be coming back
to maybe top here or further
below and
then further up to the imbalance
possibly hold
on
sorry about that
guys
um you see these Wicks how they act as
zon sometimes that you could potentially
get rejections from mind you this watch
this area cuz this could still be a
double bottom within this area to go and
take the
high because this was an area
where there was an entry found on it but
I have mentioned to you guys um that you
could tap into this area possibly and
then trade
higher so we got the top uh let me
and then we got to tap again to the
top so scalp from here to here and then
from
here you also have an entry to come down
with this this candle that
touched to come down here and if we see
that it's trading lower down to this snd
this might be the area where you get out
get in and pay if it it just all depends
on your account size but let's say you
have an account size and you're scalping
with this this one scalp for me the tap
here to come down here that's
$2,400 on a low lot
size and on a higher lot size that's
like 10
15,000 and on my highest lot size this
is this is like $25,000
just with a little scalp so it all
depends on your your um your lot size
and your account size but if you learn
the principles all together you could
reproduce it at any size of your account
any size within your account you could
reproduce that so this may continue to
go up from here this may not be stopping
here um because we didn't get a run of
this low um here as of yet we did run
this low which wait let me see this high
uh High 443 this high
is uh
443 so the Run of this low could be the
reason why this TAPS in and then this
could short the Run of this low here cuz
this low gave us the same
high so this could be a a pull out of
the area maybe even to this imbalance
here make it a wick below this imbalance
and then and tap up but yeah we we named
it a a market ERS because like I
mentioned like you know this is this is
precision now you don't get to retail
trading there's no there's no
Precision you know if if that's $2 for
you you could actually use a 15minute
time frame and make that 200 because
it'll be longer scalps scalps will be
longer moves um but uh you
know with your account size if you have
the same type of discipline over and
over and over again again with an
account size like this this could also
be coming down to this area here below
um cuz this is the snd that essentially
broke structure to the top side but you
have this imbalance you have this
fractal here and then you have this snd
here so if it's shorting you want to
look at some of these areas if it's
shorting below these areas you want to
look at some of these areas down below
cuz this could be an snd within
here
this could be a snd within here and this
could be a double bottom within the snd
where price ended up trading back up so
this could have been the first scalp
into the area back up this could be the
next touch into the area and then maybe
take the highs possibility or just come
to this snd above because this snd above
is not uh
mitigated it's not
mitigated
so we just be looking at that there's
this fractal here fractal here there's
this um imbalance here and then there's
a snd below here so we're looking to
potentially Target this area because
this area was responsible for this
structural break at the
top as well as this area is still
responsible for all of these breaking or
running these highs so you see what I
mentioned by trend lines how you know I
love the mention of the Cherry you got
me laughing too
much
Nicholas
yeah we TR $100 to $10,000 in donate to
charity while teaching us please the
cherry on top so I'm I'm actually
looking to um to do that I want to take
a small account to a larger account and
I want to do it live and I want to do it
with a couple of people who have the
same amount of money and I want to be
able to
take everybody's account to a certain
level so the $600 marker is what I like
to start with because that's what I
started with when I first started
trading but um you know you could even
do the 200 the 200 may take a little
longer than two weeks to do but if it
was 600 I could definitely get that 600
to to um uh 20,000 in in one week
definitely get it to 20,000 in one week
because look at this look at look at
look at these
entries that I
have
here let me make sure this isn't
copyrighted music before they flag My
Stream NOP it's
not um so
look we went from this imbalance here we
got our Candlestick pattern that we
usually like to see then we got a huge
mark down this was
here when
before price even got here price even
made this dip here and this was here
when price got here let's say I took
this trade from
here to here let's say I took it here
where I saw this flip happening it's 246
Pips on a one lot size oil is $10 per
pip so if you have 246 Pips $10 per Pip
this is
2400 within one hour 2400 in one hour
using a $600
account in one hour so yeah if it's $300
then you can take it to$ 10,000
definitely but either way this is still
one hour now granted people like why are
you using a one lot size with that much
money in your account you could blow
your account blah blah no it's not
blowing my account because I know what
I'm doing other people don't so yes I'm
I'm very precise if I lose in this trade
I'm losing
like five Pips or something like that
and it could be five Pips because it
could be coming to tap this imbalance
back here so I might have got in too
early and it came up to tap this
imbalance and then traded away but look
at this price tapped this area tapped
into this we fell we came back to this
imbalance what did we
get imbalance from the left side we came
back into this imbalance we got a double
top within our imbalance and then look
we push down to where the next imbalance
below
so another 2 hours later that's 150
Pips I'd be at $4,000
already just noticing these I I show
these all the time to people these are
so easy to catch and then look we tap
into this imbalance here and what do we
do we run from this low we get a double
tap on our imbalance so let's let's talk
about the scalp first we get a 30 pip
scalp 390 bucks we get in on another
entry this pushes all the way up here
maybe I would have got out here if I saw
this huge push down then I saw this
retracing back up maybe I would have got
out there look at that another 291 Pips
we'd already be at like
7500 just utilizing these little things
that I use to create these swing points
little tiny things and I could I could
trade all of this within here too all of
this all of this through here I could
trade all of that too so it's it's
really really really easy really easy
easy they forgot about the E the EA da
that's what I'm saying I definitely want
to look into the social trading but the
social trading has high spreads and high
commissions so that's the issue with
that social trading is cool but now you
have to trade from a higher time frame
just to make that even
work are you guys been writing in the
chat uh let's
see this says Sean on the cell
this is
NZ uh this
is uh Euro USD is
it bearus OT I hear people use that that
OT what what is that OT I I really don't
know what that
is um but I see uh there's this guy
named the OT Trader on YouTube I see him
use OT all the time I just don't know
exactly what that is
waiting for a bearish flip to play out
okay yeah that's cuz we flipped
below we had the stab put in we have the
left side even though it's shorter we
have the right side we could potentially
tap into that bearish um the 15minute uh
imbalance that's there um but we no we
got the we already tagged the imbalance
up top so that's cool so yeah we could
tag into that imbalance and then
continue down let's true um on the one
minute okay oh you don't have us30 you
might be using a regulat broker then um
we're going to find a way to help you
get to the the other broker um that has
us30 because it's so perfect no indices
at all and the Leever oh The Leverage is
1 to 1,000
oo
damn what what broker you have y'all got
any more of
those one to 1,000
yo I'd be making a million dollars a day
if I had that
leverage H looks like it hit the level
oh looks like it hit his 15minute level
let's check that
out uh where was
this so was this tap into this area we
did hit this snd
above um wait is that the oh that's the
one minute I think he
said is it the one minute or am I
tripping see look at this I said that
anytime there's a double
top a double top in the area if you just
take a square and put it around a double
top look price comes back Taps into it
gives you a short I had mentioned that
on stream
yesterday price tabs here K9 give you a
short of 12 Pips and then kept shorting
down but usually it's if you put a
square around the double top that
happens usually get that that tap you
put it around the first low I mean the
the the most recent low after it leaves
the area entirely and you just cover the
highs and Bam you get to tap right into
the area and a
short so yeah it's it's
uh yeah it's
sauce oh let me actually see though um
it was just a
fib optimal trade entry okay I need to
good broker my leverage one to
3,000
what yo I'd be so filthy rich with that
type of Leverage
man um what what oh let me let me just
look back at the 15 again
so this
is
1300 on the
so oh I time zones are
different uh Ryan what what time are you
in yeah our time zones are different
um let me
see oh this is the area that so that the
the OT Trader um he usually has this
this area marked out like
that yeah he usually has this area
marked
out um yeah this this could be
accumulation happening um with wof on
the 4H hour just to have um a
markup and potentially go to tag some of
the
highs but I think this is the area here
that we were more so
yeah yeah so this this could be that too
to to in turn try to get back up to some
of these highs possibly within this area
or
that but watch it because we could have
a run of this trend line low and the
real move could be down within here let
me change this music because I don't
know what this Piano Man is trying to
do so yeah we could we could potentially
have that um yeah that's that's a hell
of a lot of Leverage it's like wow
stopped it a bit early at an imbalance
won't enter it until it has the
imbalance
at
0528 yeah okay so the the
052 8
imbalance uh within here okay that makes
sense yeah that that makes a lot of
sense um up within this area and a lot
of times that can just grab a high
grab these highs cuz this is still trend
line as
well sometimes it could be just to go up
and grab the highs grab these highs and
then short back down below to
potentially the real move that's down
there and then it takes you up so it can
just pretty much do that just push back
up to this area reject from it and then
run the lows because you have trend line
lows here too so you could expect those
lows to be ran along with these equal
lows that are around here so the real
move may be further within this
area um just a little heads
up so I'm lost what did we mention about
this area we mentioned it IM balance tap
oh this is the double bottom on the
imbalance to the left right
here yeah you see what I'm saying about
imbalances guys like super super
important we rejected out of this area
we tapped this imbalance we came back up
to this area rejected out of this area
could have taken a short from this area
back down to the imbalance because it
could potentially be a second top within
there or a equal you know low or or a
double bottom within this area so we get
that we get the double bottom on the
imbalance for the body but we also get
the double bottom here
within this
area
sorry we get the double bottom in this
snd Zone Bam Bam we run out of it where
do we top up into here this
here but we also got imbalan Taps here
with in this area that facilitated this
push back down to the double bottom and
then the double bottom gave us the push
back up to this particular area here now
if this doesn't run this because the
double bottom can stop
here make sure there's no imbalances
under here there is a slight imbalance
here
look at that look at that look at that
no look at
that look at that
like look at
this
we could still run this High being that
we ran the
low but if not then this is a rejection
here to potentially come back down but
look what's left after we tapped into
this imbalance look what we left behind
this
Wick and all you're doing on the one
minute really is recreating zones oh you
use New York time okay so maybe my time
is wrong I'm see New
York
uh oh your your 1300 area was already
hit I didn't see that my bad so yeah it
is it is New York time my bad on
that but look at this imbalance how
mention we could still take this
High we take the high and what are we
tapping into are we tapping into this
area above that was left behind
oh we got the to of the front of
it imbalance to tap within the Zone 30
Pips up how many 30 40 pip bangers do we
see Within These Little movements of
scalping that we would probably be at500
Pips already
today just because of
that and now we're here at 35 what are
we running above this we're running
above this we still have an area above
here watch this equal high up
here this
is and this is why I teach the way I do
this is why I teach as long as I do this
is
because with videos that are back tested
everybody's a genius in hindsight
everybody with so so this may be
stopping here to potentially push back
up um with with videos that are in
hindsight people like I can go back to
whatever it is um or have the video just
up and ready by the time the video
starts rolling and because
you know it's in hindsight I may already
know what's happening back here you know
I mean of course I already know what's
happening back here I've been trading
most of this so I could literally go you
know like wherever this is whatever area
this could potentially be in I can go
and find the area remember the date the
time find the area and just be like uh
I'll take this area
here you know go just like this I'll
take this area
here uh maybe I want to use the whole
Zone and I go just like this maybe I
want to use the whole
zone so if price comes up and Taps into
my zone that's where I'm getting the
entry from and then I go like
this oh look you got to tap right into
the
Zone it happens every time this way you
know like people they sound so
believable and it's like bro you just
you remember the time you went back and
you know like do it in real time let's
let's see it in real time you most times
you you don't get it you know
but that's what I want to see like
that's why I make the the teaching the
way I do I hear um ICT who supposedly is
the the founder of smart money um I hear
that he's actually going to start live
trading soon and and he's going to start
live trading because he wants to weed
out all the people in the industry who
are trading behind zooms and who are
losing and who really don't know what
they're doing he's going to he he
believes there's an algorithm in price
too and he's saying that he's going to
trade the algorithm live so he I guess
make people a Believer or whatever it is
um I really don't care much to to do
that I trade because I love talking to
people and I love looking at charts and
both of them together together are
created on YouTube so that's why I trade
I'm not really looking to prove anything
to anybody cuz if you look at my trades
you can see it it's all in real time I'm
not hiding behind a mentorship or
anything like that I'm not saying that
anybody's hiding behind a mentorship
either you know like they may be
legitimate reasons for why people do
that maybe people don't want to share
their profits to people who are living
around them or who knows them or
whatever it is so you don't create this
this idea where people start to just
rely on you and depend on you for
whatever money they need you know so I
understand why people would use
mentorships to kind of hide behind that
you know but in the same sense it's like
you should be able to still do it on
demand you're an expert at this or
you're alleging that you're an expert at
this you should be able to do all of
this on demand all of this markup on
demand and this is for this this is just
our snds constantly shifting that's all
this one minute is doing it's const
stantly shifting our snds that's it and
all we're doing is we're adjusting to
the constant shifts of the snds and the
imbalances and this and that we're we're
just adjusting to all of that and as
long as we adjust to that in real time
then you know we we'll have the
move we'll always have the move or
always have a move within a market
always within a day we could have a move
I mean look at look at the the the um
the EU trade we call the EU trade from
up
here this is from 0
5396 we mentioned it was an imbalance
that it could tap up here and we
mentioned you don't get out until you
see price
shifting so like I said you might have
price come up take this High run into
here and then shift lower so we run the
trend line liquidity above but then we
also run the liquidity below and any
other equal highs equal lows that are
within that area we just run all of it
and that's sometimes how the the
algorithm aggressively
moves you know but we see certain things
we see it happen a certain way we see
shifts in price wherever it is that we
see it and see look look at this is what
I'm talking about I mentioned to you
guys the double entry the first one is a
scalp to come
down and the next entry is a longer
move and that's all within this area of
imbalance sometimes you'll get this
without
this sometimes you won't get that
sometimes it'll just be the tap but at
times where you get both entries those
are good for
you because now you're essentially
looking at how to become involved in
this
market and the way you become involved
in this at least you know if you saw
this particular
setup we violated this low we ta back
into this area
here we violated this low we came back
up into this
area we're expecting to come back up
into this area but what are we expecting
we're expecting potentially an imbalance
touch
here or maybe one within here smaller
area of
price after we ran this low what did we
get a tap into the first imbalance
here's why I said play the first
imbalance one because ICT had mentioned
it and he gave credible reasons why but
two because I've seen it happen for
myself so I'm not going to tell you guys
to do something that I don't normally do
when I'm
trading I'm only making you guys stick
to that so you have this balance above
you have this imbalance below you get to
tap on the imbalance and just 1 minute
after tapping the imbalance we begin to
shred and then where are we shredding
into down into here this was a $5 move
on gold and this scalp was a $2 move on
gold and that's how you get two entries
from the same area from the same area so
AZ had mentioned to me that you know
with with this in particular um does it
work on gold and I tell them yeah it
does it it's the same thing over and
over and here you have it it's the same
thing that happened on gold while we
were away Lo Lolly gaging looking at
whatever it is we're looking at and we
have the setup happened the same way and
all you do is find a setup and you're
you're golden you're in the
clear just finding a setup up so look we
had another tap back into this snd
here on the lower time frame the snds
are usually
shifting so we had another tap back into
this area here we didn't get a
mitigation of the middle so watch the
push back up into this area it could run
the high give us the middle of the the
the um mitigation and then trade us
lower there's an imbalance that's right
here right below it so you just want to
pay attention to
that but this is just rejecting from
this same snd zone so it's it's going
right here let me show you
guys from this Zone
up to this
above this area
above
and all it's doing
is up down up down up down I talk about
this all the time sometimes you have
price just going between
snds and we're running lows and highs in
here we can just continue to do that the
whole
time until we finally get a breakout
above or we get one
below but we can do that the entire
time while price is
ranging I felt like that was a lot today
guys I felt like I I you know taught a
lot mentioned a lot that that you know I
feel like this this would be a good
video to go into um the earn and learn
section but I feel like I I you know
taught Hefty you know it's like a hefty
style of teaching this actually might
be the tap in here to potentially run
this high so watch
it
[Music]
um yep just got the run of the
high see that